I've been waiting for that sun to shine endlessly, without wavering.
I've been waiting for those clouds to drift through the blue skies!
I've been waiting for the freedom to sleep in as late as I want!
It's here.
It's here!
It's finally here!
Summer vacation!
Hey!
It's so hot.
yappari kimi da yo ne
Oh hey, it's you
honto odoroita yo
You startled me
futari yoku aruita namikidoori
Here we are, on the tree-lined road we walked so often
otona ni naru no wo
I couldn't wait to grow up
matezu ni toozaketeitta no wa watashi datta ne
and I kept you at a distance, didn't I
itsumo
As always,
mainasu ichido no ame ga furu
the icy rain falls
kimi ga kureta namida
comprised of tears you cried for me
sono yasashisa made wakaranakute
That kindness I didn't understand
zutto kono mune wo shimetsuketa
lay heavy on my heart all the time
mainasu ichido no ame ga furu
The icy rain falls
tsumetasugiru namida
comprised of tears unbearably cold
hagurakasu taido ni okotteta keredo
Although I was angry at my evasive personality
jitsu wa sukuwareteitan da ne
you cured me of that, didn't you
Let's play!
Impossible.
What?
I have a bunch of people to save.
People to save?
What? Yukki, are you doing volunteer work?
I guess.
After all, I'm motivated by more than just money.
What's this? An incident?
Yuuki, if you don't hurry it up, they'll all die.
We can't let that happen.
What did Chizuru want?
Who knows?
Go home.
I haven't even said anything yet!
I already know what you want.
That makes things easy!
What do you want to do? Where should we go?
Hey, where should we go?
I'm told you that I'm not interested in going out!
I'm busy!
See you later.
Wait.
Just one minute. Just talk to me for one minute.
You have a minute to talk, don't you, ma'am?
This'll make your skin silky-smooth.
What are you, a door-to-door salesman?
Coming.
Oh, Chizuru-kun.
I'm surprised you found your way here.
Are you free? Do you want to go out?
Huh? Um, well...
You can't, either?
Oh, that's not what I meant.
Let's see...
Would you like to join me?
Join you?
What's this?
I was making snacks.
I've never done it before,
but since we're on vacation,
I thought I'd give it a go.
Would you like to help me?
Why not?
Let's do it.
Oh, good. Can you mix that dough for me?
This?
Yes.
Chizuru-kun, you're good at that.
Huh?
There you go again. I'm still learning.
That smells good.
It really does. I hope it turns out well.
Tastes about right.
Shun-chan, that's no fair.
Oh, sorry.
Here.
It's deliciously sweet and light in my mouth!
I look forward to seeing how they'll turn out.
Me, too.
Once we're finished,
we should take them to...
What is this strange feeling?
It's like I'm not really myself...
Um...
Are you bored?
Now that we've come this far,
we should finish making...
Making what? A new me?
What?
You wanted someone to hang out with,
so you went to everyone's houses.
That's right. It's summer vacation,
but everyone's hiding in the cool air of their rooms.
It's really hot today.
But there's a whole month ahead of us,
so I'm sure there will be opportunities to play outside...
What about a festival?
A festival?
There's one today.
It'll be cool at night, and I'm pretty sure everyone would go if I invite them.
What do you think?
Shun-chan, thank you!
Thanks to you, I think I'll have a wonderful summer vacation!
Everyone should have their own Shun-chan.
Thanks to him, I can start to enjoy my...
It's her.
Hey!
I can't believe they didn't have anything smaller.
That looks heavy.
Need help carrying it?
I'm fine. Leave me alone.
You should learn to accept others' kindness...!
She looks like a sheep.
Oh, here it is! The invitation to the festival!
Let's see. "Can everyone make it? Let me know."
Of course I'll go!
Hey, what about you?
Hey!
Shun-chan invited me to a festival.
That was how our summer began.
A Japanese festival!
Why are you wearing a yukata?
It's a festival, you should to wear a yukata! It's refreshing!
Shouldn't you buy a baby chick at a festival?
Don't buy one. Our apartment doesn't allow pets.
There's so many to choose from.
There's so many that I don't know where to start.
I know, right? I can't decide, either.
I'm hungry.
Let's get something to eat.
"Something"?
No! Not just "something"!
As students, we don't have a large budget.
If we don't carefully and precisely choose the right food stall, we'll regret it for sure!
But there are so many choices...
I don't know what to pick.
Calm down!
In a situation like this, start with the classics! First off, we'll go with...
Takoyaki!
Hey.
Why don't we all buy something different and share?
I see.
Good idea, Yuutan!
A high schooler who knows his festivals!
Is the plan that praise-worthy?
This is delicious.
That was a really good idea!
Yes, but...
Yuuki!
Pass it around already!
Don't worry, you'll have your fair chance...
...eventually.
A fight breaks out every time we buy something.
How long are you gonna hold on to that?
Don't worry. I'll eat it so you don't get fat, Mary.
Mary?
Oh, yeah. Her hair's kinda fluffy, like a sheep's.
A sheep?
Masaki-chan?
That's not true!
Ow!
What was that for?
Masaki-chan, where are you going?
Oh, um...
So cute!
They really are.
I really wanted one when I was little,
but I could never get one.
Goldfish are so quick.
Here, Shun-chan.
Thank you, Masaki-chan.
All right!
Here you are.
Take your time, Miss.
You going for it, Mary?
Now!
Wait!
Miss, you don't know what you're doing, do you?
It rips! That thing rips!
Here's your consolation prize.
Hey, Mary.
I thought I could do it.
Don't get so down about it. You almost got one.
Don't touch me!
And why do you keep calling me "Mary"?
Don't give me weird nicknames!
Stop it. Cut it out.
Just leave me alone!
That hurt. I came to cheer you up.
You're not cute at all.
Is Masaki-chan okay?
I can't help her.
Masaki-chan.
Forget her.
If you get close--
Leave him.
Here.
Shun-chan.
Think of it as a consolation prize.
I'll treasure it.
I'll treasure it!
What was that about?
She gets super mad at me,
but treats Shun-chan like that.
Well, sorry, but I'm not any good at cheering people up.
She doesn't laugh with anyone except Shun anyway, right?
Let's go.
Is that right?
Sounds like she's in love with...
Huh?
What?
What?! Is she?!
I didn't hear the melody of love bubbling beneath the surface!
It's not underneath the surface. It's obviously above!
Really? So that's why she...
She's not cute at all.
What's the matter?
Are you boys rookies, too?
Sorry.
It's okay. This paper's too thin
to catch anything that's alive.
I'm sure that's the point of a game like this.
I feel like it shows no respect for their lives.
Hush.
Value is subjective.
His business is making a game of their lives.
Don't you agree?
You And Me.
What a generous man.
I can't believe he gave us five layers of paper.
I caught so many goldfish that I had to return some.
I'm sure you did something to make him do that.
But why Shun-chan?
He's the least manly of all of us, and like, more cute than cool...
In fact, if we're just talking about his face, he's my type...
No, no, no! That's not what this is about!
What are you mumbling about?
But...!
Sometimes, you don't even know why you like or dislike someone.
Shun-chan!
Masaki-chan!
Doesn't she look like a sheep in a flock?
Shun-chan!
She does.
More importantly, we should help her.
Kaname?
Hisako, you're here, too?
Yeah.
Onee-chan.
Onee...
Oh, Kaname-kun. So you're here, too.
Yeah.
Do you want some?
Onee-sama!
I'm Kaname-kun's friend, Chizuru.
Would you like to set off some fireworks later?
I promise it'll be a wonderful night.
Fireworks?
When did you make that plan?
We don't have any fireworks.
If love always went according to plan, heartbreak wouldn't exist.
They should sell fireworks at the supermarket.
I think there's one nearby, so I'll go check it out.
Should we go, too?
Okay.
But...
It's okay. We were just saying it'd be nice to get out of the heat.
I see. Thank you.
Where's Shun-chan?
The three of them are going shopping for fireworks.
What?
It's okay. Don't get flustered.
I have the keyring that Shun-chan gave me!
It's missing!
Masaki-chan.
Do you want to come with us?
Uh, no. I'm fine.
Really? Okay.
It should be around here somewhere.
Sorry.
Excuse me.
It's okay. Don't get flustered.
I'll just start from over there again.
What are you doing?
Don't go off by yourself, Mary.
Oh, you dropped something.
Seriously?
Leave me alone!
Why are you acting so tough?
What am I gonna do with you?
We'll help you look—
I didn't ask for your help!
Listen, an attitude isn't going to make your flat chest—
Let's go, Yukki! Forget her!
If you're going to search by yourself, try not to look so upset.
Right after I said not to...
Mary.
What is that?
So, you want us to help look?
Fine, but...
Why are you so beat up, Chizuru?
Ask her.
It cost 700 yen.
It's pretty crowded from here to the shrine.
It won't be easy.
Let's split up and search.
Sensei! The class is trying to work together,
but Yuuta-kun isn't participating seriously!
Yuuta-kun, I know you want to look at the girls outside in gym class,
but you have to put some effort in now.
You, too.
Sensei, I found it.
Found what?
Seriously?
Hey, shorty. Is that really it?
What is it, little girl?
That's it.
I dropped that bear. Could I have it back?
That? I found it.
And she's the one who dropped it.
Do you have any proof?
What?
If you don't have any proof, you can't have it.
But, I said...
If you want it, shoot it down.
300 yen per round.
I'll never grow up to become that kind of adult.
More like, you'll never become that kind of person, right?
I can't believe he'd make something he found a prize.
Thank you—
You idiot!
I can't believe you let your emotions get to you!
Let go!
Calm down.
That's right.
If you get emotional,
you won't be able to aim properly.
You're too calm about this!
Fine.
I'll do it.
All right.
Hey, you shouldn't laugh at people who are trying their hardest.
That was Kaname's best effort.
You're not helping.
You can do it, Yuutan!
This might be hard with such a small target.
That's right! It's not easy! Right?
For something like this...
We should rely on someone who's cleared countless missions before.
Well?
The size of the target doesn't matter.
Kill or be killed. That's all that matters.
It's not that serious.
What are you aiming at?!
I couldn't choose between them.
I don't believe you, Yuuki.
And now we're out of bullets.
There's nothing we can do.
They got the fireworks, so they're coming back.
Shun-chan's coming back.
He'll know I dropped it!
Old man, I need some bullets.
What?
You're already paying with bills?
So much for saving money by sharing food.
If I get it, you're paying me back, Mary.
Whoops.
You're one to talk.
Shut up.
1 round (5 shots) 300yen
Damn it.
What's wrong? You have one shot left.
I know!
Should I take over?
You stay still.
Damn it.
Who said I could do it if I fired enough shots?
Now I'm just wasting money.
Namu... Namu... Namu... Namu...
Here.
Thanks.
Why is a young girl like you chanting, "Namu, namu"?
But maybe that's why I managed to hit it.
Who knows, huh?
You're right.
They're back.
We're back!
Welcome back!
We bought fireworks.
I'm the one who got it back.
Amazing. There are so many.
We have more!
She's not cute at all.
Let's fire them off together later.
Yeah!
Should we save the sparklers for last?
If you get too close to me,
you'll get burned!
You're the one coming towards me!
Chizuru-kun, that's dangerous!
As the fireworks gently nudged back the night,
everyone's smiles were there as always.
A firework's glow is short lived,
just like your life.
If you don't stop playing around, you'll get hurt!
I can't believe they'd mess around like that.
Wielding fireworks is a serious contest.
No, it's not!
I never thought the time would come when I would sometimes softly open my hand
to look at the ordinary days that I'll treasure and hold on to forever, accumulated in my palm.
Look over here.
A photo with just me and Shun.
Here we go!
That looks fun.
Go right ahead.
Don't hold back. Go enjoy yourself.
What?
That's not what I meant.
I probably won't realize it until I'm an adult.
One Summer
boku wa nakimushi de kuyashikute dakedo
It pains me to be such a crybaby,
anata ni ima tsutaetain da
but I want to tell you my feelings right now
tada massugu ni boku wo mitsumeru tsuyokute
There you stand, silently gazing at me
Allowing me to answer those strong and gentle eyes of yours
yasashii sono hitomi ni kotaeru tame ni
itsushika miushinatteta ichiban taisetsu na mono mo
You taught me what I lost sight of
sotto anata ga oshiete kureta
What was most important to me
tashika ni sou omoeru kara
I have no doubts about that
boku wa yowamushi de iya datta dakedo
I hated how weak I was
motto motto tsuyoku naru kara
but I will continue to become stronger
anata no koto wo mamoreru you na boku ni naru kara
I will be someone who could protect you
dakara sukoshi mattete
So wait a little longer for me
Next time: Glasses and Et cetera
Glasses and Et cetera