Bye-bye!
See you tomorrow.
Hello?
What? Right now?
It's not impossible, but...
What? Shun-chan's speaking so casually!
Fine. I'll bring it.
Who cares if he does?
Okay, see you then.
What's going on, Shun?
It's just that Fuyuki and I mixed up our English notebooks.
He said he'll be in big trouble if he doesn't turn his in today,
so he asked me to bring it to him at school.
Oh, dear.
Who's Fuyuki?
My younger brother.
He's a second year in middle school.
Younger brother?
Shun-chan, you have a younger brother?
I have two older sisters, too...
What? I totally thought your family was all women...
It certainly seems that way to his brother.
So, I have to make a trip to the middle school today.
Sorry, guys. I'm off.
I'll go with you.
I'd like to see my old school again.
But...
I haven't been there since graduation.
All right! I'm coming, too!
I wanna see the middle school you guys attended!
Hey, does Fuyuki-kun look like Shun-chan?
Maybe a little.
Really?
Th-Thank you for looking after my brother.
What'll I do if he's that cute?
I could never choose!
You don't have to choose...
Okay! Let's go see Fuyuki-kun!
Go!
yappari kimi da yo ne
Oh hey, it's you
honto odoroita yo
You startled me
futari yoku aruita namikidoori
Here we are, on the tree-lined road we walked so often
otona ni naru no wo
I couldn't wait to grow up
matezu ni toozaketeitta no wa watashi datta ne
and I kept you at a distance, didn't I
itsumo
As always,
mainasu ichido no ame ga furu
the icy rain falls
kimi ga kureta namida
comprised of tears you cried for me
sono yasashisa made wakaranakute
That kindness I didn't understand
zutto kono mune wo shimetsuketa
lay heavy on my heart all the time
mainasu ichido no ame ga furu
The icy rain falls
tsumetasugiru namida
comprised of tears unbearably cold
hagurakasu taido ni okotteta keredo
Although I was angry at my evasive personality
jitsu wa sukuwareteitan da ne
you cured me of that, didn't you
I was delighted when my brother was born.
A hand smaller than my own.
A smile more innocent than my own.
But now...
Th-Thank you for looking after my—
You're late, Shun-nii.
Jeez. I came as fast as I could.
Here's your notebook.
It's damn cold out here.
Besides, don't I always tell you to turn things in ahead of—
Yeah, yeah.
Don't give me that. Listen to me properly.
Yuuki-kun, how exactly are these two alike?
Huh? Their hair's kinda similar.
You idiot!
I wasn't asking about such fine details!
Who's the one with the weird hair?
I was speaking in more general terms!
What middle school do you go to?
I'm not a middle schooler!
School of insects?
No!
Fuyuki!
I'm sorry, Chizuru-kun.
Um, this is my younger brother, Fuyuki.
No way.
What sort of genetic mystery would have to occur to create such different siblings?
Come on, Fuyuki.
This is my friend, Tachibana Chizuru-kun.
Oh, the guy you're always talking about.
Oh...
Nice to—
So tiny!
Fuyuki!
They're nothing alike!
This place hasn't changed a bit.
I was wondering why you brought everyone.
You're all here to see the school, huh?
Yes.
You look like you've grown since we saw you last.
Can you tell? I'm a growing boy, after all...
Damn. Shorts...
You've become a healthy young man
since the last time we saw you, Fuyuki.
Huh?
Oh, yeah. I'm real healthy.
So lend me some porn sometime.
Fuyuki!
How can you say something like that in public?
But Shun-nii, you don't have any.
You're so boring.
If you don't use it, you'll lose it.
Normally, older brothers have porn somewhere.
Why do you keep saying that in public?
Middle schoolers are at that age.
He's suddenly curious about all sorts of things.
Don't worry about it.
Wow, he's way ahead of you, Shun.
Shun hasn't even started yet.
My, my.
Curious middle school boys are quite a handful, aren't they?
If there's anything you want to know, you can just ask us.
I'll tell you everything you want to know.
Okay, I heard this from my friend...
Is it true that a girl's boobs feel like your upper arm?
I guess you could say that your first kiss tastes like lemons.
I'm not asking about lemons.
Hey, wait.
Is that true? They feel like upper arms?
Don't ask me! Just tell him something!
As his elder, I can't just make something up!
Then what was that answer about lemons about?
Wait a minute. If he heard it from his friend, doesn't that mean his friend has...
That's enough!
Oh, come on. None of you know?
High schoolers are nothing special.
I was going to ask you more questions, too,
because I got a girlfriend recently.
Come on! What's with this?
Just because you know more than us and have a girlfriend...
You're younger than us,
so please don't act all high and mighty!
You just said "please."
A crushing defeat.
Fuyuki, you got a girlfriend?
I didn't know.
Well, yeah.
Damn it! Show us this girlfriend of yours!
Where is she? Where is she now?
Why do you want to see her so badly?
Because I want to!
How about a picture...
A picture will do, right?
Hey, Matsuoka-kun!
Bringing your phone to school again!
I told you not to do that!
I'll be confiscating it.
Hey, wait...
Come on! Show us! Show us the real thing!
Show us, show us.
Fine, fine!
Is this a dojo?
Your girlfriend's in the Kendo Club?
Yeah.
Listen, you're only gonna look!
Once you get a glimpse of her, get outta here!
Okay, okay, okay.
Oh, what's this?
Asaba and Matsuoka, it's good to see you again.
It's nice to see you again.
It really is.
I haven't seen you guys even once since you left the club.
Sorry.
Huh?
What?
Yuuta and Shun were both in
the Kendo Club during middle school.
What? Seriously?
Hey, why don't you give it a go for old times' sake?
You can show these kids a thing or two!
Oh, no...
Right?
Um, I've really forgotten what to do.
Hey, these guys are going to teach you today!
They're your seniors!
Okay!
He's not listening.
A-Amazing!
The last samurai of the 20th century!
Yuuta, you're so cool.
More like scary, with the way he's knocking them down left and right so indifferently.
Huh? Matsuoka?
Mamiya!
What are you doing here?
Nothing, I just...
My brother said he wanted to see the Kendo Club again.
Oh.
Your brother? Oh, right.
You did say that he used to be in the Kendo Club.
Mamiya, what are you doing without your protective gear?
I just came back from the bathroom.
Are you his girlfriend?
Oh, um...
You should be careful.
If you don't watch out, this pervert will eat you...
Hey, that hurt!
You're lucky I'm used to being hit on the head!
Shut up!
I told you to just look!
Don't say weird things to her!
Oh, I see.
I bet you act all innocent in front of your girlfriend.
Hey, everyone!
Whether asleep or awake,
Matsuoka Fuyuki's got nothin' but dirty thoughts in...
Matsuoka, that's dangerous!
You shouldn't swing a sword at people without protective gear on!
But he's spreading lies about me...
Upper arm...
Matsuoka?
N-Nothing.
Hey, Mamiya! Get back to practice!
Yes, sorry!
I'll call you tonight, okay?
Sure.
Hey, you!
That's twice now!
Look at these bumps!
Oh, crap. My phone!
It was confiscated. I've gotta get it back.
Get it back?
It's your fault for bringing—
Mamiya's gonna call me tonight!
I can't answer if I don't have it!
If that happens, she might call my house.
If I'm taking a bath at the time,
my parents will answer.
If they ask me who that girl was... What would I tell them?
You're surprisingly...
What?
I don't have time for you guys.
Hold on, young man!
Let us big bros help you out!
Why are you including us?
Don't bring me into this.
You And Me.
Oh, crap. There's a whole load of teachers in there.
And Obata's near my phone.
Don't worry, young man!
Trying and failing is a part of youth!
There's no tomorrow for us!
And they say failure is the root of success.
What I'm most worried about is you guys
assuming we'll fail from the very beginning.
Put some effort into it.
Do you guys really want to do this?
You idiot! It's not that easy!
It's only a matter of time before they see through my disguise!
My uniform fits you perfectly!
That's the only thing that's perfect.
What did you say?
A uniform can't conceal my adult appeal!
I wouldn't worry about that.
You don't have any appeal to hide.
We'll just have to go for it!
Go forth, warrior! Asaba Yuuki!
It's nice to see you again, Sensei.
What?
Oh, my, Asaba-kun?
What are you doing here?
It's good to see you.
You've matured quite a bit.
I see.
Obata-sensei, is he one of your former students?
Yes.
He's a second year high school student now?
You've grown.
Damn it.
Ow!
What are you doing? Hurry—
Hold on. Give me your phone.
What?
It'll be a decoy!
If the phone she confiscated suddenly disappears, she'll get suspicious!
You're crazy. Why does it have to be mine?
I thought you said you'd help me out!
I need that help now, you bug!
Hey, stop treating me like an insect!
Shut up and give me...
All right, got...
No, you don't!
My, my.
I-I'm so sorry!
Pickled plums... Pickled plums...
H-Hang in there!
Huh?
Where's my phone?
You mean this?
Oh, thank...
Don't you know that you shouldn't bring your phone to school?
He confiscated it.
Moron!
Matsuoka...
He was acting kind of weird...
I wonder what happened...
That graduate guy was so cool!
Jeez! Why are we wearing our gear at a time like this?
It stinks.
I think we could've stood a chance in our uniforms.
What does that mean?
It's only slightly sprained.
It should be fine with just a bandage.
Th-Thank you.
Are you all right? It's dangerous to lose your focus.
Yes, I'm sorry.
Huh? There's no answer.
What should I do?
What if Matsuoka thought my protective gear smelled...
It stinks!
Um, Mamiya-san?
Yes?
Sorry, but I have to get going.
I'll stay with her.
Really? Thanks.
I'm alone with Matsuoka's older brother!
I better not do anything stupid!
Um, Mamiya-san...
Y-Yes?
I'm Fuyuki's brother.
It seems like... you've been taking good care of my brother lately, so...
No, he's been taking care of me.
Let me know if anything happens.
You know how Fuyuki's got such a foul mouth and he's violent?
Our microwave wasn't working recently.
He said hitting it would fix it,
and now it's even more broken.
That sounds like Matsuoka.
You're right. He's foul-mouthed and violent,
but sometimes he's nice and it makes my heart jump...
I mean, out of surprise!
It jumps out of surprise...
Yes. Fuyuki is kind sometimes.
When we were younger and I hurt myself,
he would try to carry me,
even though he was smaller...
Hey, don't be so angry.
Sorry. We did everything a couple of old men could do.
That's right! I even sacrificed my own phone.
What? Your phone was lost in vain.
How worthless!
I'd beat the crap out of you if you weren't Shun-chan's brother!
Okay, okay.
Damn it. Why'd I have to go and grope that old lady teacher?
It would've been great if her boobs were soft like an upper arm—
M-Mamiya!
Matsuoka.
D-Did she hear that?
Wh-What?
What are you two doing here?
Oh, I'm just...
Ow...
Are you okay?
Yes.
Fuyuki, Mamiya-san hurt her—
Shun-nii, I hope you didn't say anything weird to Mamiya while I was gone.
What?
About porn or upper arms!
What are you worried about, you pervert?
Shut up! I don't wanna hear anything from you!
The smell of my armor!
I've gotta get back to practice.
What's that smell?
Mamiya?
Hey, what's wrong with...
Get away from me!
Hey, Fuyuki-kun, what's wrong?
Hey.
Shut up! Can't you tell?
I'm dead!
She got really pissed when I grabbed her upper arm.
Ah, it's over.
She must've found out that I'm a pervert.
It's fine.
I'm just a guy who thinks more about raunchy things than recycling things.
I don't care about saving the Earth.
Just leave me alone.
You shouldn't be so hard on yourself.
Maybe she hates me.
You're right, Fuyuki.
She might hate you if you don't do anything.
H-Hey, Shun-chan!
You're too busy thinking dirty thoughts to even...
pay attention to anything else.
What do you mean by that?
It's not like I think about it all the time—
Then what was that smell?
Don't you think there's something...
you should be worrying about more than yourself?
What, what?
What's going on?
Ow...
What am I going to do? I'm so embarrassed.
My protective gear must've reeked.
He must hate me.
I've never heard of a girlfriend with stinky gear.
Matsuoka!
No!
No, no, no, no!
Get back! I smell of stinky gear right now!
I knew it! A bandage!
What?
I knew this was the source of that smell.
Hey, what'd you do to your foot?
Oh, I sprained it a little.
You sprained it? Why did you run, then?
You need to rest!
Oh, yes. Sorry...
You shouldn't practice any more today.
I'll walk you...
I'll walk you home.
No, it's fine!
Huh?
You don't need to take me home.
What will I tell my parents if they ask me who you are?
Tell them I'm your boyfriend.
My phone's been confiscated,
so could you call my house?
Okay.
Middle school kids are so far ahead these days.
This must be what they call a "generation gap".
No, it's not. We're only three years older than them.
Chizuru, you've had a busy day.
You even ended up having your phone confiscated.
Look on the bright side. Unlike Fuyuki,
Chizuru doesn't have a girlfriend to call him.
No, that's actually pretty dark.
Forget it!
Ah, this sucks...
You can go get your phone whenever you want.
Shun-chan, where did Fuyuki-kun go wrong?
Wasn't he a good kid before?
Before? He was always...
foul-mouthed and violent...
Oh come on! That means he hasn't changed a bit!
Yes. He hasn't changed at all.
He's foul-mouthed and violent,
but sometimes he shows a kind side.
He may not have much going for him, but please look after him.
Middle School Diary
boku wa nakimushi de kuyashikute dakedo
It pains me to be such a crybaby,
anata ni ima tsutaetain da
but I want to tell you my feelings right now
tada massugu ni boku wo mitsumeru tsuyokute
There you stand, silently gazing at me
Allowing me to answer those strong and gentle eyes of yours
yasashii sono hitomi ni kotaeru tame ni
itsushika miushinatteta ichiban taisetsu na mono mo
You taught me what I lost sight of
sotto anata ga oshiete kureta
What was most important to me
tashika ni sou omoeru kara
I have no doubts about that
boku wa yowamushi de iya datta dakedo
I hated how weak I was
motto motto tsuyoku naru kara
but I will continue to become stronger
anata no koto wo mamoreru you na boku ni naru kara
I will be someone who could protect you
dakara sukoshi mattete
So wait a little longer for me
The Sunshine Song
Next time: The Sunshine Song.