You always get that, Chizuru.
Is it really that good?
100% fruit juice.
Mixed Juice
With all of the different fruits in here, I feel like I'm getting a good deal!
Let me have a taste.
Don't do that!
Give me some of your apple juice, then!
Give me some, give me some!
But you have apple juice in your mixed fruit juice.
No buts!
Hey, you!
Give it back!
My 100% fruit juice!
How do you guys keep up the 100% stupidity all the time?
100%, damn it!
Damn it! You bastard!
It's not that great.
100%!
Our unchanging daily routine.
While we enjoy these quiet days,
the slightest change causes great excitement.
Sorry I'm late.
I forgot something.
It's the workplace experience list.
Workplace experience?
Yes.
Regarding Work Experience Placement
yappari kimi da yo ne
Oh hey, it's you
honto odoroita yo
You startled me
futari yoku aruita namikidoori
Here we are, on the tree-lined road we walked so often
otona ni naru no wo
I couldn't wait to grow up
matezu ni toozaketeitta no wa watashi datta ne
and I kept you at a distance, didn't I
itsumo
As always,
mainasu ichido no ame ga furu
the icy rain falls
kimi ga kureta namida
comprised of tears you cried for me
sono yasashisa made wakaranakute
That kindness I didn't understand
zutto kono mune wo shimetsuketa
lay heavy on my heart all the time
mainasu ichido no ame ga furu
The icy rain falls
tsumetasugiru namida
comprised of tears unbearably cold
hagurakasu taido ni okotteta keredo
Although I was angry at my evasive personality
jitsu wa sukuwareteitan da ne
you cured me of that, didn't you
Oh, yeah. We got a sheet like that.
I haven't really looked at it yet, though.
Is that the field trip second years take each year?
Just look at this.
Our old kindergarten, Hidamari Kindergarten, is on the workplace experience list.
You're right.
So why don't we all go
to Hidamari Kindergarten together?
Good idea.
I wonder if Kaori-sensei's still there.
Don't you?
What?
Don't ask me!
I was just a kid.
I wonder if they have more playground stuff now.
They might.
Hey, Chizuru...
Oh, go right ahead.
Don't worry about me. Have all the fun you want.
Outsiders will quietly observe from over here.
Stop your annoying pouting.
I'm not pouting.
I'm the only one who attended a different kindergarten.
I do feel a little out of the loop,
but I wouldn't pout over something like that.
Your lip is sticking out even as you say that.
Chizuru-kun.
Chizuru-kun, come with us.
But I didn't go there.
That's not important.
I want to go with you.
Shun-chan...
Thank you!
You're the only one, Shun-chan!
You're the only one who hears my inner thoughts!
You actually said them out loud.
It's decided, then.
We're all going to Hidamari Kindergarten.
Yup.
I'm so excited!
Yeah, me too.
I wonder how Kaname's love life will unfold.
I told you that I don't feel that way any more!
Many seasons have come and gone,
and although much time has passed,
we always recall our childhood.
We were both excited and somehow apprehensive about visiting the kindergarten.
This brings back memories.
It hasn't changed one bit.
Was the jungle gym always this small?
The kindergarten hasn't changed, but we've certainly grown.
Those kids don't even let the cold stop them from playing.
You're right.
It's the middle of winter, too.
Huh? What'd you say?
What's with you, Kaname? Are you nervous?
You can't blame him.
He's about to meet his beloved Kaori-sen—
Listen up, you guys.
You better not say a word about it.
If that little monkey finds out about this...
you understand what'll happen, don't you?
Okay.
So this is your kindergarten!
Chizuru-kun, where are you going?
I'm just going to look around!
Ow.
Chizuru-kun, are you all right?
You little... Who are you?
No, who are you, illegal trespasser?
Hey, that's dangerous!
Not that I care what happens to this monkey.
We're just here for our workplace experience—
Listen to me!
I don't listen to evildoers!
Really, we're not!
We're— Ow!
My hair's stuck...
Shun-chan!
W-W-Wait!
Thank you.
You should be more careful, Miss.
A woman's hair is her life.
I'm actually a man.
What?
Either way, it seems we've done something unfortunate.
Huh?
Who cares?
It's already dead.
It's not dead.
It'll grow new leaves in the spring.
It will?
You think you can do whatever you want?
Gotcha, you brat!
We'll turn you in to your teacher!
Let go of me, stupid monkey and stupid four-eyes!
Hey, guys...
Ow, stop struggling!
Kaname-kun, Shun-kun, Yuuta-kun, Yuuki-kun!
Hey!
Keep a tight grip on him, Kanamecchi!
You let him get away!
Thank you all for coming.
Kaori-sensei!
It's good to see you again.
Thank you for having us today.
No, thank you.
I-It's...
good to see you.
Kaname-kun, you've grown so much.
Yes, he's got quite the attitude now—
Hey, hey!
I'm everyone's friend, Tachibana Chizuru!
It's nice to meet you!
My, nice to meet you.
I can't believe how beautiful you are.
Do you have a boyfriend...
What, Kanamecchi?
I was just getting to know her!
And by that you mean you were hitting on her!
Okay, everyone!
These students from Homare High School will be your teachers today!
Play nice, children!
Okay!
I need to go see the head teacher.
Take care of them while I'm gone.
Oh, okay.
No problem. Piece of cake.
You have antennae!
He's a rhinoceros beetle!
I'll be your wife!
That's a little fast for me.
No fair!
I want to take things slow.
Hey, why are your faces the same?
Everything about us matches because we're friends.
You're such a cute girl!
What? W-Wait...
W-Why?
Hey! Give me back my glasses!
They're not a toy!
Run!
Let's go shopping today.
That sounds wonderful.
I want new clothes!
This dress would look good on you.
Super Lightning Blizzard!
Fight back with your own special attack!
O-Oh, right!
Strawberry Milk Cream Special!
It's not supposed to be a dessert.
Right.
Darling, we've been married for two years.
I want a child.
You want a child?
I think that would be a crime, age-wise.
Stop playing house as if it's real.
Should we have a boy or a girl?
How about this, Sono-chan?
This is our son.
What?
No, no, no! There's no way I'm playing house!
If you don't think you can,
you'll never be able to.
That's fine with me!
Now that the whole family's here, let's have dinner!
Eat up.
Om nom nom.
You're the best cook in the world.
Thank you, dear.
You too, Kaname.
You have to do it properly. Come on.
You're supposed to be taking this workplace experience seriously.
Om nom nom.
It's so good.
You bastard!
You laughed, didn't you?
Of course I didn't.
Some food got stuck in my throat.
We're not actually eating!
How dare you speak that way to your parents!
I'm so upset!
Stop being so dramatic! We're only playing house!
Beep, beep!
Out of the way, out of the way!
The second son's here! Beep, beep!
We don't need you bringing your nonsense into this game!
I refuse to play a character that isn't at least this badass!
I don't remember raising such an terrible son!
Pow.
Honey, stop!
He's not your son.
Shut up.
Honey, calm down!
Do you want to play, too?
Wh-Why would I play h-house with you?
Lame!
There you go again, Ken-chan!
Now, now.
It's not so bad.
What do you think you're doing?
Let go!
This guy will be your third son.
Say hi.
Third son?
Three might be... too many.
Huh? Why?
We don't have enough tableware.
Having a third might be problematic.
Then, I'll be the first son!
That's the spirit.
But the guy with the glasses is our first son.
I'm much better suited for the job than him!
You can be the dog, four-eyes!
Dog?
Go be a good guard dog!
You brat, I'll show you...
Stop!
Don't say such terrible things to my child!
Stop being so over dramatic!
What are you doing?
Ken-chan, you're awful!
This is stupid!
Playing house is so boring!
It's Kaname's fault for not being a guard dog.
Hey!
You're blaming me?
You And Me.
Bathroom, bathroom...
Ah, Shun-chan...
What's wrong?
I'm exhausted.
I won't make it.
I can't keep up with kids these days.
I know. Maybe they're already the new generation.
Hey, you've all gotten old fast.
We were naughty and precocious when we were little, too.
Yeah.
I guess so.
What? Was Kanamecchi in love with someone?
You were?
Oh, but kids these days are much naughtier... Right?
Yeah, they are!
Especially that brat, Ken-chan.
Ken-chan?
Between when we first got here and playing house...
I've had enough of his attitude!
He didn't seem like such a bad kid to me.
I'm sure he really is a good kid.
He just doesn't know how to show it.
Okay, okay.
Everything's a bed of roses to you.
Are you making fun of me?
There you all are.
Kaori-sensei.
It's almost snack time. Would you like to join us?
Kaori-sensei, I'm amazed you didn't think twice about coming into the men's room.
What if we were in the middle of something?
Huh?
Which means she doesn't see us as men. Not now and not back then.
Shut up!
You're not going to eat?
Huh? It's got nothing to do with you, four-eyes.
You brat!
You're always trying to start fights.
I don't like you.
I hope Kaori-sensei turns you down soon!
Th-That's not...
Don't get the wrong idea.
Sono-chan didn't hug you because she l-loves you.
You were just playing house.
Don't let it go to your head, octopus!
Oh, right. I see.
H-Hey.
Ken-chan?
You can have this.
What is that?
C-Cookies.
Whose?
Wh-Who cares whose they are?
Just eat them!
Ken-chan, I bet you stole them!
I didn't...
Sensei!
Ken-chan's stealing other people's cookies!
Again? Bad boy.
Bad boy, bad boy, bad boy...
Ken-chan, you're so mean!
Sensei, Ken-chan ate our cookies!
Hey, hold on...
Kaname-kun, are you all right?
You little twerp! You won't get away with this!
Kaname-kun!
Damn it. Where'd he...
What is this?
It'll grow new leaves in the spring.
It will?
Hey!
'on't follow ee!
I 'on't wanna be 'elled at by oo!
Hey.
'o away!
You put way too much in your mouth, stupid.
I'm sure he really is a good kid.
He just doesn't know how to show it.
That's disgusting!
Don't dribble all over someone's shoes!
Sheesh.
Let's go.
Where are we going?
Huh? You should know better than anyone else.
It's fine! It's fine!
It's not fine!
You have to do the right thing...
It doesn't matter!
I'm a bully!
She already hates me.
There's nothing...
Let's go.
Sono-chan, you're in the middle now.
Okay.
Kagome kagome, the bird in the cage...
Sorry.
When will you come out?
What?
In the evening of the dawn,
the crane and turtle slipped.
Who's the boy standing behind you?
Ken-chan?
It really is you!
H-H-How'd you know?
Because I smelled something sweet.
Sometimes, I smell sweets when you're near me.
It's so weird.
I don't know why, since you're so mean.
Sorry.
Sorry about the cookies... and your house game.
I'm sorry.
Kaori-sensei, thank you for letting us come today.
No, thank you. I had so much fun.
You're welcome to come back any time.
Okay.
Oh? What is it, Ken-chan?
Oh, right.
You're here to say goodbye—
I'm so sorry, Kaname-kun!
Are you okay?
Uh, fine.
Come now, Ken-chan!
See ya, four-eyes!
Don't give me that, you little twerp!
Those boys were fun, weren't they?
They're just annoying.
I wish we could play house with them again.
I'd be that cool guy's wife again.
Ken-chan.
What do you want the guy with the glasses to be?
Huh?
My brother.
I had so much fun at Hidamari Kindergarten.
You all went there, huh? Lucky.
There weren't any kids that precocious while we were there, though.
There were. Two of which I knew.
Let's go again sometime.
You guys go.
I won't go near that brat again.
You're still mad about that?
You two looked like you could be brothers.
What?
Cut it out. We're nothing alike.
That's not true.
He was just as passionate about the girl he liked...
as you were about Kaori-sensei.
Really? Kanamecchi, were you really?
Shun, I told you not to tell him.
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
Huh?
Oh!
That didn't count. I didn't mean to!
I can't believe it was him who spilled the beans.
Chizuru, you shouldn't laugh so much.
It was just youthful indiscretion.
This is great!
Don't treat someone's first love like a mistake!
It was as though we were standing in a beam of sunlight.
It changed cold winters and hot summers into a comfortable warmth.
I wonder how far and how long we'll travel together from that place.
The Sunshine Song
boku wa nakimushi de kuyashikute dakedo
It pains me to be such a crybaby,
anata ni ima tsutaetain da
but I want to tell you my feelings right now
tada massugu ni boku wo mitsumeru tsuyokute
There you stand, silently gazing at me
Allowing me to answer those strong and gentle eyes of yours
yasashii sono hitomi ni kotaeru tame ni
itsushika miushinatteta ichiban taisetsu na mono mo
You taught me what I lost sight of
sotto anata ga oshiete kureta
What was most important to me
tashika ni sou omoeru kara
I have no doubts about that
boku wa yowamushi de iya datta dakedo
I hated how weak I was
motto motto tsuyoku naru kara
but I will continue to become stronger
anata no koto wo mamoreru you na boku ni naru kara
I will be someone who could protect you
dakara sukoshi mattete
So wait a little longer for me