Hey.
Is it just me, or do we have an extra person in our group today?
It's just you.
That's impossible.
What's this midget doing here?
What does that have to do with you?
Masaki-chan came to ask me about something that she didn't understand in class.
Right?
I just need some stuff clarified.
I see.
Since I'm at the top of our grade, I'll tutor you.
I can explain it better than Shun.
Let me see.
Stop it!
I want Shun-chan to teach me!
You have it all wrong! Kaname, you jerk! Four-eyes!
Bookworm!
Why, you!
You're not the slightest bit cute.
Masaki-chan's face was red.
Does she have a cold?
Maybe she's lovesick.
Maybe she stayed up late studying math.
That's right.
She's desperately trying to solve an equation of love.
Do you think she went to the hospital?
You're the one who needs to go to the hospital.
A student is transferring to our class soon.
Apparently, he's returning from abroad.
Really?
There's been a lot of activity around us lately.
We met an awkward first-year,
and now, we're going to meet an unknown transfer student.
yappari kimi da yo ne
Oh hey, it's you
honto odoroita yo
You startled me
futari yoku aruita namikidoori
Here we are, on the tree-lined road we walked so often
otona ni naru no wo
I couldn't wait to grow up
matezu ni toozaketeitta no wa watashi datta ne
and I kept you at a distance, didn't I
itsumo
As always,
mainasu ichido no ame ga furu
the icy rain falls
kimi ga kureta namida
comprised of tears you cried for me
sono yasashisa made wakaranakute
That kindness I didn't understand
zutto kono mune wo shimetsuketa
lay heavy on my heart all the time
mainasu ichido no ame ga furu
The icy rain falls
tsumetasugiru namida
comprised of tears unbearably cold
hagurakasu taido ni okotteta keredo
Although I was angry at my evasive personality
jitsu wa sukuwareteitan da ne
you cured me of that, didn't you
I'd like to introduce the transfer student.
I'm Tachibana Chizuru.
He's blond!
Nice to meet you.
A blondie!
If you have any questions,
ask your class representative, Tsukahara-kun.
Tachibana-kun, your desk is over there.
Okay.
Nice to meet you.
I hope you'll share your textbook when I forget mine.
Nice to meet you, too.
Likewise.
I'm taking attendance.
Aoto.
Here.
Akaishi.
Akiyama.
Here.
What a shock!
You're that kid, aren't you?
Hey, Tachibana-kun...
No, um...
We played together at that park!
Didn't we?
That was such a long time ago.
Small world, huh?
Right?
Who are you?
What's wrong?
You stand here during every break.
Someone keeps making strange advances if I hang out over there.
It's really unusual for someone to approach you head-on.
It's not so much "head-on" as from the right.
Found you!
A clone?
We're twins.
I'm his older brother, Yuuta.
Oh, you're just his twin brother.
How do you two know each other?
In his delusional world,
we used to know each other.
That's not it!
We really do know each other!
There you are.
I thought I'd give you a tour of the school.
Are you free?
Who are you?
Tsukahara Kaname. I'm in your class.
Our teacher told you to come to me if you have any questions.
I'll ask Yukki, so don't sweat it.
Yukki?
He calls you Yukki?
We're old friends, so it's an affectionate nickname.
I'll affectionately call you, my classmate...
Four-eyes.
That name's clearly full of animosity!
Now, now...
You two must really be friends.
First thing you do is piss me off.
Birds of a feather flock together.
But Yuuki's acting like the transfer student has confused him with someone else.
A stranger's a stranger. See you later.
What's wrong with you?
He's so cold.
I feel like he used to be a lot nicer.
Nice?
That's definitely not him.
I'm sure he's just embarrassed to see his old friend again.
I have to make Yukki acknowledge me!
Hold up, Yu—
Who's that? His girlfriend?
That's not his girlfriend.
He's not even a girl.
How dare you say that?!
I know she's a little flat chested,
but it's our job as men to appreciate them anyway!
Hey, girlfriend!
Where did they go?
Huh? Hey, hey!
I told you that he isn't a girl.
Yuuta, words are meaningless unless the other person listens.
He's not a girl.
There you go again, saying the same thing as your brother.
That girl was so cute.
It's a shame I didn't get a chance to talk to her.
It's not like I was afraid of being shot down.
She seemed to be heading to the locker room.
Amazing. Did you see that?
Hey.
You really don't remember me?
Remember you?
I have no idea who you are.
Girls don't like overly persistent guys.
But you're a boy...
I was wondering who you were.
I didn't recognize you without your glasses.
With your hair like that, I thought you were Yuuta for a minute.
Oh, my bangs.
Wait!
Who are you?
I told you...
Hey, that kid you played with once...
You remember?
Could it have been Yuuta?
What?
You might have us confused. We do look the same.
You are identical, but...
I'm pretty sure it was Yukki.
You And Me.
Still not done?
Not yet.
You're just going to end up buying it.
I won't know if it's worth buying a copy
for archival purposes until I've read it.
You should stop doing that.
Books are made to be read.
You're not telling me that you know how this book feels, are you?
I do understand.
Now hurry up and buy it.
Now I'm kind of jealous.
I'll keep reading until I understand it, too.
That's not what I wanted.
That kid really is blond, isn't he?
From a distance, he looks like he's wearing a straw hat.
Could it have been Yuuta?
I have to find a way...
This one again?
This...
If you're going to buy it, just buy it already.
I can always buy manga volumes later,
but it's hard to find magazines long after they've been published.
Hold on!
Did you follow us?
Do you remember the toy I gave you?
What toy?
I gave you one!
I don't remember what it was, but I'm sure it was cool.
Who knows?
"Who knows?"
I did! I gave it to you!
Yeah, but...
Was this in front of the park?
My memory's pretty fuzzy, so I don't remember the details.
I think someone gave me something like that.
What? Then...
Oh, but I don't remember you.
What?
I see. So it was Yuuta.
I don't remember him at all, though.
What are you talking about?
At least he's stopped bothering you.
Right?
So small.
Who are you guys talking about?
That's all for today.
Students on day duty please bring the class register to the faculty office later.
Everyone I ask says they don't remember me.
Maybe I'm actually a fictional character.
What're you laughing at, huh?
Um...
You just smirked at us, didn't you?
No, I...
You're too cocky for a nobody.
What's with this hair?
You think this blond hair looks cool?
Don't get so excited over this crap!
You bastard!
What are you doing?
Yuutan and Yukki.
What do you want?
There sure are a lot of you against just one opponent.
No, no. That's not what this is.
I was just playing around.
Who do you think you are?
Say something!
I'm finished.
Where's the second volume?
Huh? Um, it's probably in my bag or my locker or...
What? How am I supposed to know from that?
Let me borrow this guy for a minute.
What are you talking about?
I'll return him later.
Let's go!
Wait!
He's busy with...
It's the Principal.
Let's go!
Hey, wait!
I'm bored.
It's summer, but Yuuta's sick.
What am I going to do by myself?
His head's yellow, like a straw hat.
Come on, play with me!
What language is that?
You want to play together?
Um, what's your name?
My mom told me not to talk to strangers.
He doesn't understand me.
Another nobody.
Do you want to try?
Put it in.
And turn it.
Oh, really cool!
Hero Yamato complete version!
No, I have to get it on my own.
More importantly, why am I here with some weird kid...
I don't mind playing without talking, though.
Wait!
Oh, no.
Sorry!
You've done it now, you jerk.
Now it's my turn.
Almost there.
Cool!
Um...
W-Wait here.
I-I'll go get an adult!
Sorry.
I guess he can't understand even if I apologize.
Yuuta-chan's finally better, and now you're sick.
Where's Yuuta?
He's out shopping.
It's a shame you can't play outside in this beautiful weather.
It's fine.
Hey!
Why are you ignoring me?
What does he want?
What you doing? I'll leave you behind!
Wait for me!
Thanks!
I'm home.
I bought some apple juice.
Thanks.
And I got you a gift.
Hero Yamato!
No fair, Yuuta. You used the toy machine?
No.
When I passed by the park,
this blond-haired kid came up to me and gave me this.
I couldn't understand anything he said, though.
I'm not interested in that stuff, so you can have it.
Yuuki?
I wanted to get it myself...
My words melted away in the sunlight of that childhood day without reaching him.
Only the blue summer sky saw what happened.
Yukki, you were the one whom I played with on that day.
You should just say it was Yuuta.
You and Yuutan aren't clones.
You read manga in the face of violence.
And I don't apologize for hurting others.
You don't?
I'm talking about what happened to you.
Oh, that.
I guess it did hurt, but I wouldn't have wanted you to apologize.
I really had fun.
I had fun and I was happy, so an apology is a little...
Right?
I wouldn't learn German just to apologize.
It'd be too much work.
Hey.
Is it just me, or do we have another extra member today?
Her name's Matsuoka-san?
Your girlfriend is cute, isn't she?
I heard she's good friends with all of you and usually comes up here, too!
Who's Matsuoka-san?
Furthermore, who are you?
I thought you'd be here.
It's Matsuoka-san.
Matsuoka-san...
You're late.
I had to fill in the class register.
Yes?
Nice to meet you, Matsuoka-kun.
Nice to meet you.
Hey!
Are you ok?!
Don't wake him, Shun.
Don't ever wake him. He never shuts up.
I tried to tell him you weren't a girl.
Words really are powerful things.
The Straw-Colored Boy
boku wa nakimushi de kuyashikute dakedo
It pains me to be such a crybaby,
anata ni ima tsutaetain da
but I want to tell you my feelings right now
tada massugu ni boku wo mitsumeru tsuyokute
There you stand, silently gazing at me
Allowing me to answer those strong and gentle eyes of yours
yasashii sono hitomi ni kotaeru tame ni
itsushika miushinatteta ichiban taisetsu na mono mo
You taught me what I lost sight of
sotto anata ga oshiete kureta
What was most important to me
tashika ni sou omoeru kara
I have no doubts about that
boku wa yowamushi de iya datta dakedo
I hated how weak I was
motto motto tsuyoku naru kara
but I will continue to become stronger
anata no koto wo mamoreru you na boku ni naru kara
I will be someone who could protect you
dakara sukoshi mattete
So wait a little longer for me
Next time,
Noisy Medicine