Now that the rainy season has started, it rains quite a lot.
I don't like the rainy season.
As the humidity rises, so does my misery.
I'm Tachibana Chizuru!
My best feature is the mole under my eye!
I'm Asaba Yuuta.
I have a younger twin brother.
You're identical!
I'm Matsuoka Shun.
Let's see... I'm in the tea club.
Shun-chan, you're so cute!
What?
I'm Satou Masaki.
I'm a first year.
Finally, a girl!
Don't tell me you're a boy, too?
Asaba Yuuki.
My favorite magazine is Animaga.
Yeah! It's cool!
Time for the final introduction.
The floor is yours!
Hey, Kanamecchi! Don't stop the flow.
You have to introduce yourself at a mixer.
And recently, more things that contribute to my misery have sprung up around me.
yappari kimi da yo ne
Oh hey, it's you
honto odoroita yo
You startled me
futari yoku aruita namikidoori
Here we are, on the tree-lined road we walked so often
otona ni naru no wo
I couldn't wait to grow up
matezu ni toozaketeitta no wa watashi datta ne
and I kept you at a distance, didn't I
itsumo
As always,
mainasu ichido no ame ga furu
the icy rain falls
kimi ga kureta namida
comprised of tears you cried for me
sono yasashisa made wakaranakute
That kindness I didn't understand
zutto kono mune wo shimetsuketa
lay heavy on my heart all the time
mainasu ichido no ame ga furu
The icy rain falls
tsumetasugiru namida
comprised of tears unbearably cold
hagurakasu taido ni okotteta keredo
Although I was angry at my evasive personality
jitsu wa sukuwareteitan da ne
you cured me of that, didn't you
Come on, hurry. Come on!
Why are we doing a mixer?
I'm only here because you insisted that I should come.
You're no fun.
I even had Yukki and Shun-chan pretend to be girls to even up the numbers.
I don't understand why you did that.
Now, now, now, forget about this shy boy.
Okay.
What kind of guy do you like?
How about it, Yukki?
Let's see...
I suppose someone who could prove to me...
that there are things more important than money.
I'll do it! I'll prove it to you!
I'll even embrace everything in your past!
I promise I'll do it!
What about you, Shun-san?
U-Um, someone kind, I guess.
You'll fall in l-love with someone as long as they're nice?
Hey, Kanamecchi, what's your type?
I dunno.
This guy's into older women.
Much older women.
No way! You like mature women?
No!
Yuuki-Mama, Kanamecchi's going to hurt me!
All men are like that.
They never show any kindness.
Yuuki-Mama!
What are you guys doing?
And why are we having this mixer?
Youth is all about having mixers!
What?
Young people must never forget about mixers!
But you've forgotten that this group isn't right for mixers.
Also, there's the weather.
The weather?
Huh?
Uh oh.
You monkey!
Damn that monkey.
Oh, Tsukahara-kun.
I'm done here. It's all yours.
I'm amazed you were at an outdoor party in this weather.
There was nothing amazing about it.
Aside from Tachibana-kun,
you're all childhood friends, aren't you?
Yes, since kindergarten.
I see.
I'm sure you've all changed a lot since then.
We haven't changed one bit.
Shun's always been a flowery guy,
and Yuuta and Yuuki were even more problematic as little kids.
They really were a couple of precocious preschoolers.
You're right.
Children are always more precocious than adults think.
While I was working in high school, I visited a kindergarten, and the children there were a handful.
Now that you mention it, I guess I was pretty mature for my age, too.
Kaori-sensei!
Yes, yes.
Kaname-kun, what's wrong?
I've figured it out.
No matter how much it snows,
the flowers of love will always bloom.
Kaname-kun, you reek of cheesiness.
That's not what that means!
The students from Homare High School are here to help us work.
They'll be your teachers for the day.
This is Kouichi-sensei and Akira-sensei.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you!
Um, what should we do?
You can start by reading them picture books.
Who does he think he is...
talking to my Kaori-sensei like that?
Love is fleeting.
It's not over yet!
I'll never lose to a guy like that!
This brings back memories.
When I was your age, I cried when I read this.
I felt so bad for Snow White.
Did you really?
Yeah. I was a crybaby.
How lame.
How can you protect the princess when you're crying?
I'd fight the witch before anything happened to her!
I'm sorry.
He believes he can solve any problem with money.
No, with strength!
Onii-chan, look, look!
Look at mine first!
Oh, um...
Yours is terrible.
No, yours is.
Don't fight...
Your rival's popular.
He thinks he's so great because he's sorta tall and handsome.
I'm way better.
Yeah.
Compared to your good looks,
his good looks don't seem inferior at all.
That means I'm worse than him!
It's okay, Kaname-kun.
There are always obstacles in love.
They say your first love never works out.
You're not helping!
Hooray! A snowball fight!
Now you've done it!
Get back here!
Are you okay by yourself?
Does he...
He hates you!
He does.
It's okay.
I love Kaori-sensei.
Kaname-kun, that's huge.
Why don't we combine yours with mine and make a snowman?
I'll stack them.
Kaori-se—
Are you all right?
S-Sorry.
Don't worry about it.
There you go.
Your snowman's complete.
Are you okay?
I don't need your pity.
Jerk!
Um, did I do something?
Don't get the wrong idea.
I could've helped Kaori-sensei, too.
What? What is this?
I look like such an idiot.
You're a cool little guy.
Snow White
I could only cry, but you're different.
You can fight for her and defend her.
You're a cool little guy.
Damn it.
I hope...
Someday, I hope...
I can be just like him.
How embarrassing.
I know I was just a kid, but...
Damn it. My face is burning.
Huh?
Is something wrong?
No, it's nothing.
If you'll excuse me...
I wonder how those kids are doing.
You And Me.
Damn.
It's that stupid monkey's fault...
He made us have that stupid mixer.
It's really pouring.
He's a surprisingly deep sleeper.
He's defenseless.
You shouldn't do that.
Now, now.
Oh. Kaname, you're looking well.
What are you doing here?
We came to visit.
Visit?
I can't believe you caught a cold as soon as the season changed.
Kanamecchi, you're like an old man.
Whose fault is it I caught this cold?
Ow. You're mean!
And we came all the way here to visit you, old man!
Who are you calling an "old man"?
Kaname-kun, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Mail received
Asaba Yuuki
Yuuki!
Why are you taking pictures of me?
Delete that!
Come on! Give me your phone!
Give you my phone?
You think I'd give you my phone when it has all sorts of personal information on it?
What?
Personal information about the top student in our grade... doesn't come cheap.
That's nothing like him!
It's nothing like him,
but I like your Kanamecchi impression!
What's good about it?
Don't you laugh under your breath at me!
Sorry.
Enough.
I'll force you to...
No, you have to rest.
Let go, Shun!
I can't rest peacefully as long as they're here!
Hey, do these look good on me?
Yeah, but if you wear them too long, you'll damage your eyes.
Your house sure is nice, Kanamecchi.
Thank you for going out of your way to come visit Kaname-kun.
Oh, thank you.
I haven't seen you before.
Nice to meet you. I'm Kaname-kun's mother.
I'm Tachibana Chizuru.
You're quite young... And beautiful!
Why, thank you.
Kaname-kun, he just made a pass at me.
Are you jealous?
Not really.
Hey, you shouldn't make a woman cry!
Why is she crying, anyway?
Huh? There's one extra juice.
Oh, that's mine.
You're gonna drink in here, too?
Because I want to talk to you, Kaname-kun.
You can talk to me any time.
Liar.
You're always so stoic.
You've even stopped holding my hand recently.
I haven't held your hand in years.
I wouldn't call that recent.
Do I annoy you?
Do I really annoy you so much?
What's with "annoying me"?
That's not it. As time goes on, it just—
But you said... But you said that you loved me!
Can't we go back to the way we used to be?
Is it too late?
Hey!
Has the love disappeared?
That's not something you should say to your son!
You have to remember the day...
that you told her she'd be your first and last.
That never happened!
We're family!
I need to go to the supermarket!
Oh, Hisa-chan!
Oh, hello.
Hello.
Your mom's pretty cute, Kanamecchi.
I try to avoid introducing her to my friends.
Kaname-kun, you should lie down.
I'm fine.
Oh, right. Will you be able to do make-up work for the classes you missed today?
I had Yuuki-kun and Chizuru-kun take notes for—
I'll be fine.
I'm sure they didn't take notes anyway.
Then, I'll...
I said I'll be fine.
I see. You're right.
I just have to memorize the stuff...
that we're doing right now, so it'll be fine.
Kaname.
I heard you caught a cold.
Ah, Hisako-chan.
Shun-kun, it's good to see you again!
You grew your hair out again.
A girl barged into Kanamecchi's room!
Who is she? Is she your girlfriend?
How naughty!
Stop saying nasty stuff.
She's just a childhood friend.
Who'd date this brute?
Nice to meet you. I'm Aida Hisako.
Same here. I'm Tachibana Chizuru.
Ow! You shouldn't punch sick people!
Then you should shut up and rest like a sick person.
What's this?
I found a photo in your desk drawer.
Hey, don't touch my desk!
Let me see, let me see!
What do we have here?
Hey!
Isn't this from that time your family and mine...
had that... I think it was a barbecue...
Is it really?
Math II
That's all?
I was hoping for something more unexpected.
Math II
English II
You don't have anything but study materials on your desk.
Your disappointment is making me angry.
Who's this?
That's my sister. Her name's Shizuna.
Enough already!
I still can't believe you'd treasure a photo like that.
That's not it.
I stuck it in there because I didn't have anywhere else to keep it.
Really?
Shut up. Go away!
If you try anything weird, I'll throw you out.
I could've done it myself.
Shun-kun, you're a guest.
So are you, Hisako-chan.
I've spent lots of time here since I was little.
And now, after all these years...
Oh, his medicine.
Did Kaname-kun take any this afternoon?
Should we take it to him?
You worry too much!
Kaname-kun...
He's never relied on others.
Tsukahara Kaname
3 days, 3 times a day
Dosage: 1 capsule
Instructions: Please take within 30 minutes of every meal.
Coldcurin 250
He's always helping me with things,
but I never get to help him.
Oh, right.
Yeah.
Well, that's fine, isn't it?
Huh?
You think so?
I'm sure he doesn't mind.
Chizuru's Ultra Dive!
A perfect score! He's done it!
He's set a new world record!
You scored a zero!
That hurts. Get off, you monkey!
What's all that noise?
Chizuru-kun, don't do that.
Kaname-kun is sick...
Huh? What?
Hey. If you don't stop, you'll...
So heavy... You're all so heavy.
I hit my chin.
Shun's jump was too low.
It wasn't my fault.
You did this to yourselves!
Sorry about today.
We came to visit you,
but all we did was make things worse.
You really did.
Take it easy tomorrow.
You're taking tomorrow off, too?
How does that negatively affect you?
Actually, it'll be great going to school without you yelling at me.
Huh?
But it'll get boring without you, so get well soon.
Take care, Kaname-kun.
Bye bye.
You heard them.
Don't give me that.
They shouldn't have made such a racket when they visited.
But I think you're looking a little better.
Your fever's down.
All that racket made you sweat it off.
Shut up.
The rainy days continue.
I hate the rainy season.
I don't hate the rain, though.
The rain pounds noisily on my window,
but there's something comforting about the sound.
Hisako.
There are notebooks on my desk. Can you bring them to me?
What?
If I'm going to lie here, I might as well look over my notes from class.
Actually,
those boys just left with all of your notebooks.
What?
Classics
His notes are perfect!
They really are.
Classics
What did they come here for, exactly?!
boku wa nakimushi de kuyashikute dakedo
It pains me to be such a crybaby,
anata ni ima tsutaetain da
but I want to tell you my feelings right now
tada massugu ni boku wo mitsumeru tsuyokute
There you stand, silently gazing at me
Allowing me to answer those strong and gentle eyes of yours
yasashii sono hitomi ni kotaeru tame ni
itsushika miushinatteta ichiban taisetsu na mono mo
You taught me what I lost sight of
sotto anata ga oshiete kureta
What was most important to me
tashika ni sou omoeru kara
I have no doubts about that
boku wa yowamushi de iya datta dakedo
I hated how weak I was
motto motto tsuyoku naru kara
but I will continue to become stronger
anata no koto wo mamoreru you na boku ni naru kara
I will be someone who could protect you
dakara sukoshi mattete
So wait a little longer for me
Next time: One Summer
One Summer