Tee hee hee hee!
Do you really hate the Faunus that much?
What a thing to say. The Faunus
are the ones who hate humanity.
Not all Faunus are like that!
How many times do I have to say it?
Blake, calm down!
I'll distract her...
I'll lure Negative Weiss away.
Huh?
You and Yang go search for the Nightmare.
Uh, yeah. Okay.
What are you whispering about?
Step away from Ruby.
I won't allow you to deceive
my precious imperial subjects.
Precious?
The ones you locked in a tower?
Tee hee hee!
Look, she ran away, Sister!
Silence.
Klein, Sister...
Achoo!
Follow Ruby. I will take care of Blake.
Aye-aye, sir!
It feels so weird to get
sleepy inside a dream.
Yang, come on!
You're back! Where's Blake?
She's distracting them.
The other Weiss is chasing her.
And while she's doing that, we go
find the Grimm possessing Weiss, right?
How did you already know? Wow!
Well, it just makes sense.
I kinda don't feel like
I'm pulling off this leader thing.
That isn't true at all.
But we don't have time for that anyway.
Okay? Let's go, let's go!
But...
Hmm?
I can hear Miss Ruby and Miss Yang's voices.
What a relief, what a relief.
Oh. It really does seem
like the inside of her heart.
So, where should we go?
I wonder if we can use this.
Oh!
Right on! Nice job, Ruby!
You're the best! What a leader!
Tee hee.
Ladies!
As long as my eyes glow red, I,
Grumpy Klein, will not let you pass!
I have never known another
person as outrageous as yourself!
I drive you out again and again, but you
keep sneaking into my sacred places.
Do you realize how much you've
disturbed the sacred order?
What an absolute nuisance.
Are you that desperate to chase me away?
Or do you just hate being around Faunus?
Faunus are not allowed to enter.
That is the law here!
She doesn't run out of Dust?
I guess anything goes here.
I won't even wait for my sister
to pass judgment.
This time, I will finally
expel you for eternity.
Grimm? She can do that, too?
Are you that desperate to chase me away?
Are you that desperate to chase me—
Or do you just hate all Faunus?
And you always just run away!
There's trouble, Sister!
Don't bother me! Get back.
Even though I came all the way here to
tell you that Ruby and Yang escaped?
What did you say? Yang, too?
Blake sure took you for a ride!
Don't forget your
responsibilities, dear sister.
I won't let you pass!
Oh, oops! It's this way!
I am truly sorry, Mistress Weiss.
Croak...
We're doing this for Weiss's sake!
Ew, it's pitch black.
This thorny briar patch
is a Grimm, isn't it?
Please, take us to where Weiss is.
It worked!
Another success!
Hee-hee!
Huh? She's got Grimm, too?
What, are you serious?
Oh, yeah. We'll open a door.
Blake, so you fought that other Weiss?
Are you hurt or anything?
We were basically just playing tag.
But I'm fine. Thanks.
Hey, how many coins do you have left?
One left.
After all that, I'm also down to one.
I have two.
Wanna pick who'll save the last one?
I'll leave it to our leader.
Um, okay, I'll save mine.
I'll use it to get us out of here.
Good, it's decided then.
If the Grimm is in there,
I'll call the Professor.
Yeah, please do.
The professor told us never to
touch the Nightmare's thorns.
That would've been
impossible without the relic.
Ruby had it covered.
Eheheh.
Oh!
That's the Nightmare.
Yang.
I'm on it!
Ah, hello? This is Yang. Wha—
Sis?!
What the?!
How dare you enter these sacred halls.
Wait, is she protecting the Grimm?
Do you really not understand why we're here?
Stop talking nonsense.
Get out right now!
The relic!
Why betray me, Ruby?
Huh?
I must protect what is precious to me.
Why can't you understand?
Sorry, Weiss.
I think I misunderstood.
I don't really know...
what's precious to you.
But there's no way it
would be a Grimm, right?
I'm begging you, open your eyes!
You've disappointed me, Yang.
Huh?
You're the one who made her like this.
Spoiling her, coddling her...
Your selfish behavior robbed
Ruby of the chance to grow up.
You know, I'm starting to get,
like, really ticked off!
You don't know what you're talking about.
Yang, no. Calm down.
Enough of this.
I'll lock the three of you away forever!
Calm down. Calm down. Calm down. Calm down.
Like, really ticked off!
Ruby!
Ow!
Oh!
Why you...!
Yang!
Wake up now! Immediately!
Phew. Did you all wake up?
I can sense that all of the markers
in the dream have been destroyed.
We have no choice but to enter
the dream a third time and replace them.
Starting again from scratch.
The landscape and the rules of Weiss's
dream should not change significantly.
Utilize what you have learned thus far
and devise a new strategy.
A strategy...
It will take some time
for my Aura to recover.
Until then, the three of you
should think about your plan.
If you do not succeed in the
next attempt, however,
Weiss's life will be in danger.
I bet Weiss is hungry, too.
Jeez! What a selfish,
stubborn little princess.
Who does she think we're doing this for?
The Nightmare is just trying
to make us think she's like that.
Let's think about our plan.
Yang?
Where are you going, Sis?
To get some fresh air.
I can't fight when my mind's stuck on this,
so I won't be able to
think of a strategy, either.
That's true. I'll do the same.
How about we meet back here in an hour?
Yeah. Okay.
"Precious," she said...
Is that how she thinks about me?
I want to understand her,
but it's so hard.
I'm sorry, Weiss.
Hmm?
What are you doin' all by yourself?
Shouldn't you be with your friends?
You're just too soft on Ruby.
My older sister was so strict...
Just shut up. I already knew that.
What did you already know?
Woah! Where'd you come from?
Hello, my friend Ruby's older sister.
I am Penny.
Y-Yeah... Hello.
Were you talking to yourself just now?
Or were you perhaps speaking with
a being that is beyond my perception?
Talking to myself.
Or, more like talking to someone
from a dream. She's a little stubborn.
Then you may require maintenance.
Main...?
There were versions of us
inside her dream, too?
Huh. What were we like?
Uh, um, well...
Just like me, all of you are
locked up somewhere in there.
Why, though? Did we ever
do anything bad to Weiss?
We might not be locked up
because we're bad, you know.
Huh?
He's right.
When something is really important to you,
don't you want to hide it
away and keep it safe?
Because you're scared
of losing it or something?
Right. Maybe she's trying to protect her
memories of her friends from the Nightmare.
Aw, well at least let me out.
Then we could fight together.
That really isn't the point.
Fight together...
I wish I could, too.
I can recover really quickly.
Really?
I have learned that dreams are maintenance,
used to process excess information.
So I, too, make efforts to dream.
To this end, I have conceived and
programmed many different scenarios.
I... don't really understand.
It is possible to perform
various kinds of maintenance
by swapping out different dreams.
Why don't you try that too,
Ruby's older sister?
It's Yang.
That's not how it works...
Oh? Maintenance, yeah...
Huh. In the dream,
your friend keeps you away?
Yeah.
The same way that human society
keeps the Faunus at a distance.
But doesn't that just show how
much she's thinking about you?
Thinking about me?
In the dream, if she pushes you away
but you keep coming back,
that's gotta be it.
I mean, I get the feeling
it means your being there
is powerful enough to change her.
Change... Weiss?
Can I?
If she's accepted you,
that's awesome in itself, isn't it?
Doesn't it mean you were
able to change her mind?
The White Fang's founding ideals
were like that too, at first.
Huh?
We wanted to change the world.
We wanted them to accept us.
But then after being rejected,
after losing hope,
violence was the only thing left for some.
But I refuse to lose hope.
No matter how many times I'm rejected,
I'll keep trying to make them accept us.
Thanks, Sun.
Believing that you can both
change each other for the better...
Isn't that what friends are for?
Don't give up.
...and then maybe Negative Weiss will
forget about protecting the Grimm.
Once Negative Weiss is gone,
we'll totally be able to beat the Grimm.
Certainly.
When we did it, more than
the Nightmare itself,
it felt like parts of Jaune's
dream were attacking us.
That Grimm isn't that strong.
Well, at least it wasn't when we fought it.
What's this? You're ironing
out a plan with Team JNPR?
Yeah. Welcome back, Sis.
Guess what! I came up with a strategy!
Heh.
And. So. Did. I!
Wanna hear it?
Yeah! Tell me! Tell me!
Once Blake gets here... Oh!
Sorry I'm late.
I just got here, too.
Did you think of something?
More like, I know what I need to do now.
Then let's call a team meeting!
Well? What do you think of our plan?
First, regarding Yang's idea,
yes, it is possible to change
what happens in a dream.
Mm-hmm!
But only if the dreamer
sees it as a positive change.
If Weiss considers it to be a negative change,
you will encounter resistance.
I feel like I understand
how Weiss wants to change.
I was the same way.
I knew I had to change,
but I couldn't find a way to.
I want to tell Weiss, deep in
her heart, that it's okay to change.
I'm sure that Weiss will also think
that what we're about to do
is something good. I believe that.
I didn't understand,
but we're not the only ones
who are struggling.
Even Weiss is fighting
against the Grimm in her heart.
Very well. One last thing.
Regarding Ruby's idea,
it actually does have precedent,
and it has generally
produced positive results.
Is that right?
So prior experience with
Nightmare possession can be useful?
Yes.
Jaune's heart still retains the memory
of hosting the parasitic Nightmare.
Other Nightmares will mistake Jaune
for someone who is still possessed,
and will likely ignore him.
Oh, no kidding?
You mean he's not worth noticing?
No, Nora.
He has developed immunity, so to speak.
But the closer Jaune gets
to the Nightmare's body,
the more of a reaction he'll have.
Eh... What kind?
The most common ones are itching
and difficulty breathing.
That's just like an allergy.
I'm getting a bad feeling about this.
In return, you should be
able to move quite freely
in a dream controlled by a Nightmare.
Seriously? That's great!
We can totally use your help, Jaune!
But if the rejection is too strong,
there is a risk he may die
from shock inside the dream.
Be careful.
Ew. Dying in your sleep?
Please stay alive, Jaune.
Ugh... but this is for her sake.
I hope I can pull it off.
I know you can do it, Jaune.
Believe in yourself and your Aura.
I'll try.
You have to search for the key to her heart.
Somewhere in the dream,
there should be an item
identical to the one you found before.
All right, Professor.
I do not mean to frighten you,
but if you fail again,
in the time that it takes
for my Aura to recover,
it is quite likely that Weiss
will lose her life.
Do you understand?
We won't fail again.
We gotta hurry and wake Weiss up,
so we can tell her how
tough this was, right guys?
Yeah. Right now, I just want to talk
to her. About all sorts of things.
All right, prepare to enter the dream.
I now invite you all into the dream.