Weiss...
Oh, I fell asleep!
Shh.
Cream and five sugars.
Just how you like it, right?
Here. Coffee.
Thanks, Weiss.
You've caused so much trouble.
I thought I could trust you
to help me protect what's precious.
I thought I was doing the right thing.
I'm sorry, Weiss.
I just felt bad for them
being locked up like that.
I understand exactly how you feel.
That's why you can get away
with things that I can't.
Huh?
You can move through the castle
walls and the city freely.
Actually, I understand how Yang feels, too.
When I see you, it makes me
want to set them free, too.
Not exactly to spoil them, though.
Didn't you hate me
because I was so embarrassing?
Well, I do find your simplistic
and reckless nature questionable.
But I know I can count on you.
Oh? Really?
Sure.
Also, I've never met anyone
else lonelier than myself.
You're lonely, Weiss?
But I... oh.
Oh, yeah. You are, too.
In order to not to lose those precious
to you, lock them away carefully,
and put them to sleep.
Oh! Speaking of precious things,
my Crescent Rose.
The barrel is actually on the other side.
You got that wrong, Weiss.
No, Ruby. Everything has its reason.
Reason?
After all, it hides in the shadow
of the person you're facing.
Weiss, where are you going?
I, too, must go to sleep.
Aren't we sleeping here together?
I guess you don't like
the bunk bed after all.
I always, always wanted one.
But this is your dream.
I have to return to my own place of sleeping.
Don't you see?
Yeah, I guess so.
Good night, Ruby.
Good night, Weiss.
Hey! Ruby!
Hey! What happened?
Ruby! Are you okay?
Seriously? Ruby!
Is the situation serious?
Ruby has been trapped
by a dream inside the dream.
The Nightmare must have
snuck inside her heart.
My Semblance is being obstructed
and can't help her escape.
Jaune...
What? What?
What happened?
His Aura is getting stronger.
Go for it, Jaune! One, two! One, two!
A little more...!
Weiss!
Ow. Ow.
Is this the train?
Are you awake? Thank goodness.
My last coin...
It is not clear how, but she
appears to be out of danger.
My Semblance has not been
completely exhausted yet, either.
By the way, what kind of power
does his Semblance have?
Well, we don't know yet.
He has only just learned
how to activate his Aura.
Seriously! I was so surprised that he
was fighting without his Semblance.
Sometimes battle helps to awaken powers...
powers hidden deep inside oneself.
Has Ruby fallen asleep?
Have Yang, Blake, and the
others also fallen asleep?
Mirror...
Tell me something,
Tell me who's the loneliest of all.
Mirror, what's inside of me?
Tell me, can a heart be turned to stone?
Mirror, mirror, what's behind you?
Save me from the things I see.
I can keep it from the world.
Why won't you let me hide from me?
Mirror, mirror...
Tell me something.
Who's the loneliest of all?
I'm the loneliest of all.
Aw, don't look around so much.
It's really embarrassing.
I can't reach Ruby or Jaune.
It's like our shed back home,
except 100 times creepier.
Covered in junk that never gets cleaned up.
Oh... I mean, I wasn't talking about you.
I'm talking about this place.
I feel the same way.
I wonder if it is a gathering spot
for things that have no other place to go.
The White Fang.
Yang.
A relic! This must be
the relic meant for you!
I knew we'd find one!
Wow!
Wh-What?
What? What? What just appeared?
I can't tell if they're Grimm
or the White Fang.
Why are they so tame?
Probably because I'm here.
Maybe to Weiss, they and I are alike.
Hey, you don't know that.
Remember, the Grimm made this dream.
I think I understand why.
Huh?
I used to believe that the Schnee Dust
Company and people persecuting Faunus
were all dangerous and terrifying.
The same way she thinks.
Deep in my heart,
I knew they weren't all that way.
But I convinced myself that their
hostility gave me a reason to fight them.
Hmm... Well, even if you did,
you aren't like that anymore.
Anyway, let's take this and hurry back.
And then get rid of the Grimm.
I'll use my coin, so—
If we do that, we'll just be
stopped by Negative Weiss again.
Inside the dream,
we're no match for her powers.
We don't know that.
I'm sure Ruby is doing her best right now.
We should hurry—
I'm sure she understands
that if we don't think of a better plan,
we have no chance of winning.
We've done enough thinking already.
What else can we do?
Get a Grimm allergy like Jaune,
so we can sneak in like cowards?
That's not how I do things!
I'm telling you, brute force won't work.
Oh... But there might be another way.
Huh?
So there's a reason for this, too?
The door we need isn't opening.
We can only get into buildings close by.
There aren't any robot soldiers.
If we go now, we can probably
make it to that building.
Are we really going there?
We really should look for
Yang and Blake instead.
We've already used up
all of our coins, anyway.
Weiss will fall asleep
while we're doing that!
She'll never wake up again.
Weiss—the real Weiss—said so.
But what if the statue on
the building starts moving again?
We don't know where more soldiers
or thorns will appear.
We can't beat Negative Weiss.
We can't start acting recklessly.
Then I'll think of a plan
that isn't reckless.
This train... nothing blocked it
from coming here, right?
Y-Yeah...
I wonder if we can ride the train
all the way to that building.
Are you serious?
There aren't any tracks.
There weren't tracks before, either.
It should move as long as I'm here.
You? What do you mean?
Weiss said that to me.
That I can move around freely.
Weiss didn't hate me, either.
So I'm sure she'll let us through.
She'll understand.
But that was Weiss, not Negative Weiss.
Negative Weiss is the one
that'll come after us.
If she does, that means Weiss
hasn't fallen asleep yet.
We could buy some time while we wait
for Yang and the others to return.
Are we bringing these girls along, too?
I want to help Weiss become more free.
It might sound selfish, but I think
it's the right thing to do,
so I think these girls should fight, too.
Hey, now, did you forget what I told you?
The girls will turn into monsters
and go on a rampage again.
But that happened because of the Grimm.
The Pyrrha who stayed with you
didn't turn into a monster, did she?
Oh...
And all I told them was
to fight for freedom.
That's probably why they went on a rampage.
Then what will you make them do next?
I'll ask them to fight for Weiss.
I want to get Weiss out of here.
I want Weiss to realize she wants to leave.
What is happening?
What? What?
Phew...
Of course a Company train
would be packed full of Dust.
We've got all the ammo we need!
Please! Let us through, Weiss!
Keep going!
Weiss...
Let us pass, Weiss.
If you trust me, let us pass!
Don't be foolish.
Even at this stage, you still don't
understand what is and isn't allowed.
I will pass judgment on you
and put you to sleep.
Shoot! Keep shooting!
It's no good. At this rate, we're done for.
Move, damn it! Move!
This is bad!
There!
Be a good girl and go to sleep, Ruby.
I have to save Weiss!
This is the end for you.
What is that?
What's happening?
Yang!
Hello!
The White Fang! But why?
Daughter of the Schnee family!
Humans or Faunus—
I'll show you which is superior and just!
"Mirror of Darkness."