Legends...
Stories scattered through time.
Man, born from dust, was strong,
wise, and resourceful.
But an inevitable darkness—creatures of
destruction, the creatures of Grimm—
set their sights on man
and all of his creations.
When all seemed lost,
and it seemed man's brief
existence might return to dust,
the smallest spark of hope
brought forth a great light.
Once born of dust, man used
his passion and ingenuity
to discover a new power,
appropriately called Dust.
Man thus lit their way through
the darkness and restored civilization.
Hey, listen Mom!
Yang graduated from Signal Academy
and got accepted to Beacon Academy!
Isn't that great?
Sis always said she wanted to be a Huntress,
and it's really happening!
Which is a little frustrating, too.
Of course I'm happy for her,
but I want to be a Huntress too,
and my grades at Signal aren't good.
What can I do to be more like her?
Anyway, when it comes to handling weapons,
I know I'm as good as anyone else.
I just gotta work harder!
Someday, I'll fight to protect people
from the Grimm just like you did, Mom!
Oh? Yang!
What were you talking to Mom about?
About your acceptance. I'm so happy!
Is that right? Thanks!
The arrangements have
been made, Mistress Weiss.
Shall we go, Klein?
Yes.
You're drinking
in the daytime again, Mother?
Are you ready, Weiss?
Whitley. Do you think you're the one testing me?
I'm worried about you.
A test this dangerous isn't normal.
I'm sure you would agree, Sister.
No. This is hardly enough to intimidate me.
Shut up and watch.
I've always watched you,
my fearless, foolish sisters.
I am very pleased to see you,
Father. Elder Sister.
This is the final test, right?
This is utterly pointless.
Wasn't this your choice, Father?
Weiss is prepared to do it.
Well, then, please unleash the Grimm.
Fine. But the instant I decide
you can't do this, you fail.
And that will be the end
of your selfish behavior.
Understood.
Aww...
Now you understand, correct?
We're finished here.
No. It isn't over.
Adam, are we really doing this alone?
The only guards will be Atlas toys.
The humans fear the White Fang
too much to face us.
But you... are you scared?
Do you think I'm the type to scare easily?
I'm very aware of your bravery.
That's the Company's train.
The entire cargo of Dust is ours.
Well, this is going to get messy.
Try not to have too much fun.
Your Aura can only take a direct attack
once or twice at most.
The moment you're hit, you're finished.
The powerless return to dust.
That is the law of this world.
Mistress Weiss, you did it!
You will accept my enrollment
in Beacon Academy now, won't you?
Father...
Have it your way!
Perfect. We'll run the train
into the ravine.
It isn't on autopilot.
There are human workers riding, too.
Just humans. They aren't Faunus like us.
Right...
Blake?
Farewell, Adam.
Blake!
Are you betraying me... betraying the White Fang?
I have to find my own path.
Should we follow Blake?
Leave her be.
Once she learns more about the world,
she'll know we're in the right.
I forgot the city was so big!
It's so much more fun than Patch Island.
I can listen to music at scroll shops,
visit cafés and weapon stores,
and the time just flies by!
Oh, what should I do about Yang's present?
The Dust shop is still open!
The latest issue of Weapon Magazine! Awesome!
You can't get it on
Patch Island until next week.
The city of Vale is so advanced!
"We are delighted to accept you
into Beacon Academy."
Dad, did Ruby come home?
No, not yet.
She said she'd be back in a minute.
I wonder what happened.
She's secretly buying a present
to celebrate your acceptance, Yang.
Oh, why did you tell me?
I was trying so hard to play dumb.
Sorry, sorry.
We won't have as many chances
to go out as a family now.
I wonder if Ruby will do okay with me gone.
When she gets excited,
she loses sight of everything around her.
It's about time Ruby became independent.
It's great that you support each other,
but it's not good for Ruby
if she's always depending on you.
Fine, fine, I know.
She certainly is late, though.
Welc—
Do you have any idea how hard it is
to find a dust shop open this late?
You can take my money.
We're not here for your money.
Help yourselves.
"The first stage of a weapon's transformation
should combine both offensive
and defensive capabilities."
Yeah, totally!
Huh?
Hey kid, put your hands in the air.
Yes?
What is it?
Put your hands up!
Are you robbing me?
Yeah!
You punk!
A Semblance?
A Beacon Academy student?
You were worth every cent. Truly, you were.
Well, Red, I think we can all say it's been an eventful evening.
And as much as I'd love to stick around,
I'm afraid this is where we part ways.
You won't get away!
You thief!
Persistent...
She's nearby.
Ruby, you're all over the place!
What's going on?
Ruby, what did you do?
We got a Huntress. Let's beat it!
Wow! You're a Huntress?
Miss, did you not stop to think about
how your actions put others in great danger?
Is your Aura strong enough
to stop every bullet they fired?
But they...
Oh, Professor Ozpin!
Just stopping by for a quick visit.
Good evening, Tai.
Professor! I...
Don't worry.
I just want to speak
with your daughter a bit.
Hey, was that...
Yeah.
The head of Beacon Academy.
There's someone here
who would like to meet you.
Ruby Rose.
You have silver eyes.
Um, you are...?
Do you know who I am?
Yes, probably.
Professor Ozpin.
You're the headmaster at Beacon Academy.
Nice to meet you. Now, a question.
Do you want to attend my school?
Huh?
Unbelievable! Really?
Yeah. He said he'd let me
skip two grades to get in.
Amazing! Now we can enroll together!
She's gifted. She reminds me
of your Team STRQ.
Ruby is still a child.
Children eventually leave the nest.
I never dreamed they'd both leave together.
"Notice of acceptance..."
Now I can take a different path.
Your remaining luggage
has been sent to Beacon.
Thanks. I'd better go.
Why don't you wait a little longer?
Winter was too busy to come.
Father and Whitley couldn't
be bothered to see me off.
Isn't that right?
But I'm happy that you came, Klein.
Please be well.
You too, Mistress.
Please take care of yourself.
I am certain you will become a fine Huntress
and will carry on the legacy
of Master Nicholas,
as a descendant of the great Schnee family.
I believe in you.
I'm going, Mom.
Phew! I made it.
Phew... I made it in time.
Thanks, Dad!
For you and Mom and Uncle
and my teachers...
And... I'll be as good as the best Huntsmen!
I'll become a super awesome Huntress,
and I'll make tons of friends, too!
That's the spirit.
But you don't need to
overdo it trying to be the best.
You two should just stay
the way you are. Got it?
All right, Dad! We should get going.
Write to me, okay?
Yeah!
See you later!
Through battle, man won life.
But even the most brilliant lights
eventually flicker and die.
And then...
darkness will return.
So stay vigilant, guardians
of the light, but take heed.
There will be no victory in strength.
But perhaps victory is in the simpler things.
Things that are long forgotten...
Things that require a smaller, more honest soul.