I-I can't believe this!
How can you not know what your boyfriend's post graduation plans are?!
Well... We never talk about stuff like that.
What?!
You're already a senior, but you haven't discussed it?
What do you normally talk about, then?
Stuff like the upcoming Umibouzu concert...
Or guessing what order he'll perform his songs in...
I figured it would be something like that, but...
You've got to be kidding!
Aren't your boyfriend's post graduation plans a source for concern when making your own?
Do you two talk about this stuff with Nakao-chi and Suzuki-kun?
Of course.
Nakao-chi is going into the family business, running a dessert shop,
so I'm planning to become a nutritionist to help him out.
Like Kazuyoshi Yamaguchi's wife, huh? How admirable!
Kazutoyo Yamauchi is a Japanese historical figure from the Warring States period. His wife was known to be highly loyal to him.
You idiot! That's Kazutoyo Yamauchi's wife!
Ah. You're right.
What about you, Chiharu-chan?
I've decided to go to the same university as Suzuki-kun for the time being.
I-Is that so?
In that case...
...comparatively I...
Premonition of Separation?! Risa and Otani's Different Paths
I'm going to university.
What?! University?!!
No need to act so surprised!
What's with that?
Are you serious?
Of course I am.
Oh? So you really are serious...
There's no way you'll get in.
What was that?!
Sitting entrance exams isn't free, you know.
I'm aware of that!
Here "ronin" refers to a high school graduate who failed to get into university, and is studying to retake entrance exams the following year.
If you become a ronin, it'll cost you...
Reconsider before you go wasting your time and money, okay?
You could've at least said "Wow! Go for it!"...
You're not cute at all!
No, no. I am impressed by your reckless, adventurous spirit,
but I'm not going to say "go for it".
Is that how you really feel, you idiot?!
Now, now, Otani-kun.
If I were her, I'd be trying to stop you too.
Wouldn't you?
I would indeed.
What the hell do you guys take me for?!
An idiot.
IDIOT
Why am I the only one you hit?
Because you're the most annoying!
Well, sorry for being honest.
You're all damn rude.
I'm the type who can do anything if I put my mind to it.
You probably can't do it even if you put your mind to it.
Shut up!
I'm going to try, and I'm definitely going to get in.
You just watch, you bastards.
O-Otani?
Otani! Wait!
Did you come to laugh at me some more?
No.
Hey, Otani, why do you want to go to college all of the sudden?
It's not all of the sudden.
I've always wanted to.
I...
Hey, it's old man Otani!
Let's play basketball!
Y-You gave me a start.
What are you guys doing here?
Let's play, old man!
Let's play! Let's play!
This old man has to study for exams. I can't.
How uncool. Exams...
Shut up! Now hurry up and get lost!
Sheesh...
Who were they?
Kids from my neighborhood.
I play basketball with them from time to time.
You mean they play with you.
Shut up.
Anyway... I want to play basketball.
At university?
I mean after university.
As a school basketball coach or something, you know?
Going to university, getting certified,
and playing basketball with brats like that everyday...
I think it'd be fun.
Are you saying you want to get a teaching certificate? You want to become a teacher?
I was just giving you an example!
Well... I do like kids and all.
Elementary kids and such...
An elementary school teacher?
For example. Just for example.
Otani... a school teacher?
Sensei! Otani-sensei!
Y-You're laughing too much.
This is why I didn't want to tell you.
That girl... She's definitely the old man's girlfriend.
But old man Otani's shorter.
I guess that's what they call "disparity".
You guys are still here?
Give me that basketball. I'm confiscating it!
Hey! Give it back, baldy!
I'm not bald bald! If you want it, come get it!
That Otani... He's a big hit.
So Otani wants to become an elementary teacher.
If he does, it'd be hard to tell who's the kid and who's the teacher.
Still, it's nice to see him smile like that.
Half of me thinks it's impossible, but I'll support him.
That's what I thought.
But before I knew it, something happened that would have a deeper impact than Otani's college plans.
Nobu-chan is...
Going to an undergraduate university in Hokkaido?!
What? You guys haven't heard?
Well, it's true.
Nobu-chan, what is this all of the sudden?
No matter how much you liked our trip there...
You've got it wrong.
Oh? Then why, exactly?
Are your parents getting transfered?
Grandma's body is deteriorating, so she's going to go and live in the country.
I'm going along to take care of her.
But... What about your mom and dad?
They've both got jobs here, so they can't go.
She says she has some old friends up there,
but Grandma will get lonely all by herself.
Are you okay with this, Nakao?
A long distance relationship...
No problem! It'll be fine, right?
We'll call everyday, right?
Ah, I see...
Nobu-chan and Nakao-chi are going to maintain a long distance relationship?
Hey, Risa, will you come shopping with me after school?
Don't you have to study for the entrance exams?
The undergraduate university in Hokkaido offers entry by referral.
All I need to get in, is a high school diploma and an interview.
Is that so?
Yep. So I'm all set!
Sorry, Risa.
Huh? What for?
For not telling you about going to Hokkaido.
It's okay. You only just decided, right?
Right, right.
In any case, are you really planning on buying all of those?
That's why I came shopping today.
I can't come back just to shop.
Ah. I see.
When I told Grandma I'd go with her to Hokkaido, she gave me quite a bit of spending money.
That's nice...
Say, Nobu-chan, your grandma has given you a lot of money over the years, hasn't she?
Yeah. That's why, in a sense, I'm doing this to repay her.
I love my grandma, after all.
What about Nakao-chi?
I love him too.
Are you really okay with this?
Yeah. Nakao-chi is okay with it too.
He's coming over to have dinner at my place tonight.
Hey, Risa, which of these is better?
That one.
Well, we are talking about the self-assured, strong-willed Nobu-chan, after all.
No matter where she goes, I'm sure she has the confidence to do well.
Nakao-chi, I'm going to get some eggs, okay?
Sure.
Thanks.
Nakao-chi, is this really alright with you?
Is it really alright if I take Nobuko so far away?
I care about you too, Grandma.
I'd be worried if you went all by yourself.
I'm so happy to have such a wonderful granddaughter.
And she has such a wonderful boyfriend too.
Grandma.
Thank you.
Nobu-chan.
Okay! Grandma's going to perform an act she's saved specially for Nakao-chi!
An act?
Grandma!
Grandma?
Carp!
He liked it! He liked it!
Grandma, your body is weak. Don't over exert yourself.
I had fun.
Be careful, okay?
Nakao-chi!
I'm sorry.
What was that?
Never mind. It was nothing.
Well, see you tomorrow.
At that point,
neither we nor Nobu-chan knew how Nakao-chi felt deep down.
As the day of Nobu-chan's interview in Hokkaido approached,
Nakao-chi was falling apart inside.
Nakao's been acting weird.
How so?
Well, yesterday...
Right? It's weird, right?
No way. There's just no way.
How can it be? How can it be?
Life really is just great, isn't it?
Good afternoon. It's a pleasure to meet you. Indeed, indeed. Thank you...
What are you doing?
Oh, nothing. I'm fine.
Kyah! Pervert!
Nakao! What the heck were you doing?!
There's a boy in the girl's bathroom!
I'm fine, really.
It's spilling everywhere, Nakao.
Really? I think it's pretty.
What do you think?
That's definitely weird.
With Nobu-chan going to Hokkaido, Nakao-chi is probably-
Bad news! Nakao fell down the stairs!
What?!
Chiharu-chan, where's Nobu-chan?
Gori-sensei called her to the office just now.
I'll go find Nobu-chan. You go on ahead.
Right!
I really don't know what to do with you.
Sorry. Good thing I walked away with just a scratch.
What do you mean "good thing", you idiot?!
Get it together!
I don't have it together?
If you did, you wouldn't have fallen down the stairs!
Is that so...
I guess you're right.
You've been acting weird lately.
You...
Infirmary
You don't want Nobu-chan to go to Hokkaido, do you?
No.
But it'll make Nobu-chan feel bad, so I can't say anything.
I mean, she's made her final decision and all...
Nobu-chan!
Nobu-chan, wait!
She...
Nakao...
Nobu-chan...
Risa! What should I do?!
I thought it over for so long...
I gave it so much thought...
But...
Why are you crying?
Well, you've always been the one to help me...
But now I don't have any advice I can give you.
I feel so useless.
It's not like I was expecting any advice from you, you know.
Saying that doesn't help.
Then why did you chase after me?
Well, I did intend to say something...
I have no idea what you're on about!
Me neither.
We should leave them alone.
Let's go.
Yeah. I've decided.
What are you going to say to her?
I'm going to settle this.
Who are you calling "Nakao-chi"?
What's with those glasses, Nakao-chi?
I told you, stop adding the "chi" after Nakao.
It's unfashionable and out of date these days.
What's up with him?
Nakao-chi's gone crazy.
Call me "Master".
Y-You...
Whatever. Let's get going.
If you want to go, then go by yourself.
I'll go with some other girl.
What are you talking about?
I thought you were going to settle this?
I've never told you this before, but...
...I've actually got three other women.
Will you knock it off already?!
What's up with you, Nakao-chi?
Didn't you hear me? I said I've got three other women!
Listen, Nakao-chi...
Maiko!
This is lover #1, Maiko.
Ma-Mai-Mai-M-M-Maity?
What are you talking about?
I'm Maiko.
What the heck are you doing?! Get out of here! Get!
Oh dear. Even you?
Suzuko!
Su-Su-Su-Suzuki-kun?
Sorry.
And lover #3, Haruko!
That's enough, you idiot!
Hey! Let Haruko make her appearance!
What's going on?!
Wait! Your make up isn't done yet!
What are you trying to do?
Nakao-chi, What's the matter?
You should just forget a terrible guy like me, Nobuko.
I'll go live in a harem with these lovers of mine.
You're just a bather to me.
A bather?
My gut tells me he meant "bother".
BATHER
Bather...
Understand?
Yeah. More or less.
Then get out of here.
Nobu-chan!
I'm Haruko.
What was that for?!!
Shut up, you moron!
Nobu-chan! Nobu-chan!
You there! You, man standing there!
What the heck was that disgusting display for?!!
I want Nobu-chan to hate me.
If she hates me and forgets about me,
she can go to Hokkaido without any worries.
Thanks for your help, guys.
You idiot! Why you didn't you tell me about this?!
'Cause you'd get angry.
Damn straight!
If you're going to cry about it, don't do things like this!
If you don't want her to leave, just tell her!
Otani...
I'm sorry. I know you went to a lot of trouble to get these,
but Grandma would be upset if I poked holes in my body.
Sorry. I thought you had ears pierced.
Message:
Risa
I'm still going to Hokkaido after all.
Nobu-chan...
It might have seen silly, but that little display really got to me.
After having that done for my benefit, I don't really have much choice but to go, do I?
Um... You know, Nobu-chan...
It's thanks to you that I was able to get together with Otani.
What's this, all of the sudden?
I was able to keep trying so hard because you were around.
If I'd been on my own, I'd probably just have done weird thing up until now.
Mr.Policeman! There's a suspicious person over here!
Not like that!
Anyway...
Anyway, if you've thought it over and decided, it can't be wrong.
Things should work out.
Things will definitely work out!
You came to the decision to go to Hokkaido yourself, so it'll be fine.
It'll be fine so... believe in yourself.
Thank you.
I'm sorry I can't say anything more.
No. This is plenty.
I'm the one who should be thanking you.
I can't thank you enough.
Hey, Risa, I have a favor to ask...
Just as Nobu-chan has always had my back, it's my turn to help her this time.
You know...
...I'm coming straight back after my interview.
Yeah, but...
In spring you won't...
That's months from now!
Nakao didn't come? I did call him...
It's fine. I'm only going for the interview this time.
Nobu-chan!
Nakao-chi!
Nakao...
Nobu-chan.
Yes?
Have a safe trip.
Do your best.
Do you remember these?
They were the first present I ever gave you.
You got your ears pierced?
I asked Risa to take me get them done.
But won't your grandma get mad?
It'll be alright. But I won't be able to wear them until they heal.
Once I get there, I'll wear these every day.
That way, I won't ever forget you.
Nobu-chan...
I love you, Nobu-chan.
I love you more than anything in this world.
I love you too.
Wha-What are they saying?
This is much more embarrassing than a simple "don't go".
So what? They're happy.
Man...
Nobu-chan got her happy ending,
but what's going to happen to us?
Fortunes
You there.
M-Me?
You're going to have some woman trouble soon.
That's what this baby here just told me.
What was that?
Oh? What is it?
One is a woman much older then you.
The other is a woman over 170 cm tall,
Only slightly older then you.
You're right about the older woman...
but I don't know anybody that tall.
Sorry. I've got to get to work.
Wait! The fortune telling fee!
Sheesh. And my powers were working properly for once too.
This short boy would end up having an even deeper impact on us than Nobu-chan,
although we didn't know it at the time.
Kozmui is cheating on me with a short guy from work?!
No, no.
Who would date a guy that short if they had a choice?
Are you making fun of me?!
Uh...
Lovely Complex~ Love Com.
Next: Otani's Catastrophic Declaration!!
Otani's Catastrophic Declaration!!
Be sure to watch!