I challenge you!
Let's see who can get someone faster!
What'll I get if I win?
I'll buy you whatever game you want.
But if I win, you'll buy me a new pair of basketball shoes.
Let's do it!
I'm not going to lose!
The Ex-Girlfriend Love Triangle!?
What the heck is that?
A brush? A sea urchin?
Shut up. Today, I'm a new man.
Let me fix that for you.
Don't touch me, idiot!
Trying to look cooler, huh? How sickening...
Starting today, my popularity is only going to increase.
And then you'll be buying those new shoes for me.
Huh?
Suddenly changing your hairstyle won't make you popular. you know.
Same goes for you. What good will it do to start wearing red lipstick all of a sudden?
An opening!
Nobu-chan! Chiharu-chan! Let's go home.
What should we do now. darling?
Well, let's see...
Th...This feels totally awkward.
That goes for both of us.
Why are you walking with us anyway?
There's some stuff I have to do at Nakao's place.
Man, you ruined my perfectly styled hair after it took so long it almost made me late for school.
You're still going on about that?
Not only are you small in body, you're small in character too.
I'm gonna sue you for defamation!
Go ahead anytime,
Hey Nakao. let's go get our fortunes told!
Fortunes?
HIRORIRARIN!
Couple Compatibility
Wow! Our compatibility is 85% !
Chiharu-chan, Suzuki. You guys should have a go too.
Come on, give it a go!
What do you want to eat?
You pick Nobu-chan.
Hey Otani, want to go see Umibouzu's live concert?
A friend of mine got two extra tickets and asked me to find people to go.
Umibouzu?! Seriously? I'll go!
Huh? You like him too, Koizumi?
Of course! l love him! He's just awesome!
Yeah, he's totally awesome, isn't he?!
Have you heard his new song?
Of course I have! it's freaking awesome!
it's great! His voice is just amazing, huh?
Totally, totally.
Why don't you two try going out?
Huh?
What'd you say?
You seem to share the same interests.
Your compatibility must be pretty high.
How are we compatible?!
You both like Umibouzu, don't you?
That just happens to be the case.
The expression "Tama-tama" means "happens to be the case" but the word "tama" itself is a slang term for "balls".
A Girl shouldn't say a thing like "balls-balls".
I did NOT say "balls"!
See? I hate girls like this.
I don't need to hear that from you!
Um... excuse me, are you ready to order?
Uh, sure. Just a second...
New Item
A tropical sensation
Hawaiian Dancer
Oh! A new item on the menu..
I have to try this.
One Hawaiian Dancer!
See?
You're wrong!!!
I want to be in love!!!
Like l said. you should just go for Otani-kun
Right. Chiharu-chan?
Give it a rest.
Why should I have to go for that midget?
I need someone who is at least taller than me.
But Otani-Kun is pretty popular, you know.
You're pulling my leg again.
Then let's go watch the basketball team practice after school, okay?
Look Those girls are probably from second or third year.
He got the ball.
Do your best!
They always get worked up watching Otani-kun.
Are you serious?
Hmm... the midget is actually pretty good.
Oh. That's quite a jump.
Hey, Otani!
Don't go for a jump shot just to look cool when you're so short.
Why is the coach so upset?
He got it in didn't he?
He did.
Think about your height before you jump, shorty.
What the heck?! What an irritating old geezer!
Now, now..
Yes.
Otani got chewed out by the coach...
Awww...
C-Cute?
He is so--
I see. So the midget had this up his sleeve too.
How underhanded!!
What's with that ugly face?
Oh...
So you're using itty-bitty flower hair clips to make yourself look cute?
Huh? I borrowed these from my older sister.
Oh? How cute.
You look like a little girl, don't you?
What the hell is your problem?!
I'm not gonna lose to you!
Like hell I'll buy you shoes!
When the time comes, you'll be the one buying me tons of games!
Huh?!
What was she on about?
I need to do something, otherwise..
I need to do something.
Oh, right!
Nobu-Chan!
Hook up parties.
Are there any hook up parties coming up?!
Huh?!
Hook up parties?!!
All right.
I'm going to surprise him and find a great guy.
Ah, Risa.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
A horse...
A monkey..
A bird...
A dog...
...and a pig?
Hello
What the hell?!
What is this, a zoo?
Well, zoos aren't so bad.
Zoos are fun, right?
I'm a giraffe too, after all, aren't I?
Yep. It's fine. This is fine.
What's important is what's on the inside.
Hi, Koizumi-Chan.
Eh? What's wrong? what's wrong?
Feeling down?
Say, how tall are you?
It came over.
170 cm.
Oh? You're really tall!
If you're this tall now, you may even crack three meters by the time you graduate.
Just kidding.
How could that happen?
Was that funny? That was funny, wasn't it?
People always say I'm funny.
I can't laugh.
It always comes to this in the end.
So, how'd it go yesterday?
Can't you tell from the expression on my face?
That's because your standards are too high.
Hey..
Don't go around saying "your standards are too high"  to people who don't have a boyfriend.
You asked me what kind of guys I like, and I gave you a list of qualities...
I didn't seriously expect to meet a guy that has all of them, but...
You're right. Maybe my standards are too high.
Risa..
I know.
As a person...as a woman...
As a person... as a woman...
...It's no good to go on like this.
It's no good, Koizumi.
I know! I'm just no good.
Not that, this. Very bad news.
Ahh! My Umibouzu ticket!
I just got it from Nakao.
It's for Umibouzu's Christmas Live concert.
Christmas...
December 25th Lover's day, Christmas.
In Japan, Christmas is a holiday for couples and lovers.
Wha..
Why do I have to do something as miserable as spend Christmas with you?!
Like I know?!
I'd like to throw those same words back in your face.
Don't bother.
Ohh... Why has it...
Ohh...Why has it...
...turned out like this?
What country are you supposed to be from?
What's wrong with the two of you going together, anyway?
No way.
Why should I have to walk around on Christmas being called All Hanshin-Kyoujin?
Maybe the Christmas atmosphere will help love flow between you two...
If an amazon like her gets swept up in any kind of flow, she'll probably clog the drain.
Who's flowing where now?
Even if we do walk along a romantic Christmas street together,
there's no way that love will develop.
Don't sneeze like an old man.
I think I caught a cold recently.
Are you seriously looking for a boyfriend?
Of course I am. Our challenge isn't over yet.
Well, you've got no plans for Christmas anyway, right?
Yeah.
We'll just go to the concert and then go straight home, before any romantic feelings develop.
Whether we take our time getting there, or take longer going home, it's not like we'll fall in love.
You're right.
Say, what kind of girls do you like, Otani?
Me?
Well, not the type who sneezes like an old man, at the very least.
When a girl sneezes, she should cover her mouth with her hand.
See, like tha...
Chiharu-chan with different colored hair?
How could that be?
But... But...
Huh?! There are two Chiharu-Chans?
Kanzaki.
Atsushi-Kun.
What's going on?
Kanzaki.
Atsushi-kun.
Atsushi-kun? Who's that?
It's me.
It's been a while.
Uh, yeah.
Are you doing okay?
Yeah.
Th... This is a surprise.
This girl looks exactly like Chiharu-chan.
Um... I'm kind of in a hurry, so...
Sure.
Hey, Atsushi-kun, who was that girl?
None of your business!
What's wrong, Atsushi-kun? You can tell me, you know.
How suspicious, how suspicious.
She used to be my girlfriend.
"Used to be"... You mean she's your ex-girlfriend?!
Why are you so surprised?!
No way! Seriously?
Why would I lie to you about this?
Like you wouldn't. You are Otani, after all...
You...
I've been alive for like 15, 16 odd years, It's only normal to have dated.
I haven't.
That's not something to be proud of!
Shock!
Ultimate shock...
An ex-girlfriend... That Otani's...
So even someone like Otani... How ridiculous.
Hey, I heard about it from Nakao-chi.
That girl, Kanzaki Mayu,
was the manager of the basketball club back when they were in middle school.
She went out with Otani-kun for two years.
And apparently Otani-kun really liked her.
So it really is true...
I'd always thought that Otani had never dated anyone since the day he was born, like me.
Now I feel like I've been left behind.
Hey Otani, why did you break up with your ex?
Wh-Why are you asking about that?!
Because I can't imagine why you would.
You actually managed to get a girlfriend, but then broke up with her?
I didn't break up with her.
She dumped me.
Huh?!
Um...
She suddenly told me that there was another guy she liked.
It was particularly depressing because the guy she liked...
...was over two meters tall.
We used to call him the Equestrian Ground Giant of Nishi Middle School.
I think it was probably because of my height.
B-But I'm sure that was just a coincidence.
I'm sure she didn't pick him just for his height.
Even if it was a coincidence...
... I was already conscious about my height.
Now I'm even more so.
But if I said a thing like that, you'd punch me again, right Koizumi?
Otani...
I see, So Otani has a past like that.
Huh?
You will find happiness.
Otani,
I completely understand how you feel.
Getting dumped over something like that...
No wonder you're so concerned about height.
Do your best, Otani.
You have to live on, Otani!
Oh! I left my purse at school.
You guys go on ahead, okay?
Okay.
So we've decide to have a party with everyone who was in the basketball club on the 25th.
I was wondering if you could spare some time on that day.
I see.
The more you look, the more she looks like Chiharu-chan.
No, it's not that she looks like Chiharu-chan...
Chiharu-chan looks like her.
So that's why he liked Chiharu-chan.
You have to come, okay?
There's something I want to say to you.
Huh?
Bye.
What's this? What's with that conflicted look?
Could it be Otani...still likes that girl?
Could it be Otani... still likes that girl?
Oh, the 25th...
Don't worry.
I'll go to the Umibouzu concert by myself.
Ko-Koizumi when did you-
Something she wants to say, huh?
It could be that she wants to get back together...
If you don't go, and don't end up getting back together you might blame it on me.
It's fine.
Rather than finding a new girlfriend, why not get back with your old one?
It'll be a faster way to settle our challenge too.
Koizumi...
Ahh, but since I helped you a bit...
...we'll cancel the shoes thing, okay?
I'll just treat you to tea.
Materialistic, aren't you?
Of course!
I don't know whether to consider you a good or bad person, you know.
I'm a good person, of course.
Ahh, I see.
But, to see you show an expression like that... It surprised me.
Nobu-chan, Chiharu-chan.
And so it is.
What do you mean "and so it is"?
I'm gonna be all alone for Christmas.
Want to hang out for a bit before the Concert?
Hmmm?
Um... if that's impossible, hanging out on Christmas eve is okay too.
Sorry. I'll be going over to my darling's place on the 24th for an overnight Christmas party.
I want to give Suzuki-kun a scarf on the 25th, but I haven't finished it yet, so on the 24th...
Ahh, but if I get working on it right away, I might have time...
It's fine. It's fine. You don't need to worry about me.
It's ok We're still friends, right?!
But... Sorry.
It's fine. Christmas has nothing to do with us Japanese anyway.
What does it matter if I'm alone?
Damn.
I was so bored, I came way too early.
That hurt.
Ahh! My stockings ripped! I'm bleeding!
Everyone else must be having fun right now.
Otani must have made up with his ex-girlfriend too...
What should I do? I've been left all alone.
Now that Otani has a girlfriend, he probably won't hang out with me anymore either.
What should I do?
It's winter vacation, but even if I want to hang out with everybody, I'll just be in the way.
My leg hurts.
The concert's about to start too.
What does it matter if I see Umibouzu? What does it matter if I get excited?
It's not like there's anyone I can share that excitement with.
When it comes down to it...  I feel really lonely.
When it comes down to it.... I feel really lonely.
Koizumi.
Huh?
That sounded like Otani's voice just now.
Otani...
I finally found you.
Otani?
Where'd you go?
What are you doing here?
What do you mean? We're going to the Umibouzu concert, aren't we?
Huh? But what about your ex-girlfriend?
She can wait till next time.
I did make plans with you first, right?
I may have hesitated a bit, but it's not like I'd break a promise.
I don't want to owe you any favors.
You idiot...
Huh?
You idiot.
W-W-W-W-Why are you crying?
What are you doing?
Why are you calling me an idiot?
Koizumi, what's wrong?
Kne...
Kne?
Kne...Kne... K-Kne...
Kne... Kne...K-Kne...
What are you? A bird, now?
My knee hurts.
Your knee?
Oh! It's bleeding.
What did you do?
Are you okay? Can you walk?
Well, let's go to a pharmacy first.
Okay.
Otani's hand...  is so warm.
Merry Christmas. I'm Umibouzu's lead. Umibouzu.
YO
Man that was the best.
Yeah I was so into it.
The street was filled with Christmas spirit.
Even if we are All Hanshin-Kyoujin, something might happen.
Risa...
Huh?!
Risa!
HUH?!!!
Otani. Here obligatory chocolate.
I don't want it.
Didn't you ask me to give it to you?
Give it to that Haruka guy.
Lovely Complex~ Love Com
Next: A Guy you Like or a Guy from the Past?
A Guy You Like, or a Guy from the Past?
Be sure to watch.