Got you!
Let me go! What are you doing?!
He fits snugly in my arms.
Hey, hey! Wh-Wh-What do you think you're doing?!!
It doesn't matter if I can carry him in my arms.
It doesn't matter if he's shorter than me.
I...
...like Otani.
A Maiden's Determination! Love-Love Confession Plan!!
Risa!
Nobu-chan.
How are you? Feeling okay?
Feeling?
Great, of course!
Well...
...I have come to the seaside for Umibouzu live concert, after all!
I even brought my camera.
Hurry up and be night time already...
That's not what I meant!
Coming to the beach during summer vacation should be about love and youth!
Love! Romance! Not Umibouzu, okay!
Focus on Otani-kun!
What? Otani?
What? You're still trying to hide it at this point?
Come on, just admit it to me and I'll help you out.
Help me? What do you mean by that?
You llike Otani-kun, right?
You like him, RIGHT?
Right.
Hey, boys and girls, please listen up for a sec!
Okay, let's try to give Risa and Otani-kun some alone time today.
Yes.
H-Hey!
For the sake of Risa realizing her one-sided love, we all need to do what we can!
Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-What the heck are you saying?!
Stop!
Oh, so you're finally going to confess to Otani-kun, are you?
Do your best.
Wait...
What?
I told you, everyone already knows.
The only one who hasn't realized it is Otani himself.
Uh... You've got it all wrong!
I-I-It's not like...
Hey!
I couldn't find you guys.
I was looking for you for ages...
Get together... Get together... Get together...
What's wrong? Everyone is so quiet...
It's nothing. Nothing at all, okay.
Here we go!
That's fun!
Isn't it? My turn now!
How's that?!
Hah! This is nothing like the pool!
Ahh! Salty!
You idiot!
Get together... Get together... Get together...
Here, Nobu-chan.
Catch, Suzuki-kun.
Here.
Koizumi... look, a hermit crab.
Oh, it is!
Ahh, it hid.
Get together... Get together... Get together...
How cute!
Right, Suzuki-kun, let's have a race from the beach to the open sea.
The sea is that way.
They're watching.
Get together... Get together... Get together...
They're all watching my every move.
Hey!
What's got you so stiff?
Take this! And this!
You sure are casual, completely oblivious to other people's problems!
Huh? I have no idea what you're on about.
Take this! And this!
Take that! That's payback!
You're not bad!
What? What's wrong?
You sure are clumsy.
I'm fine.
I'll watch our stuff. You guys go and have fun.
Huh? But...
Yeah. Risa will get bored all alone.
Otani-kun, could you stay with her?
Tha... That's... I'll be fine by myself!
But you're hurt. We can't just leave you on your own.
Okay. I'll stay.
My main objective for the day is to catch some rays anyway.
Ah, I see.
Well in that case, stay with Risa and you guys can both get a tan.
No, no! I'll be fine on my own.
Why do you have a problem with that?
Besides, even if you tan that skinny body of yours, you won't look any better.
What was that?!
If you're got this much time to spare, why don't you go swim?
Oh, so it's like that, huh? Let's go, Nakao, Suzuki.
When I become a lawyer, I'm gonna sue you!
But I wanted to swim with Nobu-chan...
Shut up!
Me too... with Chiharu-chan...
Hey, you idiot!
Who asked you to get him to sue you?! I told you to confess to him!
S-Sorry.
Onee-chan, you here alone?
Ya wanna have some fun together?
You idiot.
You really thought someone was trying to pick you up?
I didn't think that.
What are you doing, anyway?
Resting, resting.
Thanks...
I didn't say that was for you.
I'm gonna drink'em both. Have you no shame?!
What?! Why didn't you put it over there, then?!
Just kidding. Take it.
So annoying...
Who's fault is that? You're the one who started it.
I'm just returning the favour.
Thanks for treating me.
You sure are weird today.
A-Am I?
Are you just being quiet or are you feeling weak?
It's because I've been wounded.
Does it still hurt?
Should I get you some pain killers or something?
N-No, I'm fine.
That's okay. then.
Otani...
You're a good guy.
You only just noticed?
What if...
What if I happened to accidentally fall for you...
What would you do?
Don't say such disgusting things.
Isn't there anything better we can talk about?
With someone like you, there probably isn't!
Huh? What's that supposed to mean?
Shut up, midget!
Stop joking around.
Don't get your hopes up about ever finding a boyfriend, amazon.
Wha...What's this?!!
You're right. I'm just a giant amazon!
Otani-kun, what did you do?!
I don't know! She just suddenly...
It's my fault. I'm just an amazon...
You said a mean thing like that?
Wait! She's the one who's always calling me a midget!
So what?!
Poor thing.
Koizumi really is weird today.
A girl in love will always be emotional!
Novu-chan!
In love?
There's someone you like, Koizumi? Who?!
You're denser than I thought.
I never thought it would end up like this.
No...
This is my fault too.
Wha...
What's going on?
Risa-chan...
Hey...
You poor thing.
Thanks. I'm okay.
Hey...
I said Hey!
Do your best!
Don't ignore me! What's with you guys?!
Let's all go get snow cones.
You guys! Stop ignoring me!!!
Is your foot okay?
Of course.
We're going to an Umibouzu concert, aren't we?
I forgot about the pain ages ago.
Hey... what was all that about earlier?
The summer sun was just too much for me.
Don't worry about it.
What the heck?
So who's this guy you like Koizumi?
Not telling.
What?! Everyone else knows. You're gonna leave me out?
I'm not telling idiots.
Ah... I know.
The guy you like is shorter than you, right?
That's why you cried when I called you an amazon.
Uh... That's...
Ha! I'm right, aren't I?
You're an idiot.
How can you let stuff like that worry you?
You have your own charm, Koizumi.
Don't be indecisive. Just go for it.
So, who do you like?
Never mind.
How can I not mind?
Of course I mind, being the only one who doesn't know.
This is just the type of guy he is...
You'll find out soon enough.
But this is the type of girl I am...
What do you mean "soon enough"?
Hey, I really do care, you know.
I don't know if it'll go smoothly...
Hey, Koizumi!
...but I like him and I just can't help it.
Don't worry about it.
The concert is about to start. Let's go.
Otani.
As punishment for making me cry, take a picture with me.
What the...?
Right.
Don't be indecisive. Just go for it.
You just wait, Otani!
Still, I never thought he'd be this slow on the uptake.
He's been asking me "Who does Koizumi like?"
Over and over since we got back from the beach.
Risa, don't forget that Otani-kun is popular.
This summer vacation is your chance!
Once summer is over, we've got the school trip and a ton of events coming up.
If you keep procrastinating, you'll have to deal with a ton of rivals going after Otani-kun.
Ahh! No, no no! I can't deal with that!
There, there. I'll help you, but you need to do your best too, okay?
It's completely useless using a subtle approach with him.
You just have to do it directly.
Directly?
Tell him you like him.
Good, good!
There's no way I can do that!
It'll never work if you can't even say that.
Well... yeah...
Hey...
There's something I just have to say to you.
Is that okay?
I can't.
Basically, you need to get him alone first.
Alone? Just the two of us?
What's the problem?
It's not like it'd be your first time alone with Otani-kun.
But this is totally different.
Up till now, we've jsut been together as All Hanshin-Kyojin.
How can we get a romantic mood going now?
Impossible or not, just do it!
Are you okay with being All-Kyojin forever?
But what should I say?
Like I said...
How about,
"I've said a lot of bad things up till now, but, to be honest..."
Hold on. Let me write this down.
And then?
What are you doing?
"Gyah"? What am I, a monster?
I-I-It's nothing! We weren't doing anything!
What were you talking about so secretively?
Nothing! Right, right?
I'm not gonna say "right".
Go no. Do it now, okay.
Come on. Let's go, darling.
Huh? What's going on?
I'll tell you later.
You're excluding me again...
Otani-kun....
Hey...
There's something I just have to say to you.
Is that okay?
What's wrong?
Disgusting!
"Disgusting"?! I was trying so hard...
Fine.
There's something I've got to say to you too.
So, what did you want to tell me?
Who is it that you like?
Th-That's...
Everyone keeps talking about it behind my back. It's really getting on my nerves.
Why am I the only one who doesn't know?
That's because...
It's completely useless using a subtle approach with him.
That's because you're the one I like!
How could I possibly say that?
Hey, I'm talking to you.
I can't say that! That's beyond embarrassing!
Hey, did you hear what I just said, Koizumi?
But I have to do it over summer.
Are you even listening?
Hey!
If I don't tell him now...
Can you hear me?!
Do it, Risa. Go for it, Risa!
Hey!!!
Just be brave and do it!
Bring it on!
Cone on, already!
Oh... right.
I've said a lot of bad things
up till now, but,
to be honest
Like this, huh...
I-I've said a lot of bad things up till now, but, to be honest...
What are you trying to say?
Wait! I've got it!
You...
I...
Ohh...
No, no, no, no!
You're not just being emotional. You're being downright suspicious now.
Ughh... whatever you say...
You were shouting during the game too.
Let me tell you, we won today because of me.
You wouldn't know since you weren't watching at all, though.
Of course I know.
I was watching you the whole time.
You were so cool...
Hey, if something is really troubling you, you can always talk to me about it.
I might be able to help, you know.
Or do you really consider me that untrustworthy?
No, that's not it.
Why are you acting so distant, then?
Aren't we All Hanshin-Kyojin partners?
Why are you clutching at your head?
What? Can't I clutch at it?
Do you really like him that much? This guy?
What kind of guy is he?
An idiot.
He's an idiot... but he's a good guy.
He's shorter than me, but he's so sweet that I don't care.
Is that so...
Don't tell me the reason you've been coming to watch basketball...
...is because this guy you like is on the team?
It's that freshman, Yamamoto, right?
Huh?!
If it;s someone shorter than you, and he's on the basketball team, it has to be Yamamoto.
No wait...
Ikeda is pretty short too....
You're an idiot.
What?!
It's fine. Let's just drop it.
I feel like I'm gonna cry.
He's that dense?!
Man, Otani is seriously slow, and hopeless to boot.
Well, whatever. It's not like it matters, anyway.
Cheer up.
Here.
What's this?
A birthday present.
Oh right! It's my birthday! I totally forgot for a second there.
You sure are perky now.
Thanks! Can I open it?
You're already opening it...
Th-This is...
A fountain you can put on your bathroom wall!
Wow! Awesome! I'm super happy!
I can't wait for tonight's bath!
She's wanted one for a long time now.
I really don't understand her taste.
It's Otani.
Maybe he's calling to wish you a happy birthday.
I sent a message and told him it's your birthday.
Wh-What did you do that for?!
Hurry up and answer, or he'll hang up.
Hello?
Hey, it's me.
"Me" Who's "me"? Stoip trying to act cool.
You lookin' for a fight?
Are you free right now?
Free?
Uh...
Free
Free! Free! Free! Free! Free!
Uh, I guess I'm free.
What's that supposed to mean?
Well, meet me on the roof of the big building next to the train station at 7pm.
The roof? Why there?
Just come.
Oh, and wear what you wore when we went to the festival, okay?
Hey, you're late.
Why are we meeting in a place like this?
And what was that about the festival?
Well, it's not nothing big, but...
Here. Your birthday present.
Huh? Are you serious?!
Just look inside, would you.
Huh? Umibouzu!
This is...
Yep. It's the premium edition.
Plus, it's been signed. It's my most treasured possession.
But I thought you said you'd never give this away...
Well, if I'm giving it to a fan like you, I think God will forgive me.
And...
...this is the limited edition badge that came with the CD!!!
As a treat, I'm giving this to you too.
S-Seriously?!!!
Ahh! Thank you!
I'll never forget this!
You'd better not.
But these are all just extras.
Extras?
Is there something else?
It looks like it's dark enough. It should be about time...
What?
Huh? What's this?
There are fireworks today?
Great, isn't it?
I found this place last year.
This is the best spot.
Awesome!
How pretty...
Are you feeling a bit better now?
You've been all frustrated and weird lately.
I thought watching the fireworks would cheer you up.
It's appropriate when watching fireworks.
The yukata.
But " fine feathers don't make fine birds", right?
Shut up, you idiot!
Wow. They sure are pretty.
I...
really do like Otani.
If it's now, I think I can say it.
Otani.
Huh? What?
I...
I like you, Otani!
What are you saying, Koizumi?
I confessed to the guy I like, but...
Hey, are you crying?
Lovely Complex~ Love Com.
Next: Sunk! The Worst Confession in History!!
Be sure to watch!
Sunk! The Worst Confession in History!!