Together Forever!!
This is no good!
The more I think about Otani's exam tomorrow, the more worried I get.
I should send him a message of encouragement...
Yo, this is for real. You got mail.
It's not what you think...
I called around, but no one else could help me.
Come on in.
Sorry to intrude.
No need to be so formal.
That's not the problem here...
Sure, sure. Just come in.
Don't tell me that's your boyfriend?
This is Otani-sama.
Uh, nice to meet you.
Um... I just have one question...
As long as it's not about height.
Are you really okay with someone like this?
Take your insults elsewhere!
What's this? We have a guest?
Ah, I was just explaining...
Oh dear, oh dear, oh dear. My, my, my...
Dad?
Hey! There's no need to call him.
Oh. He was right there.
Excuse me, Father...
Uh, n-n-nice to meet you!
I'm, uh... Koizumi's... I mean... R-R-Risa's boyfriend, Otani.
What should I do? I haven't prepared anything...
Don't go to any trouble!
Hei...
Yes, I'm only just over 156cm.
I'm sorry. Forgive me.
No...
Are you really okay with someone like this?
Don't refer to me as "this."
Um... sorry to impose on you like this, asking to stay over so suddenly...
Stay over?
Uh, let me explain...
I-It's not what you think!
I don't have any ulterior motive!
The truth is, he has an exam tomorrow,
but everyone in his family has come down with influenza.
That's right!
So it isn't what you think. Honestly.
Oh, ho...
My, that is a problem.
It's fine, but where will he sleep?
Well, he could sleep in my room...
No! I mean, I'll sleep in a different room...
It's not what you think! I apologize!
My, my...
Never mind!
Here.
I'm sorry. Are you tired?
No.
Well, a bit.
But I seem totally suspicious, don't I?!
What am I doing, ending up like this the day before the exam?!
Doing stuff like this... like this...
There, there. Calm down.
Sorry.
I'll greet them properly next time.
But at this rate, I'll look like some useless guy who'd blow his exams
just so he could fool around with his girlfriend.
It's fine. I explained everything.
No. That's not good enough for me.
You're serious about the strangest things, aren't you?
I'm always serious.
I don't stand for halfheartedness.
Is that so?
But that aside, you should worry about your exam for now.
You're right...
You'll want to study all night, right?
I'll go hang out in my brother's room.
But I don't mind...
If I'm with you, I'll just end up talking to you.
I don't want to get in the way.
Sorry.
If there's an emergency, just call me.
'kay.
Right! Do your best.
'kay. Let's do this.
Yeah.
If it's Otani, he'll be fine.
Even if he was chased out of his home the day before his exam,
even if he had to meet my parents,
there's no need to worry.
Hello. Would you like something to eat?
What should I do?
Should I wake him up?
But if he sleeps for a bit...
His eyelashes are pretty long...
How cute!
Do your best tomorrow, okay?
Oh no!
Otani!!!
Otani! Wake up, Otani!
What time is your exam?!
9:20am...
But it's already past 8...
How long does it take to get there?!
If I take the train, it takes about an hour. If I rush now, I can still make it!
Your stuff! Your stuff!
Why didn't you wake me up?!
Oh, never mind!
What the...?
What is this?!
Snow? Why?
On TV they just said that the trains and buses aren't running.
Wh-What should you do, Otani?
It's fine.
Huh? What are you saying?
My life has been a mess since I was chased out of my house last night.
Snow, huh?
That certainly was a surprise.
There's so much of it too... That's how unlucky I am.
You idiot!
What are you-
All of the other examinees are snowed out too!
It's not like it's just you!
What are you rambling on about? Get up! Stand up, Otani!
I am standing.
You can do this!
Koizumi...
If you've got the time for this,
then why not run there?
Takato!
Here.
Huh?
Right.
No way!!!
But the trains aren't running...
Then take the subway!
This... This is too mu-
You're going too far!
I'll apologize if you die.
Don't jinx me!
But you've worked so hard, Otani. I don't want to see it go to waste.
It doesn't matter whether you pass or fail, as long as you do your best!
Don't waste all of your effort up until now!
Koizumi...
Hey! Don't ride tandem!
Right! The subway!
Entrance Examination Center
And then, once today is over, I'll say "Thanks for all your hard work" with a smile.
Risa:
Risa:   Exactly
Risa:   Exactly...
Risa:   Exactly... 5
Risa:   Exactly... 5 min
Risa:   Exactly... 5 minutes
Risa:   Exactly... 5 minutes be
Risa:   Exactly... 5 minutes befo
Risa:   Exactly... 5 minutes before
Risa:   Exactly... 5 minutes before.
Otani:
Otani:  I
Otani:  I've
Otani:  I've...
Otani:  I've... lost
Otani:  I've... lost all
Otani:  I've... lost all me
Otani:  I've... lost all memo
Otani:  I've... lost all memories
Otani:  I've... lost all memories of
Otani:  I've... lost all memories of my
Otani:  I've... lost all memories of my yo
Otani:  I've... lost all memories of my you
Otani:  I've... lost all memories of my youth
Otani:  I've... lost all memories of my youth.
Risa:
Risa:   Ok
Risa:   Okay,
Risa:   Okay, se
Risa:   Okay, see
Risa:   Okay, see you
Risa:   Okay, see you later
Risa:   Okay, see you later.
Otani:
Otani:  Right
Otani:  Right.
Otani!
Yeah?
Fight!
That was too loud, you idiot!
It's you, so you'll definitely be fine.
Right. Please, begin.
My future, huh?
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Been here long?
No.
The results will be out in a week.
But for now, Otani is free from the stress of studying.
We haven't been on a date in ages!
What should we do? Where should we go?
Anything is fine. Today I'm making it all up to you.
Making what up?
We couldn't do anything while I was studying,
so today you can call the shots.
Oh? Do you mean it?
Yeah.
Let's see...
Huh?
A-chan!
Mimi?
Mimi-chan...
So you've got the old bag with you too?
Sorry.
What are you doing, dressed up like that?
I'm working.
Working?
It's a shoot for a magazine.
I'm a supermodel, you know.
Ah, I see.
We're doing an outdoor shoot today.
This is the first time I've seen a photo shoot.
Mimi-chan!
Coming.
Aren't you cold?!
Hold this.
Is this okay? You'll get sick.
No, I won't.
I'm a pro.
I'm going to start shooting.
Hold it.
You over there, you're being disgusting.
Amazing! You're amazing, Mimi-sama!
Huh?
I'm moved!
What?
A pro... You really are a pro!
What are you saying?! I already told you I was.
Are these friends of yours, Mimi-chan?
The old lady is a total stranger. This is my boyfriend.
No, I'm not.
What is it?
Say, let's use her in place of the amateur model.
What?
The girl who was going to participate couldn't make it. Let's have her fill in.
Huh?! Model?! Me?!
Her?!
Don't be stupid!!!
It'll be fine. She's got the height, and she has nice style, don't you think?
No way, no way, no way, no way.
It's impossible!
I can't be a model!
Don't say that.
It's absolutely impossible!
You'll be fine.
Ah, let's go with a girly look.
Okay.
Let's go for a really cute look.
Cute? I can't do that!
Don't worry. Leave it to me.
Okay.
For some reason... that person seems really cool.
Who are you?
I'm Koizumi.
In... that...
It's cold! I'm freezing.
Ah, wonderful. Just as I thought.
No! This is embarrassing!
Not at all. You look very cute.
Right?
Uh, yes.
Really? I really look cute?
J-Just a bit.
What was that?
Never mind. Get out of my face!
How mean.
Come on, let's get on standby.
Hurry up and go.
Um, you over there... Could you smile more?
Do it!
Sorry!
I'm begging you.
Sorry.
I'm really not suited to being a model at all...
I'm not suited, but...
I do like watching stuff like this.
Thanks for your hard work. You were really cute!
Thanks...
Don't get the wrong idea. That's all thanks to the skills of the stylist.
I love the clothes you pick for me, Nakahara-san.
Stylist?
You're flattering me, but thank you.
It's true.
It feels great working with you, Nakahara-san.
All right, all right...
Let's go.
I think I found a job I want to do.
Don't tell me you want to become a model?
It's impossible.
You were way too stiff in front of the camera.
I did think you were cute, though...
Really?
No, well... just a bit.
Thanks.
But don't worry.
I want to become a stylist.
A stylist, huh?
Is it a stretch?
I mean, I do like helping people coordinate clothes and stuff...
Idiot. Don't worry about whether you're suited to it or not.
Just decide that you like it and want to do it.
I do.
Then draw on your confidence and do it.
You're strong enough.
Really?
Yeah. Otani-sensei guarantees it.
Otani-sensei!
Otani-sensei sure is a nice guy.
But before that...
there's the question of whether he can actually become a teacher.
Welcome!
Risa.
Haruka! Maity-sensei!
We went for a drive and decided to drop by.
Ah.
Friends of yours?
No, no.
I'm Risa's lover, and this is her man on the side.
What?! Are you serious?!
Don't lie to innocent little kids.
Huh? I've just been lied to?
He's so funny!
Have you been in touch with Otani?
The exam results come out today, right?
No, not yet.
Say, I saw the midget earlier.
Where?
On the bench in front of the train station.
He looked like this.
I called out, "Hey midget!", but he didn't respond.
I bet he failed!
That's unfortunate.
Risa.
Working hard?
Uh, yeah...
The short boy from the kitchen?
Um...
Nice to meet you. I'm Risa's mother.
I'm her father.
Huh?! You're so young!
No, no.
Say, have you talked to Otani?
I've been lied to again, haven't I?
No. Why?
No way!
He definitely failed. He is an idiot, after all.
Laughing at other's misfortunes will bring you bad karma.
If it were me, I'd pass first try.
Risa!
The number you have dialed cannot be reached at this time.
Please leave a message after the tone, then press the pound sign.
Shock.
He failed...
What are you doing? How many times do I have to tell you not to scream?
I'm sorry! I need to leave early!
Huh?
This is an emergency! Please!
What exactly is going on?
Matsubara-san, I'll cover for her.
Kohori-kun!
Go on. Go!
Thank you!
Wait! Koizumi-san!
I'm really sorry! You can dock my pay if you want!
Lord.
I was that age once too.
I won't be lied to anymore...
You'll be fine, Otani.
Even if you failed, there's always next year.
I'll be right here with you, even if you need to study all year.
So... so...
Otani... Geez, where are you?
Don't run away, you idiot!
Wait, Otani! You can't die!
Huh?!
It's not the right thing to do.
Wha? Huh?
Who's going to die, you idiot?!
Take the test again.
Huh?
You can re-take the test next year.
Huh?!
I passed. Why do I have to take it again?
Because...
Listen to me! I'm telling you that the university accepted me!
No way! Why?
What do you mean, "Why"?!
But you were looking depressed on the bench in front of the train station...
Oh, I was so relieved I feel asleep.
You didn't answer your phone.
The battery had run out.
I just woke up, and I was going to go over to your place.
H-Hey...
What? So you were accepted?
You made it.
What's up with you?
Don't "What's up with you" me, you idiot!
Falling asleep, running out of battery...
Do you have any idea how worried I was?
How could I?! You're not supposed to make calls while you're at work!
Well, I did!
Man...
I actually managed to pass, yet you say "No way! Why?"
Haven't you got anything else to say?
I... I was so worried.
Thank goodness.
Koizumi, there's no need to cry like that.
But... I'm happy.
Thanks.
For what?
If it weren't for you, I wouldn't have tried so hard.
So it's thanks to you that I passed.
That's what I was just thinking.
Really?
Ah, you really are a worry.
Otani... congratulations.
Thank you.
Everyone has decided on their future paths.
Soon, we'll all go our separate ways.
No way.
Even at the very end, I'm still running late?!
You're late for your own graduation ceremony.
So are you!
That's true, isn't it?
What are you doing, you idiot?
I'd like to say the same to you!
I'll say it right back!
You don't need to say it back!
It's fine, you idiots.
Good morning.
Honestly, you two...
Do you want me to rewrite your diplomas as "All Hanshin and Kyojin"?
Please don't!
Don't copy me!
Have you forgotten that you're late?
Yeah...
Are you okay? Watch your step.
What's wrong?
The valedictorian has come down with anemia.
That's not good at all.
And so, it's my pleasure to introduce
Those two idiots still aren't here...
our valedictorian speech, to be delivered by...
The ceremony will be over...
...to be delivered by Otani Atsushi and Koizumi Risa.
Whoa, this is long. We have to read the whole thing?
You idiot. The mic is on.
Huh? No way!
Are you an idiot?
Okay, you do it then.
Let's do half and half.
Then you read the first half. I don't wanna start...
What are you saying? Give it here!
Hold on!
Give it to me!
Stop it!
What are you doing?!
Now we can't read it.
This is your fault!
Uh... Quiet, quiet!
These past three years, our teachers have really taken care of us.
It's thanks to them that we've all grown so much.
You don't need to grow any taller, Koizumi.
That's true.
Well, some of us have remained small.
What was that?!
Still, here at Maido Academy, we've made a lot of good memories
and had many wonderful experiences.
But today, we say goodbye.
Some of us are going far away...
Some of us are going to part ways...
Risa...
And... uh...
Hey, why are you crying?
I'm sorry, I can't...
Koizumi...
Right! Let's have three cheers!
What are you doing?!
We can't have the comedy act cry.
You...
Hip-hip...
Hurray!
Hurray! Hurray!
Hurray! Hurray! Hurray!
I'm glad I was able to meet you, Otani.
I love you.
Me too.
I'm glad you're with me, Koizumi.
From now on, we'll always be together.
Bye bye!
See you later!