That day, when I turned 17...
...I was alone with you.
I like you, Otani!
Even now, that scene is burned into my mind;
the blooming fireworks in the midsummer sky...
What's with you? Saying a thing like that out of nowhere...
You're embarrassing me.
That stupid, blank looking face of yours...
Well, you can be a pain sometimes, but I think you're a nice girl too.
No, no, no. That's not what I meant...
No need to be embarrassed.
Once the new semester starts, we All Hanshin-Kyojin need to do our best too.
Hey, how about the two of us auditioning for a comedy show?
17th Maido Festival
Thank you for your patronage
Maido
I'll never forget what happened that day.
17th Maido Festival
Sunk! The Worst Confession in History!!
Maido
17th Maido Festival
Thank you for your patronage
Maido
Forever...
I'll curse you until your great grandchildren are born.
Haunted House
2 Year Class 3
Entrance
Haunted House
2 Year Class 3
Entrance
Haunted House
What's up with you?
Entrance
Haunted House
Remember this, you midget...
Entrance
Haunted House
I'll make it so you never laugh again.
Man, what the heck is your problem?!
You've been cursing me every day since the new semester started.
CURSE
That's right.
I'm going to curse you and make you shrink 1cm every day.
In 156 days, you'll vanish completely.
Hey!
You in the ghost costume and Mr Promoter over there!
Do your jobs properly!
Don't blame me.
This idiot is spouting pointless crap and getting in my way.
"Idiot"?!
An idiot like you shouldn't be calling me an idiot!
Just what is wrong with you? You've been upset since back then.
Are you saying you really don't know what you did?!
What? I gave you my most treasured belonging!
You should show me more gratitude.
Oh. That, I am thankful for. I was so happy I thought I'd die.
Right.
That's not it! I meant after that!
After?
Ahh... Those fireworks sure were pretty.
Gimme that!
Hurry up and find some customers.
What the...?
What the heck is wrong with her?
Why is she so angry?
Well, it's to be expected. Right, darling?
What a cruel guy.
What the hell?! I haven't done anything!
Try searching for your heart!
Do you really think you haven't done anything?!
This is fun!
We have something very fun here today!
I... like you, Otani.
That one little phrase...
...do you know how much effort that took?
And yet... that idiot...
2nd Year  Class 3
Independent Film
Police
What was that?
Ahh! Noo!
This is bad!
Haunted House
Reception
Risa-chan is playing ghost, right?
I'll kill you...
Ah... Chiharu-chan and Suzuki-kun...
Welcome.
Risa-chan...
Aren't you happy...
That sure is nice.
Scorn...
Su... Su... Su... Suzuku-kun...
Nooo~
2nd Year  Class 3
All right everyone, please line up!
I heard class three's haunted house is seriously freaky.
I heard their ghost will chase you to the ends of the earth.
The school festival...
...and that guy...
None of that matters to me anymore.
It's autumn...
Thanks for all your hard work.
Thanks to you, we made a ton this morning!
Here. Drink up.
I did work hard, huh?
We're switching shifts in the afternoon. Want to go look around with Otani-kun?
Why me and Otani?!
At this rate, I... I...
Risa, you failed once and you're already giving up?
What do you  mean "failed"?!
I didn't fail! My confession was perfect!
Otani is the problem.
If only his idiocy could be cured...
Well, I seriously thought about whether I'd be able to do that,
but alas, Otani is too dense for me to get through to.
Hey, who do you think you are?
At this stage it's beyond simple density.
"How about the two of us auditioning for a comedy show?" indeed.
Do it yourself, idiot.
What should we do?
It doesn't matter. I don't care about that guy anymore.
I guess. But the class trip is coming up pretty soon...
What will you do during our free time?
I was gonna hang around with you, Nobu-chan.
But I want to be alone with my darling.
Even though it's a class trip, for my darling and I, it'll be our first trip away together.
The romantic night view of Hakodate...
...or the canal at Otaru... There's so much I want to experience with him.
Of course...
But...
Naturally, Chiharu-chan and Suzuki-kun will want to be alone too.
So basically you'll be left alone with Otani-kun anyway.
Not good.
Otherwise you'll just be all by yourself.
Aww! Not fair!
Ah, there they are.
Koizumi-san, everyone's looking for you.
No one wants to come if you're not playing the ghost.
I see.
Fine. I'll do the afternoon shift too.
Koizumi...
...I know why you're angry.
Sorry.
I did something terrible to you.
The guy you like found out that you were with me on your birthday...
...and got the wrong idea, right?
Wh- What's with this cold atmosphere?!
I'm amazed he came up with such a complicated theory.
I'm so surprised I can't even be sad.
Huh? That's not it? That was wrong too?!
He's been saying things like that for a while now.
What the heck is it, then?!
Fine, fine.
That's exactly what it was.
How's it go again?
The guy I like found out and got the wrong idea.
You're so damn annoying. I know that's not it.
I'm the one that's annoyed, you imbecile!
"Imbecile"?
That's the first time I've heard anyone use that word.
That's the first time I've had to use it on anyone too!
ALL HANSHIN KYOJIN
Don't use weird words like that!
Idiot! You just don't understand because you're so dense!
In this pun the word for 'dense', 'nibui', sounds like "ni V" meaning "2V".
V + V = 2V
What do you make of that?!
You shouldn't make bad impulse jokes, idiot! Twit!
That's the first time I've heard that one too.
They seem to be well matched, huh?
Do you want to step in?
Sure.
Otani...
What?!
The one Risa likes is you, Otani-kun.
Liar!
You guys are just keeping me in the dark in order to make a fool out of me!
Are you listening?
So...
Someone...
Someone bring me something to hit him with! Something that'll really hurt him!!!
Calm down, Risa!
What is she doing?
He thought you were lying. What's wrong with him?!
There. there.
Why would anyone lie about something like that?
There, there.
Risa, you came!
Huh?
Oh. Haruka.
What's with that outfit?
Huh, you didn't come to see me?
Um, well... the haunted house was a huge hit so she's pretty worn out.
Oh? Good timing then!
Take a little rest at our cafe.
Yes, let's do that, Risa.
I made these cookies too. Would you like to try one?
I would, I would!
They're really delicious!
They really are.
Aren't they?
So your class is running this cafe?
No. My club is.
The home ec. club.
I told you that I made club president last time, didn't I?
Oh... Did you say something like that?
The efficiency
of full dentures
?
"The efficiency of full dentures"?
This pun plays on the phrases "sou ieba, kiitakke na" and "sou ireba, kiita", which sound similar.
So you really don't care about me at all.
I didn't say "full dentures"...
Your head is just filled with thoughts of that midget.
N- No!
I'm not thinking about that idiot...
Whatever. You're not thinking about me at all.
Hey, Haruka?
What?
Do you know who I like?
How can you ask me that?! It's that midget, of course!
So, what about it?
Nothing.
President, I brought some customers!
Oh, so you're all here.
How cute!
So you're in the home ec. club too, Seiko-chan?
I'm just a junior member who joined recently.
Oh my, what's going on here? Is a volcano erupting?
Seiko-chan, this is your fault! Why did you bring that midget here?!
But...
How can you have that kind of attitude with a customer?!!
I'm very sorry.
I regret to inform you that our establishment does not serve gentlemen of diminutive stature.
What?!!
How cruel!
Let's go somewhere else, Nobu-chan.
Ah! Hey, do you know who Koizumi likes too?
Of course I know! Why the hell are you asking me?!
W-Who is it?!
Why should I have to verbalize it again?!
Forget it!
I know too, you know.
Huh? Why? What's with this?! What's with this?!!
Risa!
Risa...
Otani's not dense.
He's just never thought that I could like him in that way.
Risa...
Basically, he's never even considered that as a possibility.
He thinks it's impossible.
Yeah. he thinks it's impossible.
That idiot...!
Risa...
He's completely calm because he thinks it's impossible!
That damn midget...
Calm down, Risa, calm down!
Idiot! Shorty! Stupid midget!
I know! Just stop, okay.
Nobu-chan...
Sorry.
I just don't like to see you like this, Risa.
Ah! I found Koizumi-san!
Catch her! Catch her!
Are you happy too?
Are you happy?
Give me your happiness!
Business is booming. What's wrong?
Darling...
Whenever I think about how Risa is feeling, I just can't feel happy.
Yeah.
I sure worked hard today.
Come on, Risa, let's go! It's almost over.
It's time for the outdoor folk dance!
No thanks.
Risa...
There was an extra girl last year, remember?
Since I'm so tall, I end up in the boys line and had to dance with all the girls.
It wasn't fun at all.
We're done with the cleaning.
Darling...
Say, where's Otani-kun?
He went to take out the trash.
I'm fine. Don't mind me.
I just want to be alone with my thoughts.
Such a huge girl falling for such a short guy, of all people....
"All Kyojin" is the tall member of the All Hanshin Kyojin comedy duo..
Otani only think of me as his All Kyojin.
Cheer up.
It may be laughable...
...but I like him.
I... like you, Otani.
What?
Oh, it's just you, Otani.
Don't scare me like that!
What are you doing? And with all the lights off too...
Nothing.
Hey, what's wrong? What happened?
I confessed to the guy I like, but he brushed me off.
Oh... that's no good... I mean... Uh...
Hey, why don't I go and try to tell him for you one more time?
No need to go anywhere.
He's right here.
Geez...
I described the guy I like to you, didn't I?
Uh, yeah...
He's shorter than you, He's in the basketball club, he's an idiot...
And... he's here...
...in this room...
Did you ever even think that the guy might be you?
"Think that"...
Huh? What?
I... I don't get you...
It's fine.
I'm tired of looking at that stupid face of yours.
Don't make that face in front of me again, idiot!
What- What are you doing! That hurts!
You're such an idiot! I don't care anymore!
Try getting a clue, you idiot!
Wait... Koizumi...
Shorter than Koizumi...
In the basketball club...
An idiot like you shouldn't be calling me an idiot!
And an idiot...
I confessed to the guy I like, but he brushed me off.
I... like you, Otani.
You're embarrassing me.
She was brushed off...
The one Risa likes is you, Otani-kun.
Did you ever even think that the guy might be you?
M...Me?
ME?!!
He... He must have realized by now...
What should I do?
Still... even if it's just once...
...I want him to think of me as a girl.
I'm really the one Koizumi likes?
Don't bring that up again on the morning of the class trip!
It's because you're like that that I didn't notice.
Bear Curry
Lovely Complex~ Love Com.
Next: Comeback Impossible! Major Heartbreak!!
Comeback Impossible! Major Heartbreak!!
Be sure to watch!