I said do whatever you like.
It's not like I like Koizumi or anything.
Did I hear that right just now?
I'm getting rejected by the same person twice?
Maity's Magic! The Transformation Patterns of Love?!
Risa!
Ko...Koizumi...
It's not like I like Koizumi or anything.
Koizumi-san, was that a snapping sound I heard just now?
Yes!
Maity-sensei, you were so cool just now-chi.
Ah, thank you.
Koizumi...
Ah, Otani-san. Good work-chi.
But you seemed a bit out of it today-chi.
Don't mind!
Wait, Koizumi. Just now, that was...
Well, I'm going home-chi. See you tomorrow.
Goo...Good bye!
Koizumi!
Y-You got it all wrong!
What have we got all wrong? Let's hear it!
E-Everything's gone bad because that old man stuck his nose in.
A man who blames his problems on others is the worst.
Say, where did Maity-sensei go?
He went after Koizumi-san.
It's not like I like Koizumi or anything.
I knew it.
I knew it all along, even without hearing him say it out loud.
I knew!
Koizumi-san.
Maity-sensei...
What should I do from now on?
Well, I guess there's nothing I can do.
Looking back, I've been giving it everything I've got since last summer.
But I guess it was all pointless.
So this is how it is...
I see. so you were rejected once already.
Yeah. Add that just now makes it twice.
You shouldn't let what Otani-kun said just now bother you too much.
That was just his way of hiding his embarrassment.
Don't be stupid. What could he possibly have to hide or be embarrassed about?
Don't worry. It's clear to me.
Just now I said "I'll take Koizumi-san for myself" as a joke.
And then Otani-kun got angry and replied in that manner.
Why do you think he did that?
Maybe it's because he just doesn't like you, Maity-sensei.
Maybe.
This time, I think I'll give being hated a go.
The truth is, I know how to perform magic.
I can use my magic to bring you happiness, Koizumi-san.
In that moment, I realized.
Maity-sensei...
No... Maity-sama!
Ready? Let's go!
M A I T Y  Love Maity!
Great. Okay!
What's that noise?
Apparently it's a cheer to support Maity-sama.
Right at this very moment, a frail maiden is having an audible breakdown,
all because of one cold man...
No!
You guys...!
It's Maity.
Is Otani-kun there?
I'll be counting on you at practice again today.
If you're not feeling well like last time, just let me know, okay?
I'll go easy on you.
I always give 100%! Just bring it on!
Really? Well, that's good.
I want Koizumi-san to see my good side.
La, la~
Maity-sama.
That wonderful smile of yours.
Maity, Maity.
La, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la~
Shut up!
I can't concentrate with all that noise!
Sorry. Let's cheer for Otani-san too, then.
Okay!
It's not good to blame your problems on others.
Why don't you hurry up and show me that determination of yours?
Koizumi-san did come to cheer us on, after all.
I need a way to show her my good side.
I've decided to start a new life.
Maity-sama will bring me happiness.
I'm going to live my life seeing only Maity-sama.
Just Maity-sama...
Maity-sama...
Maity...sama...
Watch out, Otani!
I borrowed a school bike.
Why don't you get on the back?
I don't need to.
Why don't you quit that disgusting Maity club.
Why?
Never mind why, just quit it.
It's fine. And besides, it's my choice.
What's fine about it? What's with all that anyway?
Are you trying to provoke me?
Of course, you idiot!
Because you're a midget that always speaks without thinking.
Who's the one that speaks without thinking?
Who was it that claimed to be in love, then gave up, then randomly blew me off?
What was that?!
Why should I have to hear this from you?
Anyway, I...
I'm pissed off!
About what?
I told you...
Otani-kun,
I was shocked to see you'd vanished all of a sudden.
Come on. I'll drive you home.
I don't need you to.
I see.
Well then, I'll take Koizumi-san home.
Koizumi just committed to taking me home on this bicycle.
What was that? Didn't you just say you didn't need me to?
Shut up.
Oh? Is that so?
Just so you know, I'm the one Koizumi-san likes.
There's no way she'd fall for someone like you.
Let's go.
Huh? Th-Then...
Get a move on.
What's with you?!
D-Don't just go saying things whenever you feel like it.
Kay.
I don't like you, okay.
I gave up on you.
Yeah.
I really have no idea what Otani's thinking.
Hey!
Riding tandem is prohibited!
Stop right there!
Good morning.
Wh-What's with those smiles you're wearing?
We heard everything from Maity, Risa.
Otani said something great, huh?
What a surprise.
I'm the one that was surprised.
I have no idea what's going on with him.
Now, now.
So what happened when you took him home?
Did he say anything? Did he confess to you?
No. Nothing like that.
What's going on?! But he said...
"I'm the one she likes!"
Right?
Well, I'd like to know too.
Oh, good morning.
Don't sigh when you see someone's face in the morning. It's weird.
Well what do you expect?!
We were busted for riding tandem yesterday, remember?
You were injured! It couldn't be helped.
You should be thanking me!
Thank you.
But still, you...
You...
Otani?
No.
No, no...  No, no... It's me.
He's emotionally unstable, isn't he?
I wonder why...
He's definitely jealous because you're paying so much attention to Maity.
Huh? Otani jealous?
I think so too.
Me too.
Come on, don't be stupid. I just heard him say he didn't like me, not long ago.
But wasn't that because Maity interfered?
I seriously have no idea what's up with Otani!
Otani is... jealous?
But up till now, every time I've gotten my hopes up, I've just had one disappointment after another.
I can't just expect things to work out anymore.
Otani, what are you going to do about club?
I'll just watch you guys practice.
There sure have been a lot of injuries lately. The coach isn't better yet either.
Huh? Otani-senpai is injured?
Yeah, but it's only minor.
Ahh, Seiko-chan.
Koizumi-senpai!
How are you doing?
I'm fine, but Otani-senpai is injured.
Aren't you worried, Koizumi-senpai?
Well, yeah... I guess.
What's with this odd atmosphere?
Did something happen?
Don't say a word about it, Seiko.
Those two are as clueless as baby fawns.
What are you doing, Seiko-chin?
Let's go.
Oh, sorry...
...but something terrible has happened.
Otani-senpai is injured!
You idiot! Klutz! You got yourself injured!
You lookin' for a fight?!
Oh yeah, Risa, I heard.
You're ignoring me?!
Wh-What?
You formed the Maity club, and held some events, right?
Why didn't you tell me?
I like Maity a lot too!
Oh, Really?
Haven't I told you? Maity is my cousin.
Are you serious?!
Yeah. I've liked him ever since I was a kid.
But he was always in Tokyo, so I didn't get to see him much.
That's it! I was wondering why he's so irritating...
What do you mean "irritating"?!
Maity is so much kinder and cooler than this midget that any comparison would be pointless.
Right, Risa?
If you're going after Maity, you have my support.
Do your best, Risa!
Th-Thanks!
Jealous?
Hey, what are you angry about?
Nothing.
Where's your Maity club?
You told me to quit, so I quit.
Besides, don't you need me to chauffeur you to your abode again today, Otani-sama?
I don't.
You said that yesterday too...
But when Maity-sensei showed up, you were all "Take me home!".
And then you went on saying "I'm the one she likes", and other unnecessary stuff.
And in the end you dragged me away by force.
Shut up!
My bad! Sorry!
I'm going to go help pack up.
I'll wait for you by the front gate.
Sure.
No matter how hard I try, I have no idea what's gong on in Otani's head.
But I don't want this weird atmosphere to hang around forever.
Koizumi-san's a nice girl, isn't she?
Right?
You don't need to tell me. I know.
Of course.
Was there something you wanted?
You really are short, huh?
I'm gonna to kill you! I'm gonna to kill you! I'm seriously gonna kill you!
If I were a girl, I'm sure I wouldn't want such a short boyfriend.
But Koizumi-san likes you anyway, huh?
Will you really be okay with it if Koizumi-san goes out with someone else?
Otani!
Well, give Koizumi-san my regards.
You were slow, so I came to get you.
Here. Hop on the back.
I'm fine. I can peddle.
But your foot...
Is your foot really okay?
Yeah.
But the bike's going really slow.
That's because you're heavy.
It's actually because you don't have enough strength.
Scary! Scary! Scary! Scary! Scary! Scary! Scary! Scary!
I'm gonna fall! I'm gonna fall off!
I just want to laugh like an idiot with Otani.
I wonder why things get weird once the issue of liking or disliking comes up?
If I never said that I liked him and just kept going like this...
...we could have stayed a comedy duo forever.
I think that would've been the best.
Hey, Otani...
If you've been frustrated or upset because of me...
...you don't need to worry about it anymore.
Up until now I've said a lot of things that have bothered you, but I won't say any more.
Seriously... for real this time...
I'm really going to stop liking you.
Don't go so fast!
My eyes dried out so much just now that they're getting stuck.
I can't keep them open.
You idiot.
You're heavy.
I can't open my eyes.
That has nothing to do with it.
This time, we really can go back to the way we were.
Otani...
You guys again?
My last basketball match...
Koizumi, are you gonna come to cheer me on?
Yeah. Give it your best.
I'll bring you lemons in soy sauce.
In soy sauce?!
Lovely Complex~ Love Com.
Next: The Fist of Love! Intercept it, A Maiden's Spirit!!
Otani
for  life
The Fist of Love! Intercept it, A Maiden's Spirit!!
Otani fan
Otani fan club
Be sure to watch!