Long ago, demons existed in this world...
Faced with monsters
immune to modern weaponry,
humanity was pushed to
the brink of extinction.
Dear God, please...
Please save us.
Thus, gods appeared.
They were battle deities called Idaten.
They arrived suddenly,
defeating the demons...
Give it a rest.
...and then sealing them away.
These events occurred over 800 years ago.
Grandfather! Why do you all
have to sacrifice yourselves?!
There's no other way to ensure
the seal is effective.
We will travel to the other side,
souls and all, and become part of it.
Rin, you're still young.
Keep living and watch over the seal.
Share your strength with the gods
who have yet to be born.
And if anything happens to the seal,
it's your job to deal with it.
Don't forget that!
No... No!
We're counting on you, Rin.
Goodbye.
No! Grandfather!
The Idaten Deities
Know Only Peace
#1
Peacetime
Wh-What was that sudden gust?
Gosh, that really startled me...
Is it just me, or did it feel more like
something blew by rather than just wind?
Hey, didn't we just pass some humans?
Never you mind.
There's no way they saw us.
Focus more on moving faster, Hayato.
D-Damn it! Get back here!
You hag in a kid's body!
Nine hours for a lap around the earth...
That's much slower than you usually manage.
Are you slacking?
Did you forget the part where you beat
the shit out of me, you senile old bitch?!
What arrogance when you're still half-baked.
Do you think that'll help
you become a proper Idaten?
What exactly is a "proper"
Idaten supposed to be anyway?
How does being fast even matter?
You drag me out here every day,
work me to the bone... And for what?
In the old days, endless hordes
of monsters ran rampant across the land.
We are deities called forth to do battle.
We used our speed to fight, and—
Yeah, yeah, I've heard this story.
But it's been eighty years since
I popped up in this world.
And when were these monsters sealed away?
About 800 years ago.
See? So when's this seal busting open?
The world looks peaceful enough to me.
Where are you going?
To have some fun.
I've hit my training quota for the day.
What's the problem?
Grandfather, it seems like 800
years of peace was too long...
Hey, sorry about the holdup, Ysley.
You're as swift as ever, Hayato.
Not as swift as old Rin, though...
Well, she's a freak of nature.
I'll still outdo her one day.
All you ever do is read those human books.
Would it kill you to train a little?
I'd really rather not. I'd die.
Besides...
I love studying.
And I'm able to learn more than
any human can in their limited lifespan.
Since the world's at peace, what's the
harm in having an Idaten like that?
Hey, I'm not the old bag,
so I've got no problem with it.
Come on. Let's go see what Paula's doing.
Jeez, couldn't you guys be a little quieter?
You scared them all away!
We're not you. We can't run
like dainty princesses.
Did the birds tell you anything interesting?
Come to think of it,
they said there's a bunch of humans
gathering by the glaciers up north.
What the hell are the humans doing there?
How am I supposed to know?
They mentioned giant green birds, too.
But those are probably airplanes.
Sounds like a military transport
for the Zoble Empire.
When you say Zoble...
You mean the weaponized industrial country
whose air and water have gone to shit?
What does their military
want in a glacial region?
No clue.
It'll be faster to go see
than stand around and guess.
It's only 400 kilometers away.
Even you two can make that in 20 minutes.
I guess we should get going.
You're right.
That sure is a lot of humans...
Hayato!
How are things looking?
Hey, you made it.
I dunno what they're after,
but that's a hell of a lot of security.
Whatever they want is probably over there,
but with this many people,
I can't get closer without them noticing.
Then could you check it out, Paula?
Me?
Put this in when you go.
Something the matter, Dr. Obami?
No, I must've imagined it.
How is the thawing proceeding?
It's 98 percent complete! Basically finished.
He'll be ready to move out
as soon as he's awake.
Wh-What is this thing?
One of the demons who left a blazing
trail of carnage 800 years ago,
and with a little elbow grease, he's still
fully capable of destroying the world...
Gyudo-kun the demon beast!
A bottom feeder as far as demons go,
but more than a match for any human military.
What do you think? Is that cool, or what?
And with that power under our control,
Hotaena and Sarabael will be easy targets?
Humans were never a consideration
in the first place.
The question is how the gods
may have changed...
Gods?
Don't you worry about it!
Right...
This old timer's as strange as ever.
And how is he not cold, dressed like that?
So this is one of those demons that
the old bag never shuts up about...
This was the worth the trip!
I wouldn't be so pleased if I were you.
Why not? It's just one leftover small fry.
Well, I'm sure Rin-san could defeat
it in the worst case scenario...
But how does this Dr. Obami
know about 800 years ago?
About us or the name of this demon?
There shouldn't be any humans left
with that kind of knowledge...
Maybe he's been kicking
for 800 years like Granny.
I mean, not that any human's capable of that.
It's true no human is capable of that...
But what if this doctor isn't human?
What if he's a surviving demon
who's been working for eight centuries
toward the revival of demonkind?
Hell, yeah! Free after 800 years!
Hip hip hooray!
Hip hip hooray! Hip hip hooray!
Doctor! Is it safe to be standing here?
Don't you worry. Gyudo-kun is
pretty docile, generally speaking.
As long as you don't provoke him,
he won't attack.
Though that doesn't apply to gods...
Doctor! What is this?!
Could the accelerated thawing
have driven him mad?
Paula!
Enough! Fire at will!
Stop that, you fool!
He'll come after us next!
Damn it... What's gotten into him?
A girl?
Wow!
Huh, I let him have with that kick,
but he seems to be fine.
You can run if you want, y'know.
And that's exactly what I'll do
if I think we can't beat him.
I'm sure of it! They must be Idaten!
This is the perfect opportunity...
A generation of Idaten softened
by the comfort of peacetime...
This should be good.
Let's see what you can manage.
Who are you boys? Where did you come from?!
Your odds are better staying buried
and fighting the cold, pops.
You little...
Who do you think you're talking to?!
Ow! Hey!
Why you...
The hell was that for, asshole?! That hurt!
What the—?!
Uh, behind you!
Hayato!
He's probably dead.
An attack at the speed of sound
that can generate a sonic boom?
That'd be enough to demolish a tank, but...
Um...
It's not enough to hurt Gyudo-kun.
That makes two.
And we're done.
I must say, peace does nothing
for resilience...
What?! Impossible!
His heart was gouged out!
He's not very fast.
If we focus on evasion,
we should easily be able to escape.
It's like he's only attacking
Idaten on instinct.
Lashing out at us, before anything else,
after being thawed out...
That suggests the cognitive
capacity of an insect.
What's going on here?!
Was it some kind of trick? Or is piercing
their hearts not enough to kill them?!
Ysley?
You're awake?
Whoa, you're injured! Are you okay?!
It does hurt pretty badly,
so can you stand on your own?
It only hurts? You're not gonna die?
You'll understand if you ever
get your heart gouged out.
More importantly, this exchange
has made three things clear.
First, that monster is incredibly
tough and powerful,
but it can't compare to us
Idaten in terms of speed.
If we need to flee,
that shouldn't be a problem.
Second...
It seems the good doctor
doesn't know much about us,
considering how surprised he was that
I survived having my heart pierced...
That surprised me, too!
I suppose it would.
To be honest, the first time
I had my heart pulped
and my neck broken,
I thought I was a goner, too...
What's this? An earthquake?
As for the third thing,
that monster is strong.
However...
You think I'm gonna let that slide,
you piece of shit?!
Hope you're ready for payback a millionfold!
Hayato, who has been training
with Rin-san for 80 years,
should have no problem fighting him.
Eat this!
Hey.
You left your body wide open,
you beefy dumbass!
Nice! Get him, Hayato!
He's nothing like the one in glasses.
This doesn't look good...
Okay! On your feet, big boy!
This time, I'm blowing your head clean off—
What? Is he dead?
He is dead...
Immediate death following destructive
organ trauma is a trait of organisms.
Meaning demons are closer
to living creatures than us Idaten...
I wasn't able to retrieve Gyudo-kun,
but I've obtained data that more
than makes up for that loss.
Now, you'll have to excuse
me as I make my exit.
Farewell to you, new generation of Idaten!
That's...
the new high-speed VTOL fighter jet
that can maintain a cruising speed of Mach 2!
Although, that said...
Wh-What... What was that?
Yo.
Yo, what?!
It can't escape Hayato.
All right, Gramps, quit panicking.
Let's land this thing and have a little chat.
Here we go...
S-Stop! Don't do anything drastic!
Wait, humans die from falls, right?
Did I do that wrong?
Hey, Gramps?
You still alive?
Say, Ysley, how long are you
going to study that dead monster?
Huh? Ysley?
The monster's body is gone, too...
Yes, that's right. A dead monster specimen.
Retrieve it as quickly as possible, please.
It's near where we first found it.
I'll send the specific
coordinates in a moment.
Listen, you need to hurry.
Don't let Zoble get it first.
Damn you, boy...
I can't believe you wrecked it!
Do you realize how much of a pain
it is to fix these bodies?!
You doof! Dunce! Dumb-dumb!
Stupid, stupid stupidhead!
So you're a robot, Gramps?
Man, Ysley is gonna have a lot
of fun taking you apart.
Big old stupid stupidhead!
You think this is a game, boy?!
Try this on for size! The device all men
dream about making use of...
Self-Destruct
A self-destruct switch!
And a-boop!
Damn, guess he's a goner...
Well, we're in for a treat.
She sure doesn't look like an old lady...
What are you men thinking?!
You must realize God will not
forgive this kind of pillaging!
When the world was on the
verge of destruction,
God the creator descended from Heaven
and brought salvation to
the world and its people!
What you're doing is blasphemy
in the eyes of our merciful—
God? What's that?
Tissues work better than
blessings for sneezes!
They've got other uses, too...
Well, God, we're gonna help ourselves.
O Lord...
Dear Lord, please...
Please... grant us salvation...
God!