Anything on the fugitive demons?
I apologize, but there have been
no developments whatsoever.
I see. But it's already been two years...
I wouldn't be surprised to
see some major movement soon.
I'm curious about something.
What kind of demon does one turn
into if not fused with a human?
They'd be a giant creature
with no rigidly defined form
whose body is made out of these tentacles.
Cory-kun seems to have a lot
of eyes. What about that?
We all have a lot of eyes,
but most of them look inward after fusing,
so they're hard to confirm.
Pardon me...
I've actually got a visible one in my mouth.
Not that it serves any purpose—
Ysley-dono, do you have a moment?
It's got a thin, transparent eyelid,
like a frog's...
Could you open a bit wider...?
Am I interrupting something?
N-No! That's... It's not what
you're thinking, Barcode.
Sorry. My curiosity got the better of me.
So?
Well, it turns out...
So you couldn't control your child
and have come to us for help?
I see. The exact kind of major
movement he was anticipating...
Piscalat! You've got to help him!
How old is he at this point?
Around two months.
You'll have to give up, then. Demons can't
fuse after hitting the two-week mark.
Demons who fail to fuse during that
two-week period are disposed of, as well.
Did you not know that?
Oh, no...
That aside, Buzz, do you know anything
about the other demons who escaped?
It's like I already told you.
We didn't discuss our plans.
We just fled in different directions...
Wait, something's weird here.
And you don't know anything either, Meliano?
I don't! I've been with Buzz all this time!
Piscalat's already suspicious
of everything I'm saying...
What do I do? Grab Meliano and run?
Looks like we're done with you, in that case.
M-Meliano...
Yeah, I definitely prefer seafood.
You bastard!
You've gotten a lot more powerful.
You might even be more stronger
than Nickel was, Cory.
Well, who can say for sure?
It might've been fun to find out
if Nickel were still alive.
So they hid on a deserted island,
completely isolating themselves...
I see. A bad choice, though.
Fleeing in a way that you sacrifice
all intel regarding the enemy,
in exchange for a greater
sense of security...
It's the same as when
people spend their lives
doing nothing for fear of failure.
The ultimate result...
FAILURE
It couldn't be anything but failure.
The Idaten Deities
Know Only Peace
#10 Demons
Take that... And that! And that! And that!
You okay, Gill-san?
I'm fine... I can keep going...
I really don't think so.
Your legs are pointing the wrong way.
Damn, are you two down for the count already?
This sucks. Granny's still dead on her feet,
and Prontea doesn't show up anymore...
You seem kinda bored, Hayato.
Why not fight me?
Who're you again?
Urgh...
He looks pretty different,
but I think that's Cory-kun.
Oh, Cory...
Come on! Get a grip.
Okay, guess we're doing this.
Cory who, though?
Ysley taught me the best way to use my power!
Oh, the kid with the morphing face.
Now, I'm ready whenever you are!
Nasty!
You two! Fight somewhere with more room!
He's strong! What the hell?
You wanna take this somewhere else
since Paula-chan's mad?
You gotta tell me one thing first.
What training did you do
to get that much stronger so fast?
Training? I didn't do any.
I just matured from a kid to an adult.
A lion is a whole lot stronger after
it grows up, right? Same kinda thing.
It's a bit unfair, isn't it?
Being guaranteed extra strength
just by getting older...
I would think that the Idaten's
limitless capacity for growth
via training isn't much fairer.
Do you think Hayato can beat Cory?
Probably not, right?
That said, I could definitely win if I had
the kind of strength Hayato does.
See, that fleshy armor of
his has a sense of taste.
So, hypothetically,
I could spray him head to toe
with extremely painful hot sauce...
He'd be unable to focus on fighting.
Alternately, I could do what
I did when we fought.
P-Please don't remind me!
But Hayato fights won strength alone,
no strategy or tricks involved.
But just like how a trained martial artist
who's mastered all kinds
of techniques and tactics
pales in comparison to some wild bear...
There's a kind of extreme combat power
that only an idiot is capable of mastering.
That's what I want Hayato to achieve.
Mama...
Okay, here you go.
Now say, "Ah!"
How are they doing, Merku?
There are no signs of fusion side effects,
and they're growing without trouble so far.
Those are your future husbands,
so make sure you show them lots of love.
I still just can't get behind that...
Say, Miku, are we seriously going
to do it with these kids?
Throw the TV on, would you, Merku?
The TV?
As you can see, we've got a
clear shot of the monster!
It's pulling apart this passenger liner
like it's shelling a crab!
That's...
Probably either Buzz or Raki.
One of their kids, anyway.
The ship has been split and two
and is now falling into the sea.
And this is exactly what I was waiting for.
That's quite a splash from the impact...
With demons running amok out in the open,
the Idaten are bound to focus on them.
This will give us a chance to
rendezvous with the Demon Lord,
There were an estimated five thousand
passengers on the ship— Agh!
and start cooking up some plans!
Got a package for you.
Hey, thanks.
A weird robot, a tiny camera,
and a digital camera...
What's the point of this stuff?
First, I take a picture of the robot.
Then I update the blog...
Impulse Purchase~
Something about his weird robot really struck me,
so I ended up buying it~ ^^;
I'm totally in love with how weird it looks, moving around
so smoothly while it talks through it's radio (*^_^*)
Maybe I'm weird too?
Also splurged on a camera (boom)
All these unplanned purchases (sob)
I'm totally feeling batchyrogeh about it~
(Don't ask what that means*)
I wonder if this is a good enough first picture? (omg omg)
I'd love to post it moving around and talking
but I don't know how to take video yet (^.^;
Somebody *teach me* (begging for help lol)
All done!
What?
It's got speakers that
can pick up radio waves,
and it's pretty nimble, too...
Once the camera is installed, the Demon Lord
can use it as a temporary body.
You couldn't do any better than this?
That would've been expensive...
So, how are you going
to tell him that blog is ours?
The internet will do the job
for me in due time.
I anticipated everything up until
this point when we went on the run.
Which is why the letter I gave His Lordship
included a way to get in touch.
Wait, really? Then you can just
call him and let him know.
Not happening.
I'm pretty sure the enemy
is connected to all telecom in Zoble,
and there's no way to tell what phone number
he might be using, wherever he is.
Then what did you tell him?
A nonsense phrase.
feeling batchyrogeh about it~ (Don't ask what that means*)
See this part of the blog post?
What does that mean?
Nothing at all. I made it up.
But that's what makes it special.
Because, at present,
there are no hits for that word.
Search
So the first result for it now,
feeling batchyrogeh
Your search "feeling batchyrogeh" yielded 0 results.
no matter how stupid might seem,
means it's me!
And as blatant a method as this is,
there's no way to catch on to it.
Wait, Miku, once he knows that blog is yours,
are you just going to post the address here?
Wouldn't that be dangerous?
What are you talking about, Merku?
Don't you remember how I found this place?
The information's already out there.
In a way that looks incredibly
natural, no less.
See? Simple enough, right?
And she anticipated all of this
starting when we fled?
That means she knew Zoble would fall,
that we'd be cut off from communications...
She knew she'd use
that internet cafe to plan out
our lives as shut-ins...
She'd thought this through all the way
to getting back in touch with the Demon Lord?
Miku! I can't believe you
ran off on your own!
Hi! That was faster than I expected.
Good to see you again, Your Lordship!
Stow the pleasantries, you fool!
She's so many steps ahead,
it's honestly creepy...
You must have run a search
with the perfect timing, sir.
Oh, Merku? There was actually
a set time to do that, you see.
The idea was to start searching the
second there was any major demon activity.
So that was part of the plan, too, huh?
Things were already afoot, however.
Buzz and Meliano have been taken out.
Huh. So that's their kid, is it?
They were probably begging for help
with the baby and got killed in the process.
Now then, Your Lordship, please tell me
everything you know about what's going on.
Right.
What's with that face, Miku?
I was just thinking about how boned we are.
With Piscalat's crew being brainwashed,
all we've got left is Kuraishi,
Ferlandia, Kroft, and Raki!
We are thoroughly screwed!
Can we just give up?
That's extra disheartening
coming from you, so knock it off!
Right now, I need research facilities.
I can't do a thing in a hovel like this!
I think Kuraishi has got you covered there,
so why not rendezvous with him?
And how would I do that?
Can't you do it the same way you found Miku?
That only works with a preset password.
Maybe a code, then?
The Idaten already have all
the ciphers we used in Zoble.
Any good ideas, Miku?
Sure.
What?!
He's been calling you periodically, right?
What have you been telling him
when he does, Your Lordship?
The names of the surviving demons,
how Piscalat's group was brainwashed,
the fact that Buzz and his girl are dead...
Oh, how was that going to help at all?
Give me one second, please.
Here. The next time he contacts you,
this is what you'll tell him.
What the hell is this?
Who is it?
You'll want to write this down.
I'm going to tell you how we'll rendezvous.
This is in a Zoble 3B cipher...
First...
A Zoble 3B cipher?
It uses a keyword and a password
in order to put together a message.
A kind of Caesar shift.
But what exactly is the plan here?
They'll know all of the
established keywords we use...
The keyword is...
The password of a video game
I liked when I was a kid?
I think it was
"SoSoSeSoUODhiKoNKoSeChiSaUOToKe."
What the hell's that mean?
Well, it's sure something
the Idaten won't figure out.
Damn it!
Only Miku would cook up such a
ridiculous means of communication.
I don't think using
a shared memory for a keyword
is that hard for anyone else to come up with.
The idea itself is simple enough. However...
Still, how does the His Lordship
know that password of yours?
What's with your password?
That part says "Dhik"...
Hey, just like dick!
What is wrong with you?!
Dick! Dick! Your password has a dick in it!
Quit it, Miku!
It's Miku!
I can't believe the stupid
bitch still remembers that!
So damn creepy!
Anyway, here's the message.
The Choru train station, Shimau's Toys,
in the radio section... Okay.
Man, this place is ancient.
Radios, radios... Around here?
Hey, Kuraishi.
We've finally managed to connect.
Good to see you again, Your Lordship.
Thank you very much!
You've met up with Miku's group
already, right? Where are they?
I'm apparently not supposed to tell you.
Wait, we're not going to rendezvous?
What would be the point?
It'd just give the Idaten
a chance to wipe us all out.
Not to mention this whole
brainwashing thing is scary.
They'd only need to catch one
of us to take the rest down.
That being the case,
the only person who needs to know where
to find us all is the Demon Lord.
So we're still going through with this, huh?
Really, Merku? Do you want
to screw Kuraishi instead?
Eep
In that case, it should be okay if you
set up a meeting in some forest,
confirm it's safe, and then breed with him.
Breed...
When you put it that way,
I'm not so sure anymore.
I've never had natto like this before!
Stringy
That'd be helpful since you wouldn't
have to wait for the boys to grow up...
But I don't really see it happening.
That's what she thinks, anyway.
What do you say, Kuraishi?
M-Me and Merku... and Miku?
Look, I don't care if you wanna
fool around with human chicks,
but if you cheat on me with another
demon you're dead, asshole!
Right, g-got it...
Oh, Fer-chan, you're so pure of heart!
Shut the hell up, Miku!
How about a four-way instead,
then? Does that work?
Is it okay if we're all caught up
in the heat of the moment?
Drop dead!
Damn, you haven't changed at all, have you?
Well, whatever. We still need to get
in contact with Raki and Kroft, right?
Do we, though?
Kroft is one thing,
but we don't need Raki, do we?
Foremost, she's stupid.
And considering a single misstep
could get us all killed,
I think we're better off without her.
But if we leave her out there,
she might actually come in handy.
Oh, it moved.
I'm back, Raki. How are you...
You lost a lot of weight while
I was out hunting, I see.
Where's the child?
Just had it.
So into the ocean it goes.
Well, they're just monsters, after all.
Forget about that. Come on, Kroft...
Seven years later
Oh... a whale...
Haven't seen one of those around
here in a hundred years...
But it got eaten, huh?
It's gone already. Must have escaped.
A demon... Was that a demon?
Ow, ow, ow... I surrender! I surrender!
Hell, yeah!
All right! We win again!
We can beat him pretty consistently
now! He's not so tough!
All of a sudden, Gill-san is
able to keep up with Hayato?!
Gill-san's been growing at an abnormal rate.
I'd wager the large amount of humanoid demon
thoughts contributed to her manifestation...
Which is all fine and dandy,
but here's our big problem.
This definitely isn't good.
It's the fourth one, too.
It's safe to assume that pure-blooded
demons are starting to mate.
It's strange, though.
From what Master and Piscalat told us,
they shouldn't be reproducing this quickly.
With humanoid demons, we've got a good idea
of how their reproductive cycles work.
They often abort cases that fail the fusion...
So the real reason I think the
pure-blooded demon population
is exploding is because of their diet.
In the old days, demons starving to death
and cannibalizing each other
was a regular occurrence...
But now, there's life in essentially
every corner of the planet.
We shouldn't assume the pattern sticks
with a much larger food supply around.
I see...
This has turned into a real mess.
And the wanted posters?
All we're getting is bad tips that sound fake...
To be honest, they may have
had the opposite effect.
Hey! Miku!!
Reward for information: 100 million
Huh, so we're fugitives now?
National Wanted List
Miku                     Umeyo              Kuraishi           Ferlandia
What a waste of effort!
I wonder what the big rush is.
Miku-neechan, I'm back. I brought food.
Welcome home, Teta-kun!
What now? Do you want to eat?
Or would you rather play first?
U-Um... I wanna play first.
You're such a needy boy, aren't you?
Do you want to play with me
or Merku-oneechan today?
This lifestyle is so debauched...
A little too debauched!
Nah.
I'm honestly disgusted with
how much I'm enjoying it.
H-Hey, isn't she that fugitive?
The one worth 100 mill?!
Hurry and take a shot!
Make sure you get my good side, okay?
Hello?! Hello?!
Yes, it's the that fugitive on the poster!
Right, she's on walking
down the street in Central!
How does the reward get split now?!
Miku's on Central Road!
Reports are flooding in!
I want that video here! Now!
Come on, you can get a closer shot than that!
Is this really her?
Yes. That voice and appearance
are definitely Miku's.
But what is she after?
Screw this! If I just catch her myself,
that means I get the whole reward!
Sorry, but no touching.
R-Run for it!
Okay, I should probably clear out.