800 years ago
No!
Save me, Grandfather!
There's no need for tears, Rin.
The demons are gone.
That's not it, Grandfather!
I'm frustrated because I'm powerless
and always need to be protected!
I just can't stand it!
Of all the things to cry over...
For now, let us protect you while
you gain experience for yourself.
That's nothing to be ashamed of.
But never forget...
We will be gone one day,
and when new Idaten are born,
it will be you who must protect them.
The Idaten Deities
Know Only Peace
Now then, that about demonstrates
the kind of strength we're dealing with.
Impressions?
#3
Whirlwind
I was hoping they wouldn't
be worth the consideration...
But they're potentially more dangerous
than I initially thought.
What gives, Piscalat-neechan?
Even I could beat those guys.
Damn it, Cory, I told you
not to bring fish in here!
That aside, I agree with him.
Are we running around hiding in human form
because we're scared of these worms?!
It's asinine! We should get to work
on demolishing the world straight away!
Hey, Neput, would you pipe down for a second?
Otherwise I'll kill you.
R-Right, sorry.
Now, I understand where both
of you are coming from.
Let me break this down for all of you.
First, raise your hand if you
think you can defeat these two.
That's almost everyone.
Now how about this brat?
Okay, suppose that there are several
of them as strong as this boy here...
in addition to their master,
who is orders of magnitude stronger?
Nickel and Brandy...
You two are likely the only ones
up to the challenge.
Umeyo, Miku, Barcode...
How do the current demon
and human populations fare numbers-wise?
There are currently 364 demons, with our
human troops numbering 80 million.
The general population stands at 220 million.
The human population
is growing nice and steady!
We've got all the potential
laborers we could need.
The real problem here is the demons.
How are there only 364 after a hundred years?
You're young! Would it kill you
to pump out a few yourself?
Well, this is all secondary. The main issue
is we can no longer simply remain hidden.
They are now aware of our existence.
So should we strike immediately?
Exactly!
Amidst my encounter and self-destruct,
I placed a transmitter on the boy.
A transmitter?
Yes.
It was stuck to Hayato when he
came back from chasing the doctor.
The impact may have damaged it, however,
as the audio signal yielded dead air.
Nevertheless, it pinged
from the same location for a week
until its tracking signal also
abruptly cut off the other day.
I removed its audio hardware
and discreetly placed it on Rin-san,
but I noticed it was gone the other day.
And I'm sure the enemy has, as well.
They'll dispatch someone
to this location in short order.
We have no way of knowing what other
comrades they may have! As such...
we're going to play our strongest card.
I'm positive that whoever they send
will be able to defeat Hayato.
Rin-san won't budge from the sealing ground.
In other words, the enemy
will have to deal with her.
Ysley, Paula. It's time to train.
R-Right!
Well, let's go...
Hey, wait, Ysley!
Doesn't this mean we'll be forcing
Rin-san to fight the enemy by herself?
What if she loses?
Has she, at any point in the last week,
given you the impression that she'd lose?
Well, no, but...
Besides, Paula, if the enemy we're dealing
with has the means to defeat Rin-san...
Then we never stood
a chance in the first place.
Therefore you'll be the one
seeing to this matter,
Nickel.
'Kay!
You nasty, raggedy, dried up,
nasty, dusty, crusty, old bat!
From underground?
A little too predictable, Haya...
Paula?
Over here, Granny!
How's that, you damned fossil?
Well, that's the first hit someone's
landed an attack on me in 200 years.
Now, Ysley, are you all out of tricks?
Damn it all...
If I finally manage to hit her
but she doesn't even feel it,
then I'm seriously out of my league...
Okay, I'm heading down!
What's going on?
Only four of you in all? What a shame!
Wh-Who is this person?
A human? But this feeling...
Oh, she ran!
It's like a giant demon... in human form.
Hey, who the hell are you?
From your outfit, I'm guessing
you're with that old coot.
What exactly does a human
think they're doing—
That's one!
S-Son of a bitch...
What the hell was that for?!
Huh...
Oh, right, I forgot all about this!
That's not enough to kill you.
I guess I get to experiment
and see how much it takes!
Screw you!
Now, how much of a mess do I have to make
of your insides for you to stay dead?
Hey, maybe this'll be easier than I thought.
You're an odd one for a human.
I'll be taking over from here.
I see! You must be the leader.
Hold up, Granny...
Mind your own damn business!
I'm gonna murder this—
Ysley, take Hayato and Paula and get clear.
Right.
Damn...
Please be careful, Rin-san.
That's no human. It's a demon!
What?
You should really pay attention!
With your arms extended so far out...
doesn't that make responding
quickly more difficult?
Sh-She's fast! Fighting at that distance
is out of the question!
In that case...
Gross.
Get smashed!
I-I've had...
about enough!
But now you can't use your hands!
Will your legs be enough to keep...
H-
Huh?!
How'd she recover already?!
Remarkable!
A decent match for Rin-san?
Ysley, why are we stopping here?
Let's get farther away!
No. We have to stay
where Rin-san's can see us.
Any farther away is dangerous.
Four-eyes has got a good
head on his shoulders.
If I take a pot shot at this range
and they peg my position,
they'll flee.
Never thought I'd see anyone put up
a decent fight against Nickel, though...
So having your neck skewered
doesn't kill you, either...
I'm kinda getting sick of this, seriously!
I guess this is why Pi-chan was
worried about fighting you guys.
Hold on. I have one question.
Just what are you, exactly?
I'm not entirely sure what you're asking...
But I'm a demon. Do I look
like a human or something?
Indeed you do.
I saw all manner of demons 800 years ago,
but none of them were intelligent
enough to communicate,
and there were certainly none who looked
as human as you do.
So, normally, demons have the appearance
and intelligence of that monster we saw?
That must mean the doctor is...
We were granted human intelligence and forms!
Surely even you've heard of him, yeah?
Our great Demon Lord and leader,
His Amazingness, Over-M!
I thought as much. Did he pick "Over-M"
because it vaguely sounds like "Obami"?
And did he really need to throw in
the "Demon Lord" title?
There's a palpable lack of thought
in his naming choices.
Wait, when did you put
the transmitter on her?
Earlier.
More importantly, I think I understand
a bit more about who we're dealing with.
I'd wager he's actually a mere human.
A Demon Lord? I doubt it.
He probably just implanted false memories
to make the demons easier to control.
Which is why, if I'm right, the
next thing Rin-san says will be...
Who is that?
Never heard of him.
Well, the specifics may elude me,
but you're not human, right?
And if you're just a demon,
I'll eliminate you right now.
She pulled a sword from her hand?
There's just too much here that I don't get!
A human-made sword shouldn't
even put a scratch on Nickel...
But that thing might be bad news!
Huh?! What is that?!
Where'd she get that sword from?!
It's like my glasses and clothes.
You can change your own clothing
at will, can't you, Paula?
Yeah.
Still, weaponry would have to be
a fundamental part of your lifestyle...
in order to conjure up something like that.
I'd like to see you eliminate me, lady!
I said that, but she's bound
to lop off a few of my arms.
It's a sacrifice I'll have to make.
And in exchange, I'll attack with
my full strength using my tail.
After that, I won't give you
a chance to regenerate!
I'll tear you to shreds in an instant!
It seems you and your so-called Demon Lord
doesn't know a thing about us Idaten.
You thought one of you would be enough?
Because I've never seen
any demon capable of defeating
a fully-trained Idaten solo.
Wh-What...?
I can't move...
It's over, Ysley, Paula. You can come back.
What is this?
Some sort of paralysis or sealing technique?
Induced paralysis? Grandfather
did have a technique like that...
It's beyond me, though.
Don't screw with me! Then what did you do?
Why can't I move my body?!
That's only natural...
Your head's not connected to it.
Eight hundred years ago,
the demon threat was eliminated,
ushering in a long age of peace.
In that peaceful world,
Rin was the last remaining Idaten.
Yet her heart was consumed
by overwhelming fear...
I'm scared! I'm scared! I'm scared!
Why? What is there to fear?
Grandfather's seal is perfect!
The demons should be gone for good!
But what if it's broken?
What if there are surviving demons?
Grandfather and the others are gone!
There's no one left to protect me!
I'm all alone...
And I'm defenseless!
For a long time after that,
Rin spent her days cowering in fear.
As flora spread and fauna populated,
she finally came to realize
that the demons were truly gone.
Thus she began to take action.
This was fifty years after the sealing.
What Rin sought in the peaceful age...
was power.
Overwhelming combat ability.
She had no idea exactly how strong
she would need to become,
but over the course of 350 years,
she thoroughly tempered her body
as if to purge her fears,
growing ever stronger.
In another 200 years' time,
Rin was entirely free of fear.
When Prontea, the first Idaten
born in the age of peace,
completed his training under her...
That was the day Rin finally felt at peace.
And for the first time in
six centuries, she smiled.
Wh-What?
I-Impossible!
What is it, G-Thirteen?
How's the battle shaping up?
Is Nickel struggling?
Piscalat!
It's way worse than that!
Nickel just lost in the blink of an eye!
Right now, we don't stand a chance against—
Did you think I hadn't noticed you?
Shit, shit, shit!
What the hell do we do now?!
S-So, Brandy... you wanna go next?
What— If Nickel got beat that easily,
I won't win, either!
Aren't you always talking about
how much stronger you are?!
I-I realize that, but...
I suppose you could say
that I was just being competitive...
We'll simply have to inform the Demon Lord...
I suspect I'm looking at one the
strongest cards the demons had to play.
Which means, as things currently stand...
Rin-san is unbeatable.
Are you awake, Hayato?
Y-Yeah...
But if they have power like this and
and haven't taken over the world...
then they're just using the Zoble Empire
as a means to stay hidden.
I see. Just like Prontea-san and myself.
Just the two of them, huh?
Intelligent demons, though...
Come to think of it, there was mention of...
Demon Lord Over-M, I think it was?
Didn't Grandfather—
What's all the fuss?
Granny! We need to train right now!
I won't stand for an ass-kicking
from anyone other than y—
Ooh!
You can take a nap until you
finish regenerating, fool.
Paula, where did Ysley skitter off to?
Oh, huh? Now that you
mention it, I don't see him...
Ysley-sama, we've recovered the monster
and are ready to begin our study.
We're already analyzing the sample in detail.
I see.
Keep up the good work.
I'll have another sample for you shortly.
The professor had budgetary—
Money is no object this time around.
Spend however many billions you need.
You can arrange for additional
facilities if need be.
But in exchange, I expect tangible results.
Now, next is...
Hey there, Prontea-san!
Hey, Ysley-kun! It's been ages!
What have you been up to?
Is Paula doing well?
Does she still like to frolic in nature?
By the way, that Idaten theory you proposed
has turned out to be incredible!
I can actually do things
that seem like magic now.
I knew you could, Prontea-san.
I'll be coming to see you soon.
Maybe as soon as today.
So Nickel was taken down
without much struggle...
What shall we do now?