There were four Idaten present
at the scene of the battle,
one of which we had no data on
and was exceptionally strong.
She's also apparently a survivor
from 800 years ago...
From before the demons were wiped out.
I never would've guessed
one of them was still alive.
Is Nickel's transmitter still functioning?
It was surgically implanted.
The audio feed went dead not long
after G-Thirteen was eliminated.
I have to imagine someone noticed
and intentionally disabled it.
You can implant it internally
to keep it hidden,
but you can't expect me to miss
the actual signal coming out of it.
That means they knew all
about the first transmitter
and left it partially functional
in order to gauge our response!
W-Wait, isn't this bad news?
If they attack us now...
B-B-Brandy-san, we're counting on you!
Wh-What are you talking about?!
I telling you I can win, either! No way!
I think I still have a lot
of growing to do, y'know?
Let's keep our expectations
in check, shall we?
Oh, my! Are we all going to be slaughtered?
Oh, I've always wondered what it'd
be like to be on the receiving end...
Throb
Why is this turning you on?!
Rabble, rabble, rabble...
Enough! Would you all shut your traps?!
Hush
Hush...
It's true enough that
we can't win as things stand.
Nevertheless, we can't just
keep our heads down.
If we ignore those three fledglings,
they could grow to become
monsters in their own right.
Piscalat. Neput. Cory.
The three of you will be responsible
for exterminating them!
Use the military to find and track them.
Human troops?
Exactly. They won't attack human soldiers.
We've infiltrated human society
in order to evade them...
We'll have to strike once they
split up and are isolated.
Makes sense.
We use the humans for intelligence,
and when an opportunity
presents itself, we attack.
That's the safest tactic, given that
they're protecting the humans...
I'll kill them all.
If the demons are hiding in a human nation
and there's no way to tell the two apart,
then I'll blow the whole country off the map!
It's impressive that she'd suggest the most
brutal solution without any hesitation...
I bet even the demons would be surprised.
The Idaten Deities
Know Only Peace
#4
Yellow Sparrow
Ysley, tell me where this
Zoble place is right now!
I'm going to wipe it out as soon as possible!
N-N-Now, let's take a second
to calm down here, Rin-san!
We don't know how many demons there are,
or what kinds we're dealing with.
To be on the safe side,
why don't we try bringing in Prontea-san?
Bring in Prontea?
I admit he would be a great help,
but I entrusted him with
monitoring the entire world.
I wouldn't know where
to start looking for him.
Huh? But Prontea-san is—
Right?! So we'll go and search him out!
Could you wait a week before taking action?
What are you talking about, Ysley?
Prontea-san's going to be
in Hotaena like always.
I'll explain later!
A week it is, then. Find Prontea and—
All right, Granny! I'm all healed up!
Let's get this training started already!
I was talking, you fool!
That idiotic pupil of mine...
He was able to land an attack
on Rin-san by himself...
And he managed to budge her?
Come on, you old fart! That all you got?!
Hurry up and bring it on!
What's gotten into him?
I'll have to shut him up the hard way...
He's recovering at an incredible rate, too.
Our bodies are corporealized thought.
It's natural that our state of mind
affects our physiology...
But it seems his loss, and the earnest
hunger for strength that it inspired,
has powered him up a fair bit.
Damn it, why are we watching
some rinky-dink island?
Quit complaining.
Are these three kids really
worth all the trouble?
Check out the one with the pigtails, though.
A little on the young side,
but she's pretty cute!
Hey, that's a nice rack!
Wonder if we're allowed to mess her up...
No one on these boats has noticed me.
They said we're allowed to
if we can pull this off.
They're all human.
But it's only been a half a day,
and now tens of thousands
of troops are encircling the area...
When I was young, the world population
numbered in the thousands.
There are almost too
many humans at this point.
I could try to kill them all,
but some are bound to get away...
It seems waiting for Prontea
is the wise move after all.
General Piscalat! It's that woman again.
All of our naval troops' reports
have been about her, too.
Why is she the only one?
Have they already gone separate ways?
Where does she keeping
appearing from, though?
For them to split up immediately
after the battle with Nickel...
She keeps popping in and
out from seemingly nowhere.
Is this a trap to lure us in?
Or something else?
That's quite the armada.
They responded faster than I thought.
We'll head to Hotaena
by traveling along the seafloor.
Hey, why didn't you just
call Prontea-san over?
Because if I did, he wouldn't show up.
He's got an aversion to Rin-san.
If she goes nuclear on Zoble right now,
it'll be hard to ensure
all the demons are dead.
There'd be no way to verify
that we got them all.
Besides, it's a good idea to make sure
the two remaining superpowers won't start
fighting as soon as Zoble is wiped out.
But if we can clear those obstacles,
Rin-san and Prontea-san
can take care of the rest.
While his general outlook was correct,
at the time, Ysley had no way of knowing
that his assumptions about the demon lord
were fundamentally off-base.
General Piscalat! It's terrible!
We've discovered the body
of Lieutenant G-Thirteen!
Oh, did you?
That's her response?
Wait, something's not right here...
Your Lordship, something
has come to my attention.
What became of Gyudo
the demon beast's body?
Come to think of it,
I wasn't able to retrieve it.
We just recovered G-Thirteen's,
but there's no sign of Nickel's.
I'm just speculating, but what if
the Idaten have already collected Gyudo?
You're suggesting that, wherever they took it,
they took Nickel to the same place?
I would assume they mean to study
us demons in order to learn our secrets.
I see. And since they would
need humans to expedite the study...
That makes our destination
Hotaena, doesn't it?
Goal!
Damn, this dude's tall...
I have to ask, new champ,
what's the secret to your speed?
There's no need for special
customization or hardware.
For me, it all comes down
to racing technique.
I-I see...
Now, do you have any future goals?
I'm actually done with racing.
Huh?
I got a result I'm satisfied with...
which means this experiment
has come to an end.
Hey, you again, Ysley-kun?
What's up?
Paula and I just arrived at the Zeyo Coast.
Oh, Paula's with you?
Okay, I'll be right there!
Huh? He's gone...
Good afternoon, Prontea-san.
It's been so long, Prontea-san!
I really haven't seen you two in a while!
Idaten...
Fire!
How's my magic power, Ysley-kun?
I-It was pretty rude, for one thing.
Was that the full intensity you can manifest?
Well, yeah!
It's hotter than any flamethrower, you'll find.
Although, it looks like you're
not actually here for fun...
Let's hear the details.
The land of liberty, Hotaena.
Formed by the world's business interests,
it is a nation based
on the idea of a free market.
For those with enough money,
it could be considered the most
peaceful place in the world...
Hey, it's the big guy!
Hey, hey! You've gotta tell us more tricks!
I'm a little busy today.
You're really popular, Prontea-san.
That's because he's amazing!
He can find tricks that aren't
even in strategy guides!
He's totally on god mode!
Tricks that aren't in strategy guides?
Does that mean you've
figured out how to do it?
Well, yeah. I don't think it'll be as
helpful as you imagined, though, Ysley-kun.
Hey, Paula. Where the hell are we?
Settle down, Hayato! This is a human town.
What? What am I doing here?!
And where's the old bag?!
Granny! Hey, Granny!
He's an Idaten?
You old bitch!
Is the head in the box, too?
Where the hell are you?!
Well, I'll explain in due time...
What happened to training, huh?!
Who's the granny he keeps yelling about?
Get your wrinkly ass out here, Granny!
That's going to have to wait, too...
So they're somewhere in this country...
How are we supposed to find them, though?
There are too many humans around.
I wouldn't worry. The Demon Lord will
be utilizing the humans to locate them.
All we've gotta do is kill them.
You've really changed
this room up a lot, huh?
That's right. See, all of the footage from
these monitors is linked directly to my mind.
I've been making use of the potential Idaten
abilities that Ysley-kun hypothesized.
This magic works the same way.
I sadly don't have the technical ability
to experiment with my own theories.
I'm grateful for your assistance.
Hey, who gives a shit?!
We're here to drag this guy
back to Granny, right?
Kind of a rude boy, isn't he?
Who's this "Granny," anyway?
Prontea-san, I need you to stay as
calm as possible when I tell you this.
The granny that Hayato
is referring to... is Rin-san.
I saw this coming...
I'm sorry! I'm so sorry, Master!
I'm sorry for playing video
games at home all day!
But they're gone, you know?!
There aren't any demons anywhere!
Wait, what?!
You want me to bring them to you?!
Is this— Are you mad at me?!
You are, aren't you?!
Game over, man! Game over!
She's gonna kill me!
Please don't kill me! I'm begging you!
I'm begging for mercy!
It was all my fault!
I'm so sorry, so just spare my life!
Master!
Sorry, but we're going to have to
give him time to calm down.
And it might be a while...
What's this?
It's apparently footage from
every camera in Hotaena.
Everything from public security
cameras to home video recorders.
Is this that hacking thing?
How does that work for
cameras that aren't online
or aren't connected to anything at all?
No clue. The Demon Lord's
technology is beyond any of us.
So she's not mad? You promise?
Yes. It's okay.
We've been given a week of
free time under the pretense
of looking for you, Prontea-san.
I was hoping to get your help
performing a psychohack
on Zoble's computer network
in order to help ensure our demon hunt's
efficacy by verifying their numbers.
That being said, since the task
itself won't take very long...
How about it, Hayato?
Care to train a bit with Prontea-san?
With this dude who's
scared shitless of the old bag?
Is he actually strong?
You keep talking about her like that...
Doesn't she scare you?
Like she's not gonna kick my ass
as hard if I'm nice to her?
You can be polite or you can talk shit,
either way, that psycho hag
will mess you up all the same.
Ysley-kun, how long has
he been training with Master?
Eighty years.
And his spirit has never once broken.
It's impressive.
Anyway...
I need to start looking into this.
I'll leave things here to you, Prontea-san.
Okay, then, I believe
your name is Hayato-kun?
We'll do your training first
in lieu of an introduction.
You, too, Paula.
If Hayato and Prontea-san go head to head,
the demons are bound to notice.
But they won't be able to beat Prontea-san.
If we can capture one of them alive,
things should proceed smoothly from there.
Emperor Takeshita.
On monitor 2034...
could you rewind four seconds?
Oh, very well.
Did you find them, Barcode?
Sorting large amounts of data
is my specialty, after all.
It's only for a second,
but I imagine you and the emperor
will be able to see him, too.
I see now. Looks like the first one
will be the little boy in glasses.
Piscalat, you're assigned
to deal with this one.
Copy that.
Is this supposed to be your idea of fire?
You think that's gonna work on me?!
What the hell? Ice?
Self-Taught Explosion!
What's your deal?
You some kind of wizard or something?
And is that the best you've got?
Or are you screwing around
with me and holding back?
Either way, it's pissing me off.
I hit you as hard as I could!
It's just that I've only recently learned
these magic-esque attacks, you see.
That was strong enough
to beat Ysley-kun and Paula...
He's as rugged as I'd expect
from training under Master.
I haven't had much opportunity
for practical exercises...
so I appreciate your cooperation!
I already told you that won't cut it!
Damn it, seriously?!
My attacks don't work on him, either?!
Ah, I see.
Looks like it has an additive effect if
I use it in combination with a normal attack.
I understand why Ysley-kun
brought you to see me now.
Your strength is fundamentally
lacking something, Hayato-kun.
Would you like me to teach you about it?
Suppose this creature was alive
and needed to be killed.
How would you do it, Dr. Gachikama?
Well, let's see...
I have to think that poison would be
the simplest approach, like you
originally suggested, Ysley-chan.
And if you were going to poison him,
what would be the theoretical lethal dose?
Let's see... Tetrodotoxin seems to work,
so if we fed him 50,000 pufferfish,
maybe that would kill him.
I'm not sure I'd describe that as "simple."
Even military-grade chemical weapons
would take more than half an hour.
Now, I've compiled the results of
our research for you like usual,
so be sure to take these with you.
Here.
Well, knowing that poison is effective
at all is pretty convenient.
Continue your research, Doctor.
Did you know another doctor named
Obami during your time in Zoble?
Obami?
Oh, you couldn't not know him.
Zoble didn't care about research
unless that old guy was running it!
It was always something to do with
cloning some sort of strange organism
and in vitro fertilization...
I see. So the demons are trying
to find a way to propagate.
Ysley-sama! There's trouble!
Did something happen in this storeroom?
You'll... You'll spare my life now, right?
You might be weaker than the rest,
but you're still an Idaten, I see.
If nothing else, you're quick on your feet.
But you're trapped like a rat in here,
so why don't we have a little fun?
That's Piscalat, one of Zoble's generals!
My ambush might not have worked,
but I have to wonder how long you'll be
able to evade me in a room like this.
Damn, I can't see a thing.
Can he see in the dark?
But as it stands,
I can't risk making a move...
That's a relief.
The next question is if I can avoid
an attack from the entrance...
It'll be a problem if I can't
land an attack from this range.
This might be harder than I anticipated.
What the hell? Did you start pulling
your punches all of a sudden?
Get serious, damn it!
That doesn't hurt at all!
It doesn't?
But I was hitting about as
hard as you do, Hayato-kun.
S-Say what?
That's your weakness. Basically—
Did that smash them all?
Man, how dumb are these guys if we could
find them without the Demon Lord's help?
Well, it looks like the demons managed
to track down all the commotion...
I suppose your lesson will have
to wait until we take care of them.
Okay, Hayato-kun?
Y-Yeah...
Damn, this guy's a freak of nature, too.
What the—?!
Too weak!
It seems magic doesn't
work on demons, either.
This one is strong.
But this one...
Hup!
Paula, Hayato-kun! You two take
that one. Go ahead and beat him.
Ow...
Now that the matchups are decided...
CORY
HAYATO & PAULA
PRONTEA
NEPUT
Let's get it on, shall we?
YSLEY
PISCALAT