The target has entered the department
store at an ordinary but brisk clip.
I'm here. What now?
The outside is under police surveillance,
so could you head inside and capture her?
Okay.
That's weird.
This doesn't seem right, Ysley-kun.
I looked all over, including underground,
but I don't see Miku anywhere.
Either it's some kind of trick,
or she's still hiding somewhere...
More importantly,
why is she doing any of this?
Miku said it herself...
If the enemy starts wondering
how we managed to escape
#11
Smells Fishy
or if there's any point left,
then it's our victory.
That bitch is pretty smart after all.
The Idaten Deities
Know Only Peace
I'm not seeing that creature...
Where could it have gone?
You've got plenty of speed,
but you're still sorely lacking in power!
Paula! Get back!
You demon!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
R-Rin-san...
Cory-kun is on our side,
so you can't... kill... him...
P-Paula-chan!
Hang in there! Are you okay?
Yeah...
I'll probably heal... sooner or later?
I'm not... too sure...
Just hold the wound closed.
She'll heal soon enough.
L-Like this?
What exactly are you? Are you a demon?
Uh... well...
Oh?
Hey, it's the old bat.
What the hell? You finally feeling better?
And Paula's all torn to shit...
What's new, though?
That creature that resembled a demon
and appeared from nowhere...
And this one who's clearly a demon,
yet is concerned about Paula
and supposedly an ally...
Then there's that old man who has
my grandfather and his friends' memories...
What in the world is going on?
What's with all the cops?
Something about a violent
criminal being in there.
I heard some people have been
killed inside, too.
Oh, my. How dreadful.
Looks like the experiment's a success...
Hayato!
What is it, you old hag?
What in the world is going on?
I demand an explanation!
From me?
Say, Cory-kun, could you not squeeze those?
Huh? U-Uh... I, um...
S-Sorry.
It's kind of making my wound hurt.
Wait, that's why?
You wanna know exactly what's going on, huh?
Well, do you remember how we invaded
demon central a while back?
So... Ysley and Prontea are looking
for the demons who escaped,
and that about covers it.
He actually did a decent job?!
Is that all? Then I've got another question.
There was a man in that fight
who had my grandfather's memories.
How is such a thing possible?
What're you talking about?
Not good...
General Piscalat, could you shut down all
of the surveillance equipment on the island
where Hayato and the others are?
If there's any data of this on the computers,
the Demon Lord might find it.
We don't want Rin's past coming to light.
Granted, I doubt he'd
be able to figure that out
that he's an Idaten from inside
the seal just based on that, but...
Miku's a different story. She might only
need the vaguest hint at this point.
This conversation might end up
divulging a ton of intel.
Maybe we should recall Cory-kun soon...
I'll poke around his brain
and erase anything problematic.
Ideally we'd get two...
but one should be enough.
As for the timing, let's see...
Once Cory comes back to Zoble, I think.
From what you've seen,
this Idaten is the only one with
a knack for actual strategy, right?
That's right. I'd say that the rest are
probably of lower than average intelligence.
Which means, bare minimum,
we need to kill him...
Because brute strength will
never help them find me.
Mandate! Mandate!
It oughta be mandatory to support women!
Bring back our support!!!
No Line Work!!
Let's make a living with sex alone!
Who are the real slaves?!
You think we can work regular jobs
after what's happened?!
Rich guys should have to support
a thousand women apiece!
What's going on with that protest?
Miku's reeducation was so effective on them,
they're rejecting any other kind of work.
It's like everything she touches
turns into a problem.
Why don't you head to bed, General Piscalat?
I appreciate your concern,
but after working with you over these
years and never seeing you rest,
the idea of taking time for
myself is a bit disheartening.
Considering our physiological differences,
that's just the way it is.
I'll see you later, okay?
Yes... In that case,
maybe I'll take your suggestion.
He's pretty incredible...
being able to work effectively
without ever resting.
And unlike every other man I've worked with,
we've been alone for long periods of time
and he's never tried anything.
I almost wish he would...
Wait, no, no! What am I thinking?!
Is something wrong, General Piscalat?
Wh-What is it?
Shut up!
I'm just tired!
That's right! It's just exhaustion!
That has to be it!
I'm going to get a few hours' rest.
Interrupt and you're in for an execution!
R-Right... Rest well, ma'am.
Shower Room
Stay out!
I think maybe now's a good time...
If we're not certain what the enemy is up to,
then for now, we'll have to simply get
strong enough to erase any doubts!
Ugh... she's just gone back to her old self.
Do I really need to stick around if the
monster lady is back in the equation?
Hey, speak of the devil.
There's my recall order.
Paula-chan, there's no real
point in me sticking around,
so I'm heading back to Zoble.
Okay. Have a safe trip.
They want me to bring you along.
Didn't say why.
Really? I'll go.
And then hopefully I won't
have to come back...
Is the ventilation busted?
The steam isn't dissipating at all.
I'll have the idiot who's
responsible executed later.
Damn it all...
Th-This is...
It's... the same drug... from before...
B-But who?
Impossible... How?
I should be the only one
who can get in here.
Yeah, these chemicals definitely seem to
have an immediate effect on human brains.
A regular soldier? How?!
Y-You wretch... D-Don't think you'll...
Don't look...
It's nothing to be embarrassed about,
Piscalat, my dear.
I've already seen you in the nude
during your physicals, haven't I?
I-Is that you... Your Lordship?
Mechanical bodies are quite convenient.
They let you impersonate whoever you want.
The demon sightings have all been
in the radius of this area...
And General Piscalat is late.
Maybe she's actually getting
some decent sleep for once.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I was wondering...
where is Prontea-san right now?
Prontea-san? Right now he should be
in the vicinity of the Gaina Coast
looking for Raki and Kroft—
I see. That's all I need to know,
you piece of shit!
Don't worry. You won't die just yet.
I wouldn't be satisfied
letting you off that easy.
Oh, dear... Was it something
I said, Piscalat-chan?
This is bad. Her brainwashing's
been completely undone.
What's wrong? Did you
implant a bomb in my body?
You think you're gonna blow the place?
Or make an emergency call to Prontea?
Too bad you can't do any of that
if the gizmos you hide
in your body won't work.
How? Why aren't they working?
You see, when all electrical devices are
disabled, you can't use any of them.
Pete?
No... the Demon Lord!
I see. So that was you.
You switched faces and clothing at the store—
Correct you are.
And if you had caught on sooner,
this entire plan would have been scrapped.
Looks like the Demon Lord's
pulled it off, Merku.
I see. Does that mean my skin-suit crafting
life has finally come to an end?
Granted...
I thought I was done for when
he peeked in on the changing room.
That implies one of the customers
reacted to Prontea-san searching...
How could he have not noticed that?! Damn it!
I see you're both back.
Let's get to business, Paula.
You're to join Ysley-dono.
Cory, you were recalled
because your job on the island is done.
Why not grab something to eat?
Piscalat-neechan said there wouldn't
be any missions any time soon,
but I'm betting I'll be sent to help
Prontea-san hunt wild demons—
H-Huh? I'm getting... sleepy...
I appreciate how straightforward
you are, Cory.
Being asleep will make
the procedure a lot smoother.
Paula!
Where did she go? There's no sign
of her coming back, either.
Maybe you kicked her ass too hard this time.
I have to agree that Rin-san's training
can be a bit overly severe at times.
Yep.
She seems to have headed
to Zoble along with Cory-san...
I'll ask about it.
You've mastered those human tools, then?!
So you're one of those
egghead types like Ysley?!
What are you talking about?
It's just a cell phone.
But... Huh? No answer.
Is that you, Gill-chan?
It's sure rare for you to dial me up!
Paula?
You're wondering where she is?
I haven't heard, actually.
You're better off asking Ysley-kun...
Wait, what?
We should never lose communications
with the command center!
Ysley-kun! General Piscalat!
Damn it...
They got us!
But who actually attacked and how?
I can't imagine Ysley-kun and General Piscalat
losing if they were together.
And even against an overwhelming opponent,
I think he'd probably abandon her to flee.
I'd say we finished up in the nick of time.
Say, Your Lordship,
what would you have done if undoing
my brainwashing had taken another 30 minutes?
Die, most likely.
Damn it... They really got us!
Should I be more angry or worried?
Who is it?! What do you want?!
What's all this? I couldn't
get in touch with Piscalat or Ysley,
and now I hear command's
been blown up or something.
Neput? What are you doing right now?
Working on the treaties and
other paperwork to establish
diplomatic crap with Hotaena and Sarabael.
That doesn't matter!
I need you here! Right now!
No, I'll come to you!
Has something happened?
Not sure exactly, but it's probably bad news.
That damn Miku is always a pain in the
ass when you get on her bad side.
I'd say this was basically
the best possible result.
We were able to recover Piscalat and Cory,
and the enemy isn't aware of that yet.
So, what shall we do next?
Let's see...
For now... let's not make any moves.
Oh, no, not you! You should
keep moving even harder, okay?
Yeah...
We managed to collect two Idaten samples.
Why not spend some time studying them?
At a nice, leisurely pace.
Now then...
Do you understand what's about to happen?
How about you, missy?
I kind of think we might die...
You think you're gonna die, huh?
That's a cute answer.
But for now, the physical exam comes first.
For example, what's going on in here?!
Oh, torture.
Aw, man, this is probably gonna hurt a lot.
You're gonna learn there are
things worse than death...
She's not screaming?
Ouchie!
Hey, don't kill her.
Quit trying to act tough, you little shit.
Yeowch! Ouch, ouch, ouch...
Why the hell isn't she
screaming her head off?
You're next.
I don't think a regular rectal
probe is gonna cut it for you.
Maybe I'll slice you open
from your intestines to your throat.
His mouth, too. Pull all those teeth out.
No, maybe rip his entire face off
starting with his eyes.
Those're some sweet sounds you're making!
Our flesh returns to the earth,
and our souls to the Lord's side.
Please look over us, who inherit Your works.
That concludes the prayer for the dead,
but was it really all right
to use rites from my country?
It's okay, sister.
The important thing isn't the ritual itself,
but rather nurturing the belief that
the dead should be honored.
I realize I'm not in any position to ask
such a thing from you, but...
No. This is all I can really do, so...
Besides, lately, I've begun to question
what's truly good or evil.
You think we should make
peace with the demons?
I do! If we don't have to fight,
wouldn't we be better if we didn't?
They were worried about my well being.
I'm sure we can come to an
understanding if we just talk.
Okay, let's do that.
But in that case,
we're going to need thousands of human babies
in order to maintain the demon population.
That's...
Out of the question?
In that case, the demons will have
to be prohibited from reproducing
until they die out from natural causes.
What you're suggesting in that case
isn't a compromise.
It's a one-sided death sentence.
The only path to peace
is finding a way for Idaten, humans,
and demons to all be satisfied.
Is everybody here, Your Lordship?
Indeed.
It's a rundown farm, but there
are facilities underground.
We'll conduct the experiments
on the Idaten here, as well.
Oh, I'd love to help with that part.
I've got some pretty personal
grudges against them.
Oh, hey, Cory. It's been a while.
Cory-kun...
According to the deities, in Zoble,
the demons were attempting to mass-produce
humans that they could fuse with demons.
They were just desperate to ensure
the survival of their species...
Maybe I went a little overboard
for the first day. Can't have her dying.
Hurry up and heal.
Then I'll get to cutting again.
We'll change the type of pain
over and over again...
Hey. Sorry, Cory, looks like the
experiments for today are...
What's wrong? You look kind of sick.
Oh, yeah... Probably because my
brainwashing was just undone.
Guess I'm kinda tired, you know?
What is this? The brainwashing was undone...
Maybe I should get some sleep.
It hurts... It hurts...
Well, it's your turn to keep watch.
You got it.
So, based on the information
I got from Piscalat,
the Demon Lord is practically
confirmed to be an Idaten
who came into existence
on the other side of the seal.
I'm so bored...
Could one of you two get pregnant already?
And what am I supposed to do differently?
From a human perspective,
it's easy to condemn what they do.
But as a mere fellow living thing, I can't.
A way for all of our species to coexist...
I can't imagine how to get there,
but... is there really no compromise at all?
Prontea-san just suggested that Ysley-san
and Paula-san have been
captured by the enemy...
S-Say what?!
Who got them?!
I don't know.
Where do we go to save them?!
I don't know...
Are you sure they were taken?
I... don't know.
You fool! It seems like
you don't know anything!
Please stop! If you break the phone,
we really won't be able to learn anything!
Hayato-san! Stop her, please!
Hey, calm down, Granny.
Shut it!
What in the world is happening?
Rin-san, where are you going?
Isn't it obvious?! To find Ysley and Paula!
Does she have any idea
where to start looking?
Ysley!
Paula!
Where are you?!
The Idaten Deities Know Only Peace