The religious state of Sarabael.
All of it citizens are
adherents of the same faith,
resulting in a nation united by belief.
Good afternoon. It's nice to meet you.
We're gods!
Don't be ridiculous! Do you realize
who you're talking to?!
I am the one true holy arbiter of the
Divine Prontea who once blessed this land!
I am the Third Holy Pontiff
of Sarabael, Sagishi Sakushu!
"The Divine Prontea"?
Well, let's just say this
country has its own backstory.
Okay then. Stick to the plan,
all right, Paula?
Right.
How's that?! Behold the righteous wrath
of God's divine punishment!
Another unclean soul has
been delivered unto salv...
Is this good enough? But I can't
fly with them or anything.
#7
Performance
They're just for decoration.
That should suffice.
So, what now?
Just make something up.
That isn't very helpful...
Uh, I came here today to talk with you all.
What are you all doing?!
Don't let her tricks fool you!
Those wings are fake! It's just a costume!
T-Technically, yes...
Taste the lord's might!
This is gonna be rough.
They aren't listening at all—
Huh?
I-I had no idea you were truly a god!
Forgive my rudeness!
The Idaten Deities
Know Only Peace
Now that everyone's gathered around,
I'd like to begin the discussion.
Right-Wing Captain of Sarabael's Military Order
Deban Koredaake
These brats are supposed to be gods?!
If you want to make claims like that,
let's see some damn evidence!
Evidence, eh?
I can't say we have any of that.
All we can really do is demonstrate power
and speed that prove we're not human...
There's also the fact that
firearms don't work on us.
We are the same beings as your Divine Prontea,
however, so you can consider us gods.
Hey, can I ask something?
What exactly is the connection between
Prontea-san and this country?
You're a god, but you don't know that?
I'm afraid this particular god hasn't
been around for very long yet.
Why don't you explain for her, Mr. Pontiff?
O-Of course...
The land of Sarabael is said to predate
a supposed collapse of human civilization.
It's the oldest true holy land
in the world that's still intact.
Our history states that
it was founded by God.
This country was actually
founded by Rin and the old guard
before the demons were sealed away.
Although it was originally
just an underground shelter
they dug up to keep the humans safe in...
However, for centuries,
few chose to stay in this land.
Landslides, drought,
flooding any time there was rain...
It was a very harsh place to survive.
Then God appeared to us...
Over the course of days,
he changed the landscape itself,
tamed the floods,
and transformed this land
into something far more habitable.
Before he returned to the celestial
realm, he spake thus...
You can consider this place
sacred if you want,
but don't let that stop
you from improving on it!
Develop it in whatever way makes
it easier to live in, okay?
See ya around!
Yeah, okay, I get it now.
In other words, he was fixing up
Rin-san's sloppy construction...
And now, a hundred years later,
we are faithfully carrying out the command
passed down by the Divine Prontea.
But he didn't mention anything about
purging or "saving" other countries.
N-Now then, what can we help
you almighty gods with?
Was I speaking out of place to
declare myself your servant?
You're right. Let's get to business.
In the near future, the gods,
including your Divine Prontea,
will destroy the Zoble Empire.
What?!
The Zoble Empire?!
It will be appear to be a military coup d'état
that results in a regime change.
And it will leave Sarabael and Hotaena
as the world's remaining superpowers.
Now, to prevent global chaos,
we're prohibiting war between you two.
After the coup, both Sarabael and Hotaena
will support their efforts to rebuild,
resulting in a tight-knit peace
between all three nations.
With Hotaena?
You expect us to work alongside
a country full of apostates?
What're you yammering about?
This country has been doing whatever
it wants in the name of god.
The only "god" you care about
is the symbol that you
use unite your citizens.
And you use the authority that
affords you to enrich yourselves.
I honestly think that's great!
I mean, what did the first pontiff,
who earnestly worshiped god
and spent all his time praying, accomplish?
Your people were hungry and unprepared
to deal with pandemics and natural disasters,
leading to nothing but decline.
But since you've taken over,
religion has become a business.
And by using your faithful as slave labor,
you've turned this country
into a major player.
In the eyes of human society,
that might make you scum.
But as far as us gods care?
We really don't.
Our only concerns are about excessive
environmental damage and large-scale war.
We don't want you all dying. That's all.
I don't really get the specifics
about all this human stuff,
but try to get along with
Hotaena from now on, okay?
What should we do, Your Holiness?
We'll do as the gods have
decreed and avoid war.
However, everything else
will be business as usual.
We'll continue to sell sham relics
according to improvised revelations,
keep sending psychics and entertainers
to other countries to proselytize,
increase our sway in the political
sphere of other nations,
continue gathering wealth, running
the country, and protecting our citizens.
It is the will of the gods!
"The bodies of Idaten, including their
clothing, constitute a single unit."
"Anything detached from the
main body will vanish over time,"
"so it is impossible to retrieve a sample."
How did you come to these conclusions?
Right here. The blood that was on Gyudo's
nose vanishes without a trace later on.
And Four-Eyes' glasses
also magically get fixed.
I'd say the bodies of Idaten are
less "matter" as we understand it,
and more so a kind of "existence."
It's all in the report for you to peruse,
so is it okay if I focus
on the footage for now?
It's impressive you were able to figure
out all this from so little video.
This could be the key
to finding a weakness in the Idaten.
Someone's thinking positively.
To be honest, we're way past the point
I think that's likely to happen...
Escapees will be shot on sight♥
Zoble Imperial
Maternity Hospital
Hang in there, everyone!
Remember, the state will
take care of your children,
ensuring they turn into the
same kind of soldiers
who got you here in the first place!
You don't have to worry
about parenting at all!
Relax and give birth without a care!
Looks like the girl over there just finished.
Make sure to patch up the tears.
Otherwise it could be a
problem with the next batch.
Okay!
Oh, what's up, Miku?
Oh, I just needed to talk to Umeyo!
It's kind of a hard subject
to broach, but...
You preggers?
No, ma'am.
You long-haired—
He's already able to push me back?
How is he this much stronger after one night?
One second, Hayato-kun!
What exactly did Ysley-kun say to you?
How are you hitting so much harder already?
Something about consciously trying
to get lighter, the way Paula does.
Upping my weight when I land a blow
is supposed to make a difference, too.
Oh, I see...
Lowering your weight for speed
and then increasing it for power
is fundamental stuff!
And you never realized it for yourself?
Ysley-kun! Already done
negotiating with the humans?
Yup. No problems on our end.
Thanks to the lack of delays,
we won't need the whole week.
That's perfect. I don't think we'll
be needing it, either.
Hayato-kun, practice is over for now.
Next is live combat.
We're going to invade the Zoble Empire today.
Four new targets have appeared!
M-M-Master... I-It's been so long...
Prontea! It really has been a while.
Th-That's... another Idaten
we've never seen before!
Is he the one who defeated
Piscalat and the others?
If he's too strong for us to handle,
we'll have to flee, won't we?
Um, Prontea-san, you're looking a bit shaky...
Were you able to shut down the audio
and video transmissions from the ships?
Uh... Sorry. N-No can do.
Then I suppose it's only a matter of
time before this "Miku" figures out
that we're preparing to invade.
Hey, Miku! A new Idaten has appeared!
I want you to analyze him ASAP!
Hmm? Miku?
What? The reports?
Those can wait! I want you
to start looking into this new one—
His Majesty is here, too?!
Wh-Who are you supposed to be?
M-Mistress Miku told me
to sit there and be quiet.
And if I'm found out, to hand over this letter.
Dear Demon Lord...
Looks like you caught me!
Sorry, but after assessing
the current situation,
I've decided we're totally screwed!
That being the case, I'm going to flee
the country! Hope you understand!
I'm also taking Umeyo with me
in the event that we get a chance
to rebuild the demon race later on!
A word of warning:
If the three Idaten on our radar
rendezvous with the powerful one,
or if you confirm the
presence of a new Idaten,
I'm fairly sure what comes next will be...
an immediate invasion.
AN
IMMEDIATE
INVASION
The three of them are on the move!
Th-They're so fast!
What's with these tunnels?
I'd say Kroft was the one who dug them.
Raki most likely put him up to it.
Brandy takes her responsibilities
pretty seriously,
so I doubt she'd run in the face of danger,
but I bet she told her
children to make a break for it.
I'm curious, Umeyo.
How many children are in the process
of fusing inside you right now?
Two of them. Both boys.
That means once they're old enough,
Merku and I can start popping out babies!
Wait... Me, too?!
You want me to have kids with someone
who's just a baby right now?
How perverted are you?!
Don't worry so much!
I'll make sure they know all the ins and outs
by the time they're ready for action!
That's not what I'm objecting to!
I personally like the idea
of taking some naive boy
and getting him addicted to my body.
Are shotas not your thing?
I mean, I like them, but...
I never would've guessed
that was your style!
Chat time is over! It's time to beat it!
The letter I left has been opened!
Something must've happened with the Idaten,
which means it won't be
long before they attack!
Brandy! Miku's flown the coop!
Why would she go on her own?
We could've all fled as a group.
It's obvious enough.
She meant to make herself scarce
while the rest of us are being killed.
I'm sure she judged that to be
her best hope of escape.
Emergency notice! Emergency notice!
All roads leading in and out
of Zoble are being destroyed!
M... M-M-Miku!
The path behind us just got demolished!
Looks like they're eliminating
all methods of egress.
By cutting away at the land,
they can turn Zoble into a giant island
Zoble
and then take their time wiping
out all of the demons inside.
That means, at present, any demon
on the other side of the divide...
has nowhere to run.
Not having to work
with Master is pretty relaxing...
Your Lordship, I also told my
own children to flee beforehand.
If the Idaten realize that the
majority of demons are here,
they'll focus their attention on us.
That will allow my children
and Miku's group to escape.
Come along, darling.
You were bored of playing emperor
for so long anyway, weren't you?
Let's raise some hell,
like we did when we were young.
Fair enough. Let's do it.
There it is, Granny. That's the Zoble Empire.
I see. And that's where the demons are?
But how will they attack? How will they
tell us apart from the humans?
Damn it, Granny, there's only like
300 demons in the whole country.
Is that right?
They're insane...
Not a thought in their heads...
They're attacking with no concern
for human lives, not to mention efficacy.
It's idiotic. One of them is a big old dummy.
But that works out perfectly...
Do you hear me, citizens of Zoble?
Do you hear me, all soldiers?
This is General Piscalat of the Imperial Army.
I realize this is sudden, but the time
has come for a military coup d'état.
P-Piscalat?!
Any civilians and people who
feel like surviving will need
to follow my orders and evacuate.
Your only chance of survival is to head
for the northern coast immediately.
There will be no flights out.
Air travel will make you a priority target.
Damn it, General Piscalat!
What are you doing?!
Time to hunt a traitor!
I'm gonna get a crack at General Piscalat—
Now, to those of you
who failed to flee, prepare to die.
Over and out.
They're taking advantage of Piscalat's voice!
What's going on?!
Please, God, save us!
Come on, you old bag! Quit making a mess!
How are we supposed to keep track like this?
This is such a nuisance!
Prontea says he can tell
the demons from the humans.
Leave the judgment calls to him.
We're only going after the ones
who're obviously not human.
Demon Teen    Salamanda
There you are, Idaten!
I'm the best demon there is
when it comes to digging!
And now Salamanda is gonna dig your....
grave?!
We just gotta kill 300 of those, right?
I see. This may be easier than I thought.
Now, how will this shake out?
Why am I here with you guys?
Because if any additional demons show up,
we won't be able to handle them.
We don't amount to much in a fight, huh?
This is absolute madness!
And I swear, as the fastest demon alive,
I'm gonna get as far away—
That makes ten, I think.
The evacuation seems
to be going smoothly, but...
I still don't see any priority targets.
If you want to protect the humans
so that they can rebuild later,
Operation Planning
you'll want Prime Minister Biarov.
He's human, but talented.
I'm sure he'll be useful.
It'd be ideal to make allies
of Miku and Barcode, as well.
What they look like?
Well, they operate behind the scenes,
so there are no pictures...
Wait, you want us to draw them?
I think Cory's is probably the closest.
It'll have to do, then...
Miku
Barcode
Umeyo
Is this gonna work?
You're not going any farther!
We're gonna show you the
power of the Super Beefy Bros.!
Oh? Hayato's grown a lot stronger.
This is gonna take all damn day.
Let's split up, Granny.
He's still not quite as
reliable as Prontea, but...
I'm pretty sure I pierced that one's heart.
Did I miss?
What's with them?
They're suddenly moving much sharper.
In that case...
Can't move with their heads gone.
They're still not dead,
even after losing their heads?!
Wh-What is this?
She's so solid!
I won't be able to keep her away
with ultra-thin hair alone....
Still, I must remain calm.
She's not the kind of enemy
I can beat head-on.
The important thing is that she
assumes she's fighting weaklings.
I need her to believe that.
The hell is that?
One of General Piscalat's men?
Keep firing! Shoot him down!
You're a demon, aren't you?
Hey, get your ass back here!
I can't take it anymore!
Let us out of here!
Everyone, you mustn't lose hope!
I'm sure God will show us mercy!
Hey, over there!
Man, he managed to get pretty far...
Huh, why didn't those humans run?
Wh-Who are you?
No, it doesn't matter right now.
Please, help us!
Open these cells!
Please! Help!
Cells? Huh, so this is how
you keep humans in place...
Well, you're free, but you might
be safer staying in here for now.
Though it all depends on how
wild the crazy old bitch gets...
J-Just who are you...?
He's a god.
Albeit not the kind of all-powerful
creator deity that you worship.
E-Emperor Takeshita?!
You all have won this war.
But for the sake of the future...
I need to at least manage to kill you.