I wonder if Rin-san's will be okay.
I'm honestly more shocked that the missing
half of her body has already grown back...
Maybe that kind of damage
was too much, even for her.
She's all healed up,
but she's still completely out of it.
G-Grandfather...
The Idaten Deities
Know Only Peace
One week ago, the Zoble Empire
was overthrown by a military coup d'état
organized by Imperial Army General Piscalat
and Imperial Navy Admiral Neput.
Their new weapons allowed them to
easily pierce the nation's defenses
and occupy the capital.
The bodies of Emperor Takeshita and
Empress Brandy were both discovered,
and Prime Minister Biarov has since
announced his intent to work
with the occupying military.
Thus the coup d'état was a success,
giving rise to a reborn Zoble Empire.
I suppose it's a rather
happy ending on the surface, but...
In reality, we've got a mountain of headaches.
I'm honestly not sure where to start.
You've been going through documents for
three days. Are you going to be all right?
Idaten don't really suffer the kind of
deterioration you're worried about.
You, meanwhile, seem to be on the ropes.
Is sleep deprivation an issue for demons?
#9 Shadows
My body is fine, but I think my human
brain is approaching its limit...
Barcode seems to be fine, though.
His demonic powers have a
strong influence on his brain.
I've finished my survey of all the bodies
we've been able to confirm.
Of those, thirteen demons and two babies
remain unaccounted for.
Kuraishi, Buzz, and Raki...
These three are Takeshita
and Brandy's biological children.
Then there's Miku, who fled
after tricking the Demon Lord.
Umeyo, inside of whom two
demon children are gestating.
Merku, Umeyo's assistant.
Ferlandia, who's a skilled
negotiator with humans
and has a degree of influence
in the underworld.
Meliano, who fled via an unauthorized flight.
Kroft, who is skilled at subterranean travel.
We've already confirmed
that he dug tunnels to escape.
Lastly are the Super Beefy Bros.,
who are worthless.
Those four were obliterated
without a trace by Rin-san,
so you can take them off the list.
You have surveillance on your own allies?
You're every bit as thorough
as the Demon Lord himself.
Well, you know...
General Piscalat, of the escaped demons,
do any strike you as a particular threat?
Umeyo has the most combat prowess,
but I'd say Miku poses the greatest
overall threat given the situation.
I thought as much...
An incident came to
my attention three days ago.
It happened at the Frohz estate, home to
a major noble family in the nation of Yakini.
Bodies were found slaughtered in a way
that a human would've struggled to manage.
Raki seems the likely culprit.
The Frohz estate is a beautiful property,
so I suspect she just waltzed in.
She just... waltzed into a pretty house
while on the run
and killed everyone who lives there?
Is she a moron?
The fact that she vanished afterward
suggests she's traveling
with someone who took her away.
Additionally, during the war,
Neput killed a decoy of Kuraishi's.
That felt a little too fragile.
Must be a human decoy.
It would suggest that my and Neput's betrayal
was already discovered by the time they fled.
What is this Kuraishi like?
The simplest way to describe him...
is to say he's like you.
So, you want use of this place for an
indefinite amount of time. Is that right?
That's a tall order,
even for you, Prince Kuraishi.
Aw, don't be like that, Gibaccho!
We're brothers who hit it rich
in weapon smuggling
and human trafficking, aren't we?
Not sure I see a whole lot of reason
to work with you
now that you don't have the
empire backing you up.
Organ harvesting, human experimentation,
anthrax cultivation, and bioweapons...
It's no Zoble, but the plethora
of facilities and secrets here
makes it the perfect place to host
the Demon Lord when he resurfaces.
What the hell are you going on about?
Oh, right, right. You want
a reason to work with me...
You can bet I've got that.
See, if you shut up and do as I say,
then you won't all have to die.
He's used his influence as a prince
of Zoble and his power as a demon
to establish a variety of connections
in the human underworld.
Miku's got no real resources,
so when you consider Kuraishi's
potential havens and pawns to play,
he's a pretty dangerous opponent.
Hey, Miku, are we seriously
going to stay here?
Couldn't we have stopped at an
internet cafe that has a shower?
Sadly, there are no such cafes
that don't check ID
or have security cameras.
Are you willing to risk your
life for a shower, Merku?
You say that, but you've been staring
at social media for the past three days.
What are you looking at?
The blog posts and comments
of pathetic humans,
the times they were posted,
and their leaked personal information.
Their shopping histories, too.
It's enough info for me to figure out
exactly who these people are.
First, I need to find the perfect prey...
Lastly, that nun has apparently woken up.
She's definitely interesting
as a research subject...
But for now, we'll just keep her in
protective custody until things settle down.
Unnershtood...
You should get some rest, too, General.
Right...
G-General Piscalat?!
You awake? Then hand over the bed, please.
If you're hungry,
grab something out of the fridge.
You can throw on whatever
clothes you can find, too.
General Piscalat!
Y-You attacked our homeland,
killing innocent people and kidnapping—
That's enough. Just let me get some sleep.
Zoble's gone now, anyway. No more invasions.
What more do you want?
Apologies? Reparations? Take it up with
Biarov when the reconstruction is finished.
I'd like to help
with the reconstruction, then.
I'll do whatever I can!
Can you drive a 18-wheeler?
Excuse me?
Do you have enough stamina
to clear rubble all day?
Enough medical knowledge
to treat the injured?
Have you ever prepared food
to serve thousands efficiently?
Almost everyone in this country
has military training.
You're just a "good person"
who doesn't know how to do much
other than pray for people.
Which means you're essentially useless.
If you want to be helpful, then shut up and
let me sleep so I can get back to work.
That'll accomplish more than if
you literally worked yourself to death.
I can't argue.
I've been reminded of how
powerless I am so many times...
I want power.
The kind of power I need to protect people.
The thing is, Gill-san,
the training that Idaten go through
to get strong is super painful.
That's fine. I'll endure whatever it takes.
You sound kind of like Hayato, Gill-san.
I wonder if the person who pulls you out
has an influence on your personality...
Drawing out an Idaten involves adding your
own thoughts to a nascent existence
in order to shorten the amount of time
required for manifestation.
As a result, the personality of the drawer
has a certain degree of influence
in shaping the Idaten drawn.
The desire of the nun, who was rocked
to the core by how powerless she felt,
mixed with Hayato's own desire
to create an Idaten who thirsted for strength
that would allow her to defend others.
The thing is...
Hey, you stupid old bitch.
How long are you gonna just sit there?
Let's get training! Now!
Damn it, Granny!
Screw you, then! Like I give a shit!
You can rot up there for all I care!
After learning the Demon Lord's identity,
Rin-san seems to have lost her will to live.
Here's hoping that doesn't
have a negative outcome.
Pete-kun, I've found the emperor's
administrative password,
so could you pull up his files
and organize them for me?
Huh?! O-Oh, right away!
Pass everything you find
along to General Piscalat.
How is he able to figure out
passwords just by sitting there?
How's it going, Prontea-san?
Have you found any clues?
I've been poking around as best I can,
but to be honest, I haven't
found anything interesting.
Nothing like the Demon Lord's research data?
There's a major hitch with that...
It won't display on a monitor
and can't be printed out.
It's some sort of file format that can
only be observed by those
who link their consciousnesses to the computer.
And I have no idea what it actually says.
Prontea's intellect and
academic accomplishments
are on par with an average adult male.
When confronted with
professorial-level research data,
it appears little more than an
incomprehensible collection of symbols.
So I tried writing it out to show
someone like you or Professor Gachikama...
But diving in and out of cyber-consciousness
while jotting a bunch of technobabble
you don't understand is a real pain!
It took me four hours to get this little bit.
Humans... demons...
and human-demon hybrids...
It appears to be three
patterns of genetic code.
Is that of any help?
Since I've got access
to Gyudo and Nickel's bodies,
I would've learned it sooner or later.
See what I mean? A total waste of four hours!
And there are tens of thousands
of files like this.
I'm sorry, but you'll have to give up
on the Demon Lord's research.
If you're dead set on getting access to it,
we'll either need to invent a monitor
that can display brain imagery...
Or you'll have to train until you
can use this kind of ability.
You could always study until
you understand what you're—
Nope!
I think any more would be a waste of time.
I'm going to do something else.
Any suggestions?
We've been able to identify
the nine demons who escaped.
As soon as we confirm their locations,
go ahead and eliminate them.
And in the meantime, I'd like you
to help train the other Idaten.
Go ahead and make them strong enough
to defeat the powerful demons
on the scale of Brandy and Nickel.
Anything less won't be of much use.
That's a pretty big ask.
Are we really going to need that
kind of firepower in the future?
If the demons are able to continue
evading us for long enough...
I get the feeling we will.
She looks good.
Buzz & Meliano
More... More!
Hotel District
Raki & Kroft
Hey, Kroft, I'm hungry.
Right, right.
Could you throw together twelve servings'
worth of food and bring it up?
We're out of money...
Raki, could you grab some more?
Here.
Raki's power is essentially
the same as Brandy's.
She can extend her hair
up to several kilometers,
so thin as to be invisible...
The difference is her
lack of strength when doing it.
But it's great at stealing money
from people without making a scene.
It's one reason I haven't ditched this idiot.
I'm going to need her power on the run.
That's become clear to me
during this time.
Room service!
Ah, it's here.
Kroft, something's wrong!
The person delivering room service...
He doesn't weigh anything!
Excuse me, sir?
I brought the food you ordered...
Sir?
Strange. How'd they figure it out?
The place is surrounded.
There was no sign of anyone
suspicious escaping.
They have to be hiding somewhere.
I don't see them anywhere.
In that case...
Underground!
One of the escaped demons is
supposedly good at subterranean travel!
Bingo!
They've barely got a minute's head start.
Should be easy enough to catch up.
Huh... that's a lot of branches.
I hope you don't think that'll
be enough to get away.
Prontea-san!
I don't think he's going to find them...
Lots of branches
All you have to do to
severely complicate a search
is create a bunch of dummy routes
while covering up the real one.
Correct route
Buried
I couldn't find them...
I figured as much.
Damn... Why didn't I account for a
subterranean escape in the first place?
We'll probably never get
another chance like this.
That was a close one!
But what's going on? How'd they find us?!
We used an alias when we checked in.
They must have looked into it.
We may never be safe
entering a human town again.
Oh, no!
Does that mean we have to stay underground?
Without any beds or baths? No way!
Things are too dangerous to spend long
listening to this moron's bullshit...
But that doesn't change the fact
that I need her power.
Kroft...
I don't want you to die, Raki.
I'll try to comfort you
through the painful parts...
So please, listen to me.
O-Okay...
Damn it. I hate to do this,
but there's no other way.
I guess I'll love you.
Ultimate Ragnage Fantasy Online 14
Doxxing Thread
Gineko Ouka
: she is such trash, everything she says is cringe
for a shit support, always wants to take charge
Mackerel Miso : your stereotypical e-girl
ZobleWoo : I partied with her for a bit and she was total shit~
ZobleWoo :
I partied with her for a bit and she was total shit~
Modest Monk :
but all of her gear was pretty fancy lolol
Obachan : probably pay2win
gross how she has all of that cutesy gear that doesn't look good on her
would look better with the pig tail and the shit hat
Karma :
G lol i lol n lol  e lol k lol o lol O lol u lol k lol a (roflmao)
Anaryu :
I found this psycho's blog lol
Screw you assholes!
You think I'm too slow with heals?
Gineko Ouka     Real Name: Bonnie (Female)
You min/max burnouts
are screwed in the head.
God, they're so irritating and stupid!
I wouldn't party with you if you paid me!
Delivery!
Took them long enough.
Could you be any slower? Damn...
Hi... I'll sign for it right away,
so if you could just leave the—
Hi! Good afternoon. Nice to meet you.
We're just going to intrude
for a couple of years.
This place is a dump! Couldn't you
have found a nicer place, Miku?
It'll be a normal house,
once it's all cleaned up.
This is actually on the nicer side of what
I could find, so stop being so picky.
Hey, can I shower now?
You might want to hold off...
since things are about to get messy.
Good point.
You know, I'm pretty fragile,
so having a human stab me
like that actually does hurt.
The thing is, I happen to love having
a body that can feel pain so easily!
It lets me enjoy the most
brutal pain and intense ecstasy...
A total visceral package!
Female. Lives alone. Recluse.
Easy there. Don't make a fuss.
Does all shopping via delivery.
No friends or relatives, distant or otherwise.
Has assets thanks to her parents,
who died in an accident and left her
enough money to live like a shut-in.
Homeowner. And that's why we picked her.
Her passwords and account information
are all sitting in her inbox.
Uses her birthday for her cash
and credit card PINs.
We won't even need to question her!
It'll be okay.
Merku, go ahead and kill her.
What? Already?
This should be a piece of cake.
All I have to do is play the
role of a nerd on the internet
and keep posting on a blog
that no one is reading...
Then we just nibble through
her savings a bit at a time.
She'll be fully replaced.
If you want to get mad, maybe be mad
about the fact that your hollow joke
of a life didn't amount
to much more than that.
Since the surgery is underway,
allow me to explain the powers of
the devil in white, Merku-chan!
I can deftly control my tentacles
within a one-meter range.
They're not much use in a fight,
but when it comes to surgery,
I can do the work of twelve doctors at once.
You want a prescription? Well, don't ask me!
I've assisted His Demonic Lordship
in addition to Dr. Umeyo,
but I actually know less
than your typical nurse.
I'm just an assistant!
That about covers it!
What do you think, Miku?
I get the feeling your body and face
are both hotter than the original...
but since you'll just be accepting
deliveries, it's probably fine.
I have to put on someone's
skin just to answer the door?
What a pain.
What about everything other
than her face and fingerprints?
Everything else can go.
Umeyo, could you eat it up?
You want me to eat a human? Whole?!
I'd rather not. They don't taste very good.
So, what do we do now, Miku?
For now, it's probably best not
to do much other than live in peace.
I can take that shower, then?
Go on ahead.
And in a few years, we can
rendezvous with the Demon Lord...
So, what the hell are we doing now, Kuraishi?
Good question... I'm honestly not sure.
What the shit is that supposed to mean?!
I can't think of a way
to contact the Demon Lord.
And the Idaten are playing for keeps.
You heard they've got Neput
and Piscalat on their side, right?
Which means they know all about
our emergency contact methods.
I tried passing along a
message using a human, but...
Hey, wanna do a little job for me?
I'll make it worth your while.
Call this number in three hours.
Yeah?
Then you just repeat
what I'm about to tell you...
Who is this?
W-Well, I'm just calling
because someone asked me to...
The guy who hired me is listening
and he wants me to tell you something.
A wise decision. They're listening
in on this as we speak.
Right now, the survivors are Miku,
Merku, Kuraishi, Buzz, Raki,
Umeyo, Meliano, Kroft and
Ferlandia. Those nine.
They already know that, as well.
Seems time's up.
That was certainly fast...
We're with the police.
We'd like to talk to you for a minute.
W-Wait, I didn't do...
Now, now...
We just want to talk.
But that guy asked me...
Those are cops from another country...
and they got here so quickly.
Just how deep in human
society are these guys?
So if we tell His Lordship where we are,
it's as good as telling the Idaten?
The Demon Lord mentioned
demons who managed to escape.
And of those demons, the one most likely
to find a way out of this mess
has to be Miku.
So, how are we going to
contact the Demon Lord?
That's a secret.
If I wanted to, I could get
ahold of him in a few days,
but it'd be best to wait a few years
until they're distracted
with something else...
So, for now, let's just
enjoy the leisurely life.
A few years later, on a deserted island
Buzz & Meliano
You damned—
Buzz, stop it! Please, stop!
Let go of me, Meliano!
That thing is nothing but a monster!
You're wrong!
That's no monster! It's a child!
Our child!
Luce, wait! Don't go! Please, come back!
Don't get any closer!
It'll eat more than your arm next!
It's no use... Without the Demon Lord,
we're totally worthless.
Nothing more than monsters...