Is the idea here that you can
beat me by working together?
Hayato!
I'm gonna chew you up now!
Let go of Hayato!
Hey, whoa! Hold up! T-Time out!
Wait, can you not see in front of you?
Then even I can handle this!
Huh? That worked really well for some reason.
The Idaten Deities
Know Only Peace
Wh-What is wrong with you?!
No one cares!
Now die!
Looks like a pretty even fight.
Now then, my demon friend...
You know how you're not supposed
to look at the sun with a telescope
or a magnifying glass?
I never did understand why they say that.
Damn it, of all the stupid tricks...
The flash grenade seems effective enough.
She's blocked off the exit...
Now then, it's going to take a second
for you to recover your vision...
Why don't we chat a bit?
General Piscalat, you're rather sharp.
The fact that you were thorough enough
to lure a weak opponent like me
into such a vulnerable position...
It's proof of how well you
understand the position you're in.
You appreciate that demonkind has next
to no chance of winning this conflict.
I know what your goal is.
You intend to eliminate the three
of us, who are still immature,
and then figure out a way
to deal with Rin-san
once you've taken appropriate precautions.
Does that about cover it?
Speculate about dream scenarios all you want,
but you're all going to die today.
It's that simple.
I'll concede that my death
isn't out of the question.
But the demons you sent after my friends
will all die by Prontea-san's hand.
That's your full power, then?
I think I've gotten a good grasp of it.
And now it's my turn!
In the end, it seems straight-up punching
them is the most powerful after all.
Rin-san isn't the only Idaten
capable of defeating demons.
I'm afraid you all are the ones
speculating about dream scenarios.
You don't seem to realize that
demons only posed a threat before
because tens of thousands of you
went on a mindless, frenzied rampage.
I don't see your point.
And whatever it is,
you're still going to die.
Idiot. Keep running your mouth.
Are you sure about that?
If I can escape from this room,
I can contact Prontea-san.
That will ensure you die.
I'm sure it would.
Just keep talking, scum.
There's one other thing to consider:
intelligence can sometimes be a hindrance.
He can't be stupid enough
to think that'll work again!
What were you trying to do?
Did you really think that would damage me?
I guess not. All I could manage
was to rip your clothes.
And I have to say, you have a fantastic rack.
Y-Y-Y-You bastard!
This is what I meant. You've restricted
your movements, and for what?
Some asinine notion of embarrassment?
I'm fairly certain that
demonkind's primary objective
is to find a way to propagate the species,
which made me realize something.
Your elevated intelligence has resulted
in an elevated sense of pride,
leading you astray
from the goal of reproduction
and giving rise to shame
at being stripped naked...
Why, you're acting like
a sweet little virgin.
Y-You... You piece of shit!
You're dead! I'm going to kill you!
I swear I'll kill you!
Die!
What?!
I'm afraid that trick won't work.
The first demon that came
after us already tried it.
Nickel...
Damn! What is he up to now?
What is this? He's just standing there?
And not doing anything?
What's his game?
Poison?!
Don't tell me this is why he was rambling
all entire time?! But what's the point?
Poison doesn't have any effect on...
In pure demons,
no substance causes a
physiological reaction this quickly.
But... you all have human brains.
And while the human brain can
resist pain to some degree,
it has no real defense against pleasure.
Yes, this is a highly potent
narcotic and aphrodisiac cocktail.
If you had simply struck without hesitation
at the start, you could've killed me.
But that streak of intelligence you have
inspired fear of the risks involved,
hesitation, and failure.
I guess you're not listening anymore.
The enemy can't overcome Hayato's
defenses and regenerative speed...
But Hayato's own attack power is lacking, eh?
Holy shit, you are gross-looking!
At this rate, Hayato-kun
will win within a few hours.
But that'd be a bit too dull.
Let's try one last experiment.
Paula, can you hear me?
Prontea-san?
Try fighting with that sword.
It's the same as what Master uses,
but I can actually separate mine from my hand.
Think of it as me lending you my strength.
O-Okay!
It's like a character at the start
of the game getting end-game gear!
Paula, give it to Hayato.
Here, Hayato.
Okay...
Wh-Whoa!
Whoa, wait a sec!
I give up! I surrender! So stop!
I'm begging you, just don't kill me—
Winning wouldn't feel right
if I had to use that to do it.
Bring it. Let's settle this the normal way.
So he's truly interested in getting stronger
without using any cheats, huh?
What... are you going to do with me?
Well, since I did manage
to capture you alive,
I have a few things in mind
that I'm bound to enjoy.
Don't! Just... kill me instead.
I get the feeling you're imagining something
lascivious, but you don't need to worry.
Although you might have
preferred that, considering...
I'm a scientist.
The bed I fool around on
is of a surgical nature.
The only insertions I make
involve sharpened scalpels.
Because I came into existence naturally,
I didn't understand my nature
until I met Hayato...
And before that happened, I dissected
an innumerable number of humans
to understand what I was.
I've got a knack for tweaking
the human brain, you see.
#5
Color
First fleet is reporting
no changes with the target!
What do you think, Brandy?
Second fleet is reporting
no changes with the target!
She's not budging, that's for sure.
It's getting boring to watch.
Third fleet is reporting
no changes with the target!
Maybe I'll have Miku take a look instead.
Miku?
Wow, you're still looking feisty after
what those soldiers did to you, huh?
I will not be shamed into submission!
But you people need to stop
this travesty before—
What are you... Stop it!
I can tell you won't submit to violence.
You've got a strong heart,
one that held up in spite
of how you were humiliated for days on end.
But I'm pretty sure that
twice yesterday... you know?
N-No!
You're afraid...
Deathly afraid ever since you
felt the first twinge of pleasure!
You're scared that even though you can
withstand any amount of suffering,
ecstasy might be what finally
gets you to give in!
Stop it! Just stop!
Okay. I will.
I stopped.
"You didn't have to stop right away."
You didn't have to stop right away...
Y-You're wrong!
Miku, could you come with me
to the monitor room?
Brandy? C'mon, things were
finally getting good.
What about her training?
I was going to have her eyes rolling around
in her head from consecutive climaxes!
Well, your plans are canceled,
so get a move on!
'Kay...
You were lucky this time.
Empress Brandy!
Your nation treats people like toys!
You will suffer divine punishment for this!
Have you no fear of God?!
God, huh? That's certainly a scary prospect.
I wasn't expecting them to be on that level.
What exactly do you mean...?
Good question.
If you really think you serve a god,
maybe you should ask one yourself?
Already worn out? Looks like I win, then.
Damn it...
Six hours, huh? That was
faster than I expected.
Okay, got it.
Welcome, Neput, Cory.
The two of you will also
be undergoing Ysley-sama's
wonderful brainwashing surgery to join me!
Surgery
Somebody help!
No! Don't touch me! Not there!
Demon Trio
ELIMINATED
No changes on any of the monitors.
Rookie Seaman
Pete (Human)
The target hasn't moved.
Hi! You called?
Miku, what's your take on this situation?
I'm glad you asked! It's nice to have
a couple of young ones around, y'know?
How old are you, anyway?
Hey!
Let me ask you again.
What do you think, Miku?
I'll need to watch a bit longer.
I'm amazed she can screw around like
that in front of the emperor...
But why did they bring in the trainer?
Okay, they're ready!
A-Are they going to be okay?
Oh, they'll settle down in a bit.
Don't you worry.
So, why don't you tell us all about
the remaining demons and
what they're doing in Zoble?
Right. Very well.
There are 359 of us left.
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
Among them, only three pose an actual threat:
Empress Brandy, Emperor Takeshita,
and Umeyo the midwife.
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
The three of them are stronger
than Neput or myself.
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
Brandy is particularly powerful.
Umeyo is dangerous
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
because she can act as an
incubator for newly born demons.
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
She can also take in humans.
The human and demon then fuse within her,
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
creating a demon with a human's
form and intelligence.
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
The reason Zoble abducts
and reeducates women is to that end.
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
Soldiers were simply allowed
to assault women at first,
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
but that often resulted in women
being killed, or killing themselves,
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
afterward instead of having children.
It thus served no purpose.
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
Now that kind of thing is only
allowed on active battlefields.
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
So much that soldiers who
volunteer for front-line duty
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
typically do so with that in mind...
What's wrong?
Er, I just thought you'd be
a bit disgusted after hearing that...
But you don't seem to mind at all.
I thought the Idaten were
supposed to protect humans.
Well, we're on their side,
but we're also pretty ambivalent when it
comes to their notions of rights and ethics.
Doesn't that mean you've won, though?
Couldn't Long-Locks here
and that monster on the island team up
and just kill everyone in Zoble?
No, destroying Zoble
without some sort of plan
could throw human society into chaos.
A war between Hotaena and
Sarabael would be trouble.
Regardless, I'll manage something
as far as the humans go.
I want the three of you to
act as though you've killed us
and return to Zoble as spies.
I'm afraid that won't work.
Why not? They tell you
to bring back our bodies?
There is that...
But the main issue is that
Miku is still in Zoble.
She's a threat of a different variety.
Hey, could you have the sixth fleet move
15 kilometers back from the coast?
And then have the first through
fifth fleets move closer by two clicks?
Miku, what's that going to accomplish?
Well, it's just a guess at this point, but...
I think she'll unfold her arms
and switch up her stance a little.
What the heck? I don't get it.
Miku? Who's that?
Is she strong?
Not exactly, no.
She's normally in charge of reeducating
the women we capture.
I'm pretty sure even the girl
with the pigtails could beat her.
Me?
I should start at the beginning...
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
The way we fuse humans and demons
involves taking an infant of each species
species and letting them combine.
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
It's mostly hand-off.
This results in wildly varying mutations,
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
both in terms of form and power.
Miku and Barcode were created after
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
an effort was made to remove the
randomness from the process.
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
It was ultimately a failure, though,
as they're severely lacking in
both strength and shapeshifting ability.
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
But it wasn't a total loss.
As a side effect, they have
remarkable nervous systems.
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
Barcode can process
incredible amounts of information,
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
and Miku has an abnormal level
of observational insight.
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
See, she moved just like I thought!
She'll notice that our brains were
tampered with as soon as she sees us.
She did, but I'm not sure why.
And what was the point?
Let's see... How about
we discuss this outside?
See, she'd taken up a position
that would let her wipe out the
entire fleet in an instant.
That's why I had them switch to
a formation that would make it harder
for her to eliminate them where she stood.
But don't you think it's funny, Your Majesty?
No, I'm not sure I understand.
Well, if she doesn't want to kill humans,
couldn't she just run away instead
of getting ready to attack?
Why would she stand her ground like that?
There's only one reason.
There must be something there
that she wants to keep safe.
I wonder what it could be...
How's it going? Any new developments?
Oh, Your Lordship!
Are you feeling any better?
Yes, I just finished repairs a minute ago.
That stupid brat just had to smash my body...
She's protecting something, is she?
I'd wager it's the seal keeping
the old demons at bay.
The old demons are sealed away?
Eight hundred years ago,
all of demonkind were trapped behind a seal.
If we can break that seal,
wouldn't the tables turn instantly?
Is that what you're thinking, Miku?
Not at all!
Y'know, Your Majesty, you're a good study,
but you're not too clever.
There are three problems.
"Problem 1"
Firstly, we don't know how to break the seal.
How do we destroy the island
with Rin defending it?
"Problem 2"
I'm not sure we have the means to do so.
Those are good points...
The return of the wild, unintelligent demons
"Problem 3"
would be as much of an issue for us
as it would the Idaten.
They can't differentiate friend and foe.
True enough.
Knowing the location of the
seal is interesting, however.
I thought we were onto something...
But I guess we'll have to
think of something else.
How do we destroy the island
with Rin defending it?
"Rin"?
How does the Demon Lord
know that Idaten's name?
Who exactly is this doctor...
this Demon Lord Over-M?
The Demon Lord...
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
He was the one who granted us
human forms and intelligence,
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
and he's maneuvering to
take control of society.
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
But because he always contacts
us via android proxies,
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
we're not completely certain
about his identity.
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
Seventy years ago,
when Takeshita and I were kids,
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
the Demon Lord seemed to rule
over Zoble as Emperor Obama.
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
We all had to wonder if
he was actually just a human using
us demons for world conquest.
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
But one day, after he'd reached
an age most humans would be dead at,
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
he abdicated the throne to Takeshita
and faked his own death
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
before returning as a scientist named
Obami that worked in military R&D.
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
He said it was so that he could dedicate
more time to the prosperity of demons,
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
but the job would take over a century.
If he were human, he'd never live that long.
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
There is a possibility
the person controlling
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
the android may have changed at some point,
but even if there's an
organized effort behind it,
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
I can't imagine why humans
would expend multiple lifetimes
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
devoted to helping demonkind.
Hang on a second, maybe he's...
No, it can't be...
If the Demon Lord is a human,
his lifespan doesn't make any sense.
But if he's a pure demon, then where
does his intelligence come from?
Maybe the Demon Lord is an Idaten?
Then why would he oppose the rest of you?
I-I dunno about the details, but...
Oh, you know how we're mostly
made up of human thoughts?
The Demon Lord could be an Idaten who
was created from the thoughts of demons!
That'd explain everything, right?
I seriously doubt that.
If he were an Idaten, he'd have to know
more about us than he does, wouldn't he?
I think we've been at this for too long.
Let's have a little break.
I'm down for that.
Actually, I kind of want to ditch altogether.
Hey, man, let's train some more.
Oh, I actually need to talk with Prontea-san.
Could we address that first?
Yeah, all right.
Hey! What about my training?
No need to worry.
I'll give you something to work on.
First, try to defeat these three.
Okay, then. Now that's my kind of homework.
General Piscalat.
Yes?
About the Demon Lord...
You're exactly right.
That wasn't like you, Ysley-kun.
Why call for a break when we
haven't made any headway?
Did you pick up on something?
Yes. I understand what's going on now.
This doctor that they call the Demon Lord...
I know who he really is.