What is the emperor of Zoble
doing in a place like this?
Why have you come to see
us... or rather, to see him?
For what reason?
And he's... a god?
God...
Damn it. That really hurt, you asshole!
You're a lot stronger than I had thought.
This might be quite the workout
for an old timer like me.
Go ahead. Come at me again. Or would you
rather run crying to your friend?
Nobody said anything about
running, you piece of shit!
The Idaten Deities
Know Only Peace
This is so irritating...
I don't think they'll be
coming back this time.
Did she do all that by swinging a sword?!
What the hell?! How big of a
monster can one person be?!
Still, I knew from the beginning
that I couldn't win...
Let's see how much time of yours I can waste.
Damn it. What are these blasted strings?!
Looking a bit more closely,
the strings are attached to them...
Maybe they're all being controlled
by a main body, somewhere else?
That's right! What you've been
fighting are merely my marionettes!
You have to defeat me if you
want to end this battle!
Then you're the one behind this!
My face! Ow, my face!
You fell right for that one!
I think I'll call it the
Netted Face Shredder!
I've had enough of this—
What the?!
My arm just flew off!
She is... incredibly good
at falling for traps.
Could I...
actually win this, if I play my cards right?
Another day, another search for
baldy Barcode, the giant old lady,
and the pigtailed bondage gal.
Everything that Prontea sees is
transmitted, via electronic signal,
to his PC at home, which is then
displayed for General Piscalat.
No. No. No.
No.
No. No. No. No.
Is it me, or are you treating
this like an assembly line worker
No. No.
who's looking for faulty products?
Pipe down.
Wait, how many people resembling
Miku have you seen?
Only the one.
Miku
I doubt there's a lot of people
with that kind of fashion sense.
Exactly. So, how do you explain her?
It's a bit too exact to
just be a coincidence.
A decoy?
Yeah. The question is, why?
Okay, I'll go have a chat with her.
I need to borrow you for a sec.
Excuse me?
What is this?! What is this?!
Stop screaming!
If you're human, you won't be harmed,
so simmer down a little!
We need to get out of here!
No. I...
I'm going to bear witness to this.
Come on, pops, you're not gonna sprout
tentacles or shapeshift or anything?
He regenerates too fast.
The longer this goes on,
the more of a disadvantage for me.
#8 Idaten
I can't do that.
I'm just good in a straight-up fight.
Which I imagine suits you perfectly.
No tricks or gimmicks involved.
True enough.
Let's do this!
I'd have no chance if he
capitalized on his speed
and healing to draw the battle out...
What a simpleton.
You didn't need to come here.
Your side would've won the war, either way.
Screw that. You expect me to hide
behind Granny my whole life?
By the way, you sure you don't
wanna pull that arm out, pops?!
Shit, this actually hurts really bad.
You take a wound like that,
and it only hurts?
You're not done yet, are you?
No. Come at me.
I think this is as far as I go...
Hey, what's wrong? You dead?
Why don't you try and get me again?
I came out here half ready to die,
but I think I might actually pull this off.
Damn you...
Your roundabout way of fighting is
starting to seriously tick me off!
Wait, what?! What the hell?!
How did she regenerate so quickly?!
What are you trying to do by
getting wound up yourself?
You can't even use that sword, now!
Really? Then maybe I'll get
a little more wound up!
Th-This is bad! I have to untangle my hair and—
That should be all of the decoys,
along with the real body.
And now I'll cut through it all at once!
Master is really going wild out there.
You seem to be the only one left.
Are you the real body?
Looks like you're done...
Then I win.
Good grief... he actually ran
off, without finishing me.
It seems he only cares about
whether he wins or not.
I'd recommend preparing
a nuclear missile launch.
Although even if it's effective,
we'd still end up dying in the process...
Your Lordship, I also told my
own children to flee beforehand.
Not yet...
It's not really over yet.
What do you think you're doing?
Isn't it obvious?!
Your wounds need to be
treated, or you'll die!
You've really taken the whole
"good person" thing to heart, haven't you?
There's no point, though.
I weigh over 500 kg.
Ow...
Leave me and get out of here.
Dying after being flashed by
a young woman won't be so bad.
Please, stop joking around!
That's a good reaction.
You know, after 20 years,
my wife still insists we turn the
lights out when we go to bed.
Women with some sense of
modesty really are the best.
I've never appreciated
the way Miku does things.
Emperor Takeshita...
You were fighting in a way to avoid the
prisoners being hurt in the crossfire.
You could've taken us as hostages...
Even now, regardless of what you're saying,
you're trying to make sure I get to safety.
To me...
You don't seem like a bad person.
Damn it... I'm not healing fast enough.
What the hell's that?
Emperor Takeshita!
One last word of warning...
I'm sure you've realized this,
but we're not human.
Which means there's no hope
for peace between our peoples.
Pray all you want, but the human hunts
will resume again, sooner or later.
If you don't want to be caught
again, flee to Hotaena.
Your life's short enough, you should
be able to live it in peace.
What are you saying?
Even if you're not human, your concern
for others shows we can coexist...
I am so powerless.
When I was attacked...
When I was taken away, and locked up.
I did nothing myself, I only prayed...
Even though a god came to save us,
and was hurt in the process!
She has the wrong idea, there.
But I can't even carry
the wounded to safety...
Prayer will accomplish
nothing. I want power...
The power to protect people,
with my own hands.
If only I had power like that god...
There are three criteria
for an Idaten manifesting:
A large volume of thoughts, a long period
of time, and a desire for salvation.
Here in the Zoble Empire,
all three criteria have been met.
And the appearance, sex, name,
and personality of an Idaten...
will be based off the most
potent source of thoughts,
at the moment of their manifestation.
What the hell are you doing here?
Um, are you okay? You seem to be hurt.
Is that a joke?!
You saw the whole damn thing!
I don't know what you mean! You've got
the wrong person! I didn't see anything!
Shit... my body...
What was that?!
This speed... is she...
I want answers before I kill you.
Where is this Demon Lord, Over-M?
Or is it you?
Demon Lord Over-M? How should I know?
You're eight hundred years old, and you
expect me to know something you don't?
I might not know him, but he
brings something to mind...
His naming sense reminds me a
great deal of my Grandfather...
He'd call one demon Super H
because it was super hard!
Or another demon who's weak, cow-like,
and preyed upon the others as food,
Gyudon-kun!
This seems to be a low-level demon,
the kind that would be used for food...
And since he's treated like a disposable
source of food, like a beef bowl,
why don't we call him Gyudo-kun?
Uh... I don't see why not.
Could it really be a coincidence?
Now, this is a fascinating subject. Would
you mind letting me join the discussion?
Who are you?!
Your Lord—
I should keep quiet, for now.
Rin, watching you fight stirred some
memories the origins of which I am unsure of.
I just had to speak to you in person.
How do you know my name—
Is that sword the same kind that Sukis used?
Someone who's as awkward as you,
on top of running from fights,
couldn't produce one of these!
If you're dead set on it, though,
swing this one around every day.
Sukis-san! Stop making fun of me!
One day, I know I'll...
How do you know that?
I remember you being a frail crybaby,
for some reason, as well.
Grandfather... everyone...
Since you've been gone, I've... I've...
Who are you?! How do you know these things?!
A good question. I have no clue, myself.
But I keep remembering more and more...
You would always flee from the demons,
but you hated being alone even more,
so you would insist on heading into battle...
Don't leave me!
I'm going with you!
How does he know this?!
She's stopped moving? She's wide open, too.
During the battle, I came up
with a way to beat her.
But I'll only get one shot at it.
Like I said, I have no idea
where Miku-sama went after that!
What do you think?
There's only one thing that makes sense.
She fled independently, to save her own skin.
There'd be no point in interrogating the
other demons even if we captured them.
So, you're saying...
She managed to escape.
Well, that's unfortunate. I can see now
why General Piscalat was so wary of her.
An excellent strategic choice.
I've got Biarov and Barcode.
G-General Neput... why would you do this?
Put a sock in it!
You're gonna go through the same thing,
so you'll know exactly why, soon enough.
I see. In that case,
hand Barcode over to Prontea-san.
As for prime minister Biarov,
give him a brief explanation
and then see to it that he gets to safety.
Copy that.
What exactly is the meaning of this, Neput?
What do you intend on doing with me?!
Once this is over, you're gonna rebuild
the country for the sake of it's people,
and the whole world.
Hayato's headed this way, too.
Do you think something happened?
Hey, sorry about the delay.
Here's your Barcode-san.
It looks like Hayato is headed this way, too...
Do you have any idea what happened?
Nope. I have a hard time
imagining him coming back,
even if he was on the verge of dying...
Where's he at?
Still in this area.
That's a bit slow...
Come on. Can't you go a little faster?
I'm sorry, no!
I've never run on water before.
What the—?!
It's fine. She's on our side.
Oh, I see! A new Idaten!
An Idaten?
True enough. Zoble did meet all the
criteria for one manifesting...
I've got surgery to perform.
Paula, take care of things here.
Yeah, got it!
Hayato, you look like you
had quite a struggle.
Were you up against Umeyo? Or the Emperor?
The Emperor, I think.
Did you lose?
Man, shut up. I beat him.
I was gonna head back as soon
as I handed her off to you guys.
That works out nicely!
So, what's your name, new girl?
Uh... Gill. It's Gill!
Nice to meet you, Gill. I'm Prontea.
Now, our hands are kind
of full with this war...
Once things calm down a bit,
we'll have a proper chat.
I hope the others were able to escape...
Hey!
Wh-Who are you?!
When did you get behind me?!
I kind of wanted to ask that.
Can you warp, or something?
Huh?
Wait... you are Gill, right?
Uh, yes. My name is Gilltina.
I usually answer to Gill, though...
How do you know my name?
A lookalike? And a human?
The resemblance is too strong
for it to be a coincidence...
Excuse me, but are you a god—
I see. You must've run into Hayato-kun.
In that case, yes, I'm also a god.
And if you're an ordinary human,
that poses some interesting questions.
How could you?
You'd provide a new data sample
regarding the manifestation of Idaten.
How could you do that?!
That's a demon. If I hadn't
killed him, you would've died.
But... still...
To end a life so casually...!
Then would you still criticize
me if I were weaker,
and fought a more desperate
battle, but still won?
What exactly would I need
to do to satisfy you, then?
I don't know!
I might have died if you hadn't killed him...
But... taking an enemy's
life so one-sidedly...
I just can't bear the sight of it!
She's an interesting human, but her
personality is pretty intensely troublesome.
So, what should I do?
I'm sure that with the war,
there are many who were unable
to escape, due to injuries...
But I'm unable to help them by myself.
Please, god, grant me your—
Better to have her sleep
until everything's over.
I doubt any style of warfare
would satisfy your conscience.
Ignorance is bliss.
His memories are patchy... there's
not much of a resemblance, either.
But he knows things only
Grandfather could know...
And there are little
habits that are the same.
Is that you, Grandfather?!
As powerful as your attacks are,
your defense is terrible!
It's so bad that even using a little
of your own strength against you
makes a limb fly off!
You can't even withstand the
impact of your own attacks!
Now, have a taste of one
of those attacks, and die!
That was way stronger than I expected...
I accidentally blew the Demon Lord away.
Well, he's a robot, so he'll
probably be fine... right?
But I need to strike again...
need to get rid of her or—
Oh, Grandfather...
I've missed you... for so long...
Could we be... together again?
Master?
Six hours after Takeshita
and Brandy were defeated,
Piscalat and Cory joined the assault.
Hayato would return to the front lines,
and Barcode would take over
operations from Piscalat.
Barcode was able to locate
the remaining demons,
which Prontea and Hayato then eliminated.
The war was, effectively, over.
Looks like we're starting
over from scratch, huh?