There exists a model of the seal Rin guards,
created at 1/100th scale...
You could say it's a replica seal.
What does it contain, Prontea-san?
There are two thousand
cockroaches trapped inside.
Huh?
Making it a very dreadful seal indeed.
Okay, then...
So, is it possible for a third party
to remove the seal?
This part here with the flag acts like
an antennae that maintains the sealing.
Destroy this and what's
inside comes spilling out.
Does it?
Rin-san must think so too,
which explains why she's spent
eight centuries guarding the seal.
And yet...
Hey, wait a sec! You're gonna
get roaches everywhere!
Here's what actually happens.
They're all dead?
The Idaten Deities
Know Only Peace
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
The exact cause of death is starvation.
This isn't like cryogenics, where they'd be
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
preserved in a near-death state.
It's just the same as how
roaches die in a few days
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
if left stuck inside a trap.
The same applies to demons.
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
They wouldn't last a year.
They've all been dead for the last 799 years.
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
Frankly, the previous Idaten
threw their lives away.
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
If they'd maintained the seal
in shifts over a year,
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
that would've done it.
But that never occurred to Rin-san
or the other Idaten.
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
Well, I don't particularly see the problem.
This means that breaking the seal
won't give the demons any advantage.
On the contrary, that mistake
gave rise to the Demon Lord.
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
Thinking about it now,
that doctor defies logic.
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
How in the world does he have
a machine that can mimic
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
human expression and body language perfectly?
Much less an interface
complex enough for all that?
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
Are things like perspiration and blinking
synchronized to his own body?
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
That's not possible with current tech.
There's only one method
I can think of that could
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
pilot such an elaborate device.
The very same one you use, Prontea-san...
Thought control.
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
Wait, what are you saying, Ysley-kun?
That the Demon Lord is an Idaten?
I confirmed with General Piscalat
#6
Smoke
that the demons found us by hacking
cameras all over the country.
And you would have to be
an Idaten to hack cameras
that aren't connected to the internet.
I think I'll skip the foreplay
and just come out and ask...
What exactly are you?
What's this, Miku? Are you doubting me?
Well, let's say that I'm very
interested in your identity.
I think you're the first one
to actually express their suspicions.
Maybe the Demon Lord is an Idaten?
Paula's wild guess about
the Demon Lord being an Idaten
based on the thoughts of demons
wasn't actually very far off the mark.
Three things are necessary
for an Idaten to manifest.
The thoughts of a number of creatures,
their desire for salvation,
and a period of time
numbering in the centuries.
Take the Idaten who sacrificed themselves
and the thoughts of the slowly,
painfully dying demons...
Add 800 years to the mix,
and on the other side of the seal,
you've got the perfect storm.
The dying demons' desperation created him
with the desire to protect demonkind,
while the Idaten who sacrificed themselves
were the source of his knowledge.
It's no matter. Feel free to probe
around all you like.
And if you do get an answer,
by all means, share it with me.
Since I have no idea myself.
Because they were disassembled
and reassembled,
his memories are extremely hazy.
He's also physically unable
to leave the barrier.
But he doesn't even realize this fact.
Thus he projects his thoughts
and only interacts with the
outside world via machinery.
That's the true nature of the Demon Lord.
So, what now, Ysley-kun?
We know where to find him...
Are we going to go kill the Demon Lord?
Or no?
His attacks are fast, but light.
Which means...
In this position, I can attack you freely
and you don't have the
strength to escape. I win.
Shut it! This isn't over yet—
No, seriously, you lose.
You've got good reflexes and speed.
But even if you land those attacks,
they're not gonna hurt!
How about this?!
You stupid or something?
It doesn't matter how fast you come at me.
If it's in a straight line,
landing a counter is easy.
Looks like that's it.
Damn... I had no idea I was this weak.
What the shit have I been doing?
You seem troubled, my boy!
That's creepy as hell!
What're you doin' down there?!
Shouldn't you be asking about
how to attack with more power?
Okay...
Very good! Allow me to explain.
Li'l
Kids
Scale
What's this supposed to be?
Just what it looks like. A scale.
Hop on, Paula.
Okay...
It says 36 kilos. So what's the big idea?
Now try reducing your weight to zero.
Like this?
Well, that explains how you're so good
at moving without making a sound.
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
Doing this allows you
to move silently and swiftly,
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
as well as scale walls and ceilings.
Now, want to land heavier attacks?
Just make yourself heavier instead!
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
As you can see, Idaten can defy
the laws of physics governing things
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
like mass and air resistance.
Even in combat!
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
Reduce your mass to accelerate,
then increase it several tons
when you strike.
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
Easy as pie.
All Idaten are capable of
making themselves lighter.
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
Even Hayato, who has trouble moving silently,
can reduce himself to 1 or 2 kilos.
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
But "getting heavier" is a separate matter.
In order to vastly exceed your
base mass requires a level of
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
sophisticated mental imaging comparable
to projecting a weapon from your body.
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
Reaching several tons would
take hundreds of years,
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
but a couple hundred kilos?
Only a couple years.
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
A few dozen kilos? A few weeks.
In the best case,
maybe even a few days.
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
I think Paula might be able
to manage it now to some extent.
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
Hey, it worked! I can get up to 90!
All right, let me give this a try.
I've got a baseline of 65,
and then... I get heavier.
It didn't change at all, damn it!
Because you were only flexing just now.
You need to imagine what you're
trying to make happen. Picture it.
Okay, let's try this.
Now, Hayato-kun,
take in the the pressure on your legs
and the ground right now.
Then imagine all that weight is yours.
Prontea-san...
Oh, Ysley-kun!
It's been less than a week
since Zoble attacked us.
Is this training going to have any effect?
Well, if it doesn't, we can leave
Hayato out of the coming battles
and I'll train him over a longer period,
since we're going to be fighting
the Demon Lord eventually.
Are we going to go kill him? Or no?
Let's not.
The idea of an opponent who's a mixture
of a number of Idaten and demons...
We don't yet know how strong he might be.
You think he'd pose a threat
even if Master and I fought together?
It's a simple matter
of not being absolutely certain.
But one thing I know for sure is that
the Demon Lord isn't building
his strength in there.
In other words, we can leave him be
and he won't get any stronger in the interim.
Okay, so you want to put
the biggest problem on hold
and use that extra time
to come up with a perfect plan?
Can't say it's my style...
If you want to fight that badly,
I won't stop you,
but you'll have to be the one to
convince Rin-san to break the seal.
Moreover,
Rin-san will be free to go wherever
she likes once the seal is no more.
You're right! We should make sure we're
fully prepared for whatever might happen!
That said, we will have to fight
the Demon Lord eventually...
I wonder if I have to train, too...
What a drag! I just wanna do research!
Damn it! How long am I supposed
to carry this thing?!
Until your body memorizes
the feeling of its weight!
If you're still thinking of it at "carrying,"
then you're going about this all wrong!
Okay, try that again while
increasing your weight.
I'll tell you how different it comes out.
Going from 36 kilos to 90 kilos...
That should be twice as powerful!
That was heavier, yeah,
but you weren't going as fast.
I think the trick is to only get
heavy for the moment of impact.
That's kind of a big ask, y'know...
Even for someone who's a natural
at lowering her weight,
increasing it in an instant
seems to be difficult.
When I think about how long this'll
take to be viable in combat,
it makes my head hurt...
He's making them do this
knowing full well
that they won't be able
to pull it off, isn't he?
How the hell am I supposed
to learn this shit?!
Hey, General Piscalat! Come fight me again!
I don't mind, but...
Good grief, this boy has no patience.
From the look of it,
I doubt this will go any differently.
He doesn't seem to have learned a thing.
Gotta make my body heavy...
Just like that rock!
Wh-What was that?
Whoa, holy shit!
That really was way stronger!
Prontea-san, you're awesome, man!
Uh, yeah, thanks...
Seriously, you're awesome!
How the...?
I'm up next.
You're gonna have to prove
that wasn't a fluke just now.
Fine by me! Bring it on!
Th-This is...
He's able to chain attacks even
though that's far more difficult.
That boy... Is he actually a prodigy?
I think I understand.
It may be that Hayato has never thrown
a punch at his natural body weight.
This is actually kind of convenient...
He might be increasing his weight
more than he's realizing as a result.
Prontea-san?
Yeah, you're right!
Hey, wait, is this for real?
Then all of his previous attacks were
thrown at only a few kilograms?
Which means he's gotten this
strong in just eighty years...
That's even harder to believe!
Not bad...
There's room for improvement,
but you win, kid.
Hell yeah!
So this is the kind of power that
an Idaten who grows up
earnestly yearning
for strength can achieve...
All right, next up is all three
of you at once, right?
Hope you two weren't
expecting a nice, long break!
No, that won't be necessary, Hayato-kun.
I'll be your opponent this time.
This probably suits him better
than holding up a boulder.
I'm going to fight normally,
with one handicap:
I won't dodge any of your attacks.
Your goal is to manage to damage me.
Damn, you might be pretty awesome,
but you're still a royal pain
in the ass, y'know that?!
Don't screw with me!
Damn... I guess beating him
isn't gonna be easy after all...
Freaking monster...
He's so incredibly powerful...
Did we seriously intend to wage war
against someone like this?
It's a little late now, but that's terrifying.
Piscalat-neechan...
We're due to report in. What should we do?
We've got two choices. We can keep quiet
or give a false report to buy time.
But...
Based on this footage alone,
they really don't seem that impressive.
There's something weird
about how weak this boy is.
It's like he's actually much stronger,
but doesn't realize it somehow.
If he could utilize his full potential,
would be he be stronger than me?
I think you'd still have the edge, Brandy.
Y-Yes, of course I would.
But I'm pretty sure he
could beat the rest of us.
In fact, I think some of us
might already be lost...
What do you mean by that?
There's been no report from
Piscalat's group whatsoever.
Miku will probably see through
any ruse we try to pull.
The smart call is simply to stay quiet.
Are the three of them dead already?
No, I bet that they've been
captured and squeezed for intel.
Don't be ridiculous.
Even if they were caught, I doubt Neput
and Piscalat would talk so easily.
I get the feeling Cory-kun would spill
the beans pretty quickly under torture.
Torturing Cory-kun...
And Piscalat's such a virgin, too...
Plus, when I think about Neput
on top of everything else...
God, I want some!
Brandy, my brain's not going to work
otherwise, so I need a bathroom break!
If you're going to the bathroom, then why
are you taking that filthy thing with you?!
Fine, I need a good ****!
Could you please not be so blunt?!
Honestly, she doesn't have a
trace of refinement...
But did they really lose?
Your Lordship? Darling?
Hmm?
Has there been any news?
None at all.
There's been no contact
from Neput and the others.
We can't even tell if they're a lost cause.
With Nickel gone, you're our
strongest line of defense.
I'm counting on you, Brandy.
Yes. Leave it to me.
Well, Miku, did you discover anything?
She's so focused and serious!
Is the situation really that dire?
It was actually just post-climax clarity.
Paula, if you're bored, would you like
to join me on a trip to Sarabael?
It'd be easier for the two of us
to convince them that either alone.
That's fine with me.
Damn... I keep hitting him
and it's like he doesn't feel it...
You know, Hayato,
there's one other simple way
to increase your attack power
that doesn't involve your weight.
I wonder what he's filling
your head with now.
What's this all about?
And why all the secrecy?
Is something going on?
Mom?
First Prince Kuraishi
No one knows that I've called you all here.
Second Princess Raki
Third Prince Buzz
I'll get directly to the point.
I want the three of you to escape
the country immediately.
When you do, take a demon
of your choosing with you.
Any questions?
What for? And why are
we doing this in secret?
To prevent demonkind from being wiped out.
As things currently stand, Neput
and two others have been captured,
and since we have no way of knowing when
they might leak information about us,
I have no choice but to take
action on my own in secret.
Why the three of us
and not our older siblings?
Well, that's because...
The three of you are the ones
I actually gave birth to.
Hey! What's so funny?
Oh, I'm sorry, it's just...
You were talking about things like
preserving demonkind and intel leaks before
to justify it, but you really just
want to help your kids escape.
And you're usually so rational!
I guess you've got a
maternal streak after all!
I had no idea!
Shut it! Just get out of the kingdom
before I kill you myself!
Okay, Mom.
We'll go. We'll run.
Take care of yourself, too, okay?
Please be care...ful...
Yes. You three take care, as well.
They didn't know I have
a maternal streak, huh?
Well, neither did I.
Here you go!
Kuraishi-sama, you rock!
Ferlandia!
I've got a big trip coming up.
You should join me.
I've got shit to do, unlike you.
That means no time to join in
your playboy games.
Madame of the 7th
Zoble Pleasure District
Ferlandia
Look, just come with me.
Direct orders from Empress Brandy.
The rest of them are mere distractions.
Huh, so it's not just fun and games?
Zoble Air Force Major
Meliano
What is it, Buzz? You wanted to talk?
Uh, well...
Um, it's about...
Should I explain to her what's going on?
Or would it be more natural to tell her
how I feel and see what she says first?
Kroft!
Butler to the
Zoble Royal Family
Kroft
Oh? What is it, Princess Raki?
Please! Take me away from this place!
This is just getting more depressing...
I don't wanna die yet.
I wanna run... I wanna run...
God...
If you're watching,
I beg you, send us salvation.
My devoted faithful, the world
is in need of salvation!
The Zoble Empire uses their military might
to commit every manner of barbarism!
Hotaena has forsaken God in favor
of indulging in wanton delights!
They are sinful nations whose
policy is to blaspheme God!
They are in need of redemption
that only we can offer!
Yes, redemption in the form of death!
At this point, their only hope is for
their souls be purified at the hands of us,
God's humble servants!
Redemption for the devils!
Purification for the devils!
The finite wealth and resources of this world
cannot be monopolized
by such unholy authoritarians!
Their management is a task
that only we, God's servants,
are fit to handle!
What the—?!
I've heard the rumors,
but that was a seriously pathetic sermon.
Didn't it amount to "no one's
allowed to have power, except us"?
What are you impudent
children trying to say?!
And just who are you?!
Good afternoon. It's nice to meet you.
We're gods!