Training with Rin-san, huh?
What's she like anyway?
She drew out Hayato and Prontea,
and taught them how to fight.
#2
The
Black
South
She's also a survivor of the Idaten who
battled the demons 800 years ago.
The only living being to truly understand
the demonic involvement of the past.
She's the strongest Idaten
in current existence.
If we're going to learn how to fight,
she's the best person to turn to.
Plus, at the moment, it's dangerous to be
apart from either her or Hayato.
According to Hayato,
that doctor was a robot...
We can assume whoever was controlling it
is now in possession of all the data
it collected during our battle.
Suppose they have a minion even more
powerful than that demonic beast,
and it were to attack.
We'd be done for.
If we stick with Hayato and Rin-san
under the premise of training,
we can probably avoid getting done in.
Probably?
Well, the plan doesn't preclude the
possibly of getting killed by Rin-san...
To be honest, I'm not thrilled about this.
I used to train alongside Hayato,
At the time, I thought to myself,
"What's the big deal?"
and as embarrassing as it is to admit,
it was so harsh that
I turned tail after three months.
"Why is Ysley exaggerating so much?"
I haven't seen Rin-san since.
Time to die, you old—
Just as brutal as I remember.
The Idaten Deities
Know Only Peace
What... What was that?! You call that training?
It looked like a beating!
Well, er, theoretically.
It's the proper way to train an Idaten, but...
The problem is that Rin-san
doesn't understand the theory.
She's just doing what she wants.
And that's terrifying!
Come on, Ysley. Wouldn't it be safer
to go learn from Prontea-san?
She vanished!
Well, well... We meet again, Ysley.
It's been, what, fifty years?
And you have the nerve to show up now?
What's with this unbelievable bloodlust?!
Shit. She's even angrier than I anticipated.
The wrong answer here means death,
and no excuse will be enough
to make a difference.
That being the case...
I have only one option!
Rin-san!
I can't deny that I ran
from your training once before,
and I know how presumptuous
it may seem after all this time,
but please teach me how to fight again!
Ysley took the direct approach.
He straightforwardly, without pretense,
asked for what he wanted,
which effectively served
to mask his true intentions.
True Intentions
Mask
And it was super effective.
To Rin, who was driven by her
sense of duty to fight demons,
an Idaten who shirked his training
in order to learn in the human world
was essentially the same as a shut-in
who did nothing but play porn games all day.
But when Ysley spoke, it was as if
that sort of fail-son suddenly
put on a business suit...
I'm so sorry for everything
I put you through!
Starting today, I'm going to turn
over a new leaf and look for a job!
And the degree to which this affected Rin
was not unlike that of a mother.
I see, I see! So you've
finally realized your duty!
Oh, Grandfather! I've never been happier!
Now then, Ysley, who's the girl?
Oh, right. This is a new Idaten...
My name is Paula. It's nice to meet you.
Really? Did you draw her out?
Or was it Hayato?
Oh, no, I was drawn out by Prontea-san.
"Drawing Out"
Idaten are naturally occurring entities.
If they are left alone, they will still
manifest within a few centuries.
But with the intervention of another Idaten,
they can be drawn out in an instant.
Those drawn out in this fashion often take
the Idaten responsible as their master.
This is why Rin,
who spends nearly all her time
where the demons have been sealed,
will occasionally travel
across the world with Hayato.
She means to find and draw out
new Idaten to join her.
Oh, Prontea, eh?
That takes me back.
It took me 200 years to
train him into shape.
Of all my students, he's the only one
I'd say can stand on his own two feet.
So, are you here to train, as well?
I still regret it to this day.
Well, that's what I was thinking of.
Why didn't I just say no
and run away back then?
Very well.
Come at me, then.
What? Already?
Well, since we're just getting started,
I should probably take it easy—
Rest in peace.
Well, she's certainly fragile.
What in the world did Prontea teach her?
Probably nothing in terms of combat...
Well then, Ysley, let's see what you've got.
C-Certainly.
Pleasure to be working with you...
You still alive, Paula?
Can't talk, huh?
Probably a punctured lung, I'd wager.
I can't believe the dumb old bitch
just chucked me like that!
My face still smarts.
Hey, it's Ysley and Paula.
What brings you guys around?
Finally decide to start training?
Oh, damn, is Paula almost dead?
She won't be able to move
for three days, I'd say.
You never hold back, do you?
Well, don't sweat it.
You get your organs mashed up enough,
you stop worrying about it eventually.
Okay, Hayato, we're sparring again.
What, already?
Ysley, you're up again in two hours.
I hadn't abandoned my training
with her previously just because it was harsh.
I couldn't accept that this daily routine
would amount to any real growth.
Why is it that we Idaten know our names
at the moment of our manifestation?
Couldn't say. It's a good question, though.
How does the drawing out
process work, anyway?
How exactly do we appear in nature?
It should be impossible for organisms
to simply appear from nothing.
We're gods, so doesn't that explain it?
Then, as deities, why do we
have human appearances,
manifest wearing human clothing,
and communicate with human language?
No clue.
I also thought talking to her
was a waste of time.
Zoble Military
Front Line
We are not waging a defensive war.
We espouse no lukewarm ideology, either.
This is an invasion, plain and simple.
Now, tell me what you want!
We want to kill, ma'am!
We want to steal, ma'am!
We want to spoil, ma'am!
Who do you want to kill?
Our enemies, ma'am!
What do you want to steal?!
Their wealth, ma'am!
And what do you want to spoil?!
The finest girl I can find, ma'am!
Virgins, ma'am!
Little girls, yeah!
A housewife in front of her husband!
Shotas!
A beefy older gent, ma'am!
Too far, dude! Unbelievable!
I respect your candor. Permission granted.
The land and resources will belong to Zoble!
Everything else is your reward.
Pillage to your heart's content, you dogs!
Charge!
I have a report, ma'am.
All C-Soldiers are to return
to base immediately.
There was an emergency
notification from Dr. Obami.
From the De... the doctor, you say?
Yes, ma'am. What shall we do?
Requesting a return in the
middle of a battle like this...
It's fine. I'll be the only one returning.
The outcome of this battle
was a foregone conclusion.
By the way, I'd take a few
steps back if I were you.
There's a missile headed this way.
What... General?!
General!
Direct hit confirmed!
Did we take out General Piscalat?
Reload immediately!
Fire as soon as the target is—
Idiots.
Ready a jet for me.
I leave the rest in your hands.
Take everything.
Ma'am! Understood!
All right, that should do for today.
Okay...
Come on, guys. Let's go hang out.
Can you move yet?
Dead...
D
E
A
Dying... Gonna die...
Paula, your eyes are doing
some kinda fish thing!
Ysley, is there really any
purpose to this training?
Are you sure it's not just torture?
I wondered the same thing for a time.
But there is a proper logic to it,
so rest assured.
What the hell's logic
got to do with training?
You fight every day,
you're bound to get stronger.
Honestly, I envy your
simplistic outlook, Hayato.
Wouldn't most people
turn to weight training instead?
That said, weight training
would be pointless for Idaten.
Since we've got nothing to do until
we're healed, I might as well explain...
Don't care. Your explanations
are too confusing.
It's okay. I'll hear you out.
Did you have to make it sound so pitiful?
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
We Idaten are different on a
cellular level from all other organisms,
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
including humans.
Hence the unique training.
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
Consider how we can survive
having our hearts crushed.
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
Rin-san believes our
supernatural nature explains this,
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
but demons die easily when
their hearts are crushed.
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
See, the destruction of the heart
stops the circulatory system,
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
halting the delivery of oxygen and nutrients.
This is where we differ from living creatures.
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
We require no nutrition
and don't really need to breathe,
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
thus a lack of circulating
blood is no problem.
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
Though we act short of breath when tired,
this is more a "habit" than anything else—
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
a habit of living creatures.
Our genesis lies in the
thoughts of living creatures,
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
and our creation is dictated by them.
The reason we have human forms
rather than anything else
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
is that humans have considerably
more thoughts than other creatures.
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
The reason you specifically are able
to speak with birds is because
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
you're partly composed of bird thoughts.
Now then,
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
what does any of this have to do
with torturous training?
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
Hayato was actually right.
The more your organs are destroyed,
the less it bothers you.
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
His body is already become
something distinctly inhuman.
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
In exchange, he's gained something
that living creatures do not have:
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
a metamorphosis which makes
him more effective in combat.
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
The kind of evolution we undergo
is tied to our own thoughts.
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
Wanting to be stronger,
have more resilience, et cetera...
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
And the most efficient way to
force these changes is to expose
Fast Forward Explanation in Progress
the body to extreme stimuli.
So how long does that all take?
Somewhere between fifty to a hundred years.
Sorry. Not happening.
Come to think of it, why would you suddenly
start such nuts and bolts training?
Did seeing a demon in person suddenly
make you realize your responsibility?
Is that what it looks like, Paula?
That's the face he makes when he's
got something really nasty in mind...
Hey, Granny, what's that?
What's what?
You've got something on your clothes.
Some tiny metal thing.
What is this?
Some kinda machine, maybe?
What's it doing on you, though?
I have no idea.
C'mon, what'd you have to break it for?
Ysley might've been able to figure it out.
Doesn't matter. Once it's broken,
it's not anything anymore, is it?
Yeah, guess not.
Oh, but it was.
Gend Autonomous Zone Invaded and Occupied by Zoble Forces
Paula, remember how I told you we're born
from the thoughts of living creatures?
The thing is, thoughts alone
don't make us manifest.
It takes an additional element...
A desire for salvation.
It's okay. Don't be scared.
Dear God...
Please, God...
Please... grant us salvation...
God!
That doesn't make any sense, though.
You said human desire for salvation
is what makes Idaten appear,
but we don't help humans at all.
That's not so strange. It's other humans
who make humans suffer in war, right?
What sense would it make
to fight humans to save humans?
I guess you're right...
Two human nations fight,
and one is destroyed...
The victor grows in its place,
so it's not a problem.
It's not as if the humans care about how
the composition of a forest might change
as long as there are still plants there.
And if an invasive species wipes
out the native wildlife of a lake,
they'd just think of it
as a good fishing spot.
This is all to say that,
while we're in a different position,
our thought process isn't
so different from the humans'.
Still, there's a condition under which
we will fight to protect them.
Consider the demons...
For example, say you happened upon that Gyudo
monster attacking some humans.
If you were as powerful as Rin-san,
what would you do?
I think I'd get rid of him.
Yet why would you help humans
that you normally just ignore?
Huh, that's a good question...
I wonder.
I guess because I'd feel
compelled to fight the monster?
Wrong. It's because if you do nothing,
the humans would be wiped out.
Humans are similar. If a forest they
normally don't care about catches on fire,
they'll make an effort to put it out.
But right now, mankind is distinctly
not on the brink of destruction.
They're prosperous enough
to kill one another for simple
self-interest, of all things.
And as humans engage in pointless
wars to amuse themselves,
the collective thoughts of those
caught in the crossfire
is what calls us forth... to do nothing.
Thus we do nothing.
I suppose you could say we're a generation
of Idaten deities who only know peace.
Is there no God after all?
Still, there's something I don't understand.
What purpose do the demons serve?
Did you know, Paula?
If left uncontested,
they'd continue to predate and destroy
until the world was completely barren
and they ultimately died from starvation.
It doesn't make any sense.
If there are any intelligent
demons out there...
I would love to ask what they want.
Hey! Pi-chan, Pi-chan!
Long time no see!
You been doin' good, yeah?
It's been a few years since
I last saw you, right? Right?!
The way she talks is still annoying.
Nickel!
You need to show more respect
to a superior officer!
Come to think of it, you're right!
I need'st be formal with my manner
of speech, do I not, General Piscalat?!
How'd she survive a fall from that height?
Putting that aside, this meeting
should be of incredible import!
I dare say we're in for the first
meeting of substance in quite some time!
Your Majesty,
Prime Minister of the Zoble Empire
Biarov
why am I not a part of this meeting?
Because it has nothing to do with you.
Emperor of the Zoble Empire
Takeshita
Empress
Brandy
That's right. Your job is running
the government, isn't it?
Just focus on policy and diplomacy.
What the hell kind of diplomacy could a
war-mongering nation like this manage?
As you wish, ma'am.
Hey there, Your Majesty the Emperor!
You're looking as miserable as ever!
We'll be waiting in the
meeting room! Bye-bye!
I must say, formal language is most tiring,
don't you think, General Piscalat?!
You're not even pulling it off.
Nickel certainly seems to be in high spirits.
We should get going ourselves.
Yes, I suppose we should.
This meeting was called by Obami,
head of weapons development...
What is that madman's game now?
Kagekiki.
Sir?
I want you to look into this.
By your command.
Meeting Room
Commander of the Zoble Imperial Navy
Neput
Child Soldier
Cory
Zoble Army Defense Force Soldier
G-Thirteen
The Lively Chief Clerk
of Childcare Support
Barcode
Star Midwife
Umeyo
Animal Trainer
Miku
And everybody else
Is that everyone?
The doctor's not here yet.
PM Biarov's Personal Agent
Kagekiki the Ninja
What a bizarre assemblage...
What do they mean to discuss?
Sorry about the delay, folks.
Head of Weapons Development
Doctor Obami
Let's get this meeting underway.
What happened to you...?
Shut it! My usual body got
wrecked by that Idaten brat!
His "usual body"? It was wrecked?
And what exactly is an Idaten?
Granted, that's part of why
we're having this meeting.
First, let's start with...
Oh, can I take care of one thing first?
What is it, Nickel?
Would you look at that!
If isn't Kagekiki-kun!
Look, I understand being curious...
But eavesdropping is just rude!
Oh, sorry about that, Take-kun.
Try to be more careful.
Now, we're ready when you are...
O great Demon Lord who granted
us human forms and intelligence.
All right, let's start by reviewing
the footage of the Idaten.