HIT IT EXACT
Pour in exactly 2000g of water
and get a great prize!
4117 grams!
2117 grams over!
How unfortunate!
Look at that!
I told you that we didn't need the last cup!
You're blaming me?
You're always blaming other people!
Is there a prize for getting close?
I don't think we're anywhere near the mark.
You put too much water in! Too much water!
You're the one who added the last cup!
Something's been off since the beginning of the second semester.
First question!
High
Schooler
Quiz
Intense
battles
are here!!
Which Feudal Era commander became famous...
for giving salt to his enemy's generals?
Giving salt?
What kind of old lady was he?
Give up, already.
Summer's long over, fall is ending,
and the cultural festival has started...
Victory is sweet!
You didn't get a single question right.
Kaname-kun ended up getting seven questions in a row.
Something's not right...
Poor Cinderella.
Her stepmother and sisters must have bullied her again today.
Oh, sorry!
Are you all right?
What are you looking at?
Here.
Shun-chan...
Thanks!
Something's not right.
yappari kimi da yo ne
Oh hey, it's you
honto odoroita yo
You startled me
futari yoku aruita namikidoori
Here we are, on the tree-lined road we walked so often
otona ni naru no wo
I couldn't wait to grow up
matezu ni toozaketeitta no wa watashi datta ne
and I kept you at a distance, didn't I
itsumo
As always,
mainasu ichido no ame ga furu
the icy rain falls
kimi ga kureta namida
comprised of tears you cried for me
sono yasashisa made wakaranakute
That kindness I didn't understand
zutto kono mune wo shimetsuketa
lay heavy on my heart all the time
mainasu ichido no ame ga furu
The icy rain falls
tsumetasugiru namida
comprised of tears unbearably cold
hagurakasu taido ni okotteta keredo
Although I was angry at my evasive personality
jitsu wa sukuwareteitan da ne
you cured me of that, didn't you
A single flower blooms in the darkness surrounding our school tonight,
for it is the origin of my name.
Bathroom Hanako-san in the cultural festival!
I'll even make the famous Hanako-san my own.
My appeal is limitless!
Hold on, Chizuru-kun.
I'm quite famous, myself.
Whoa! What is that, Yukki? You look so cool!
It'd be perfect if my dad was here, though, for the eye.
The eye?
Hey, come on! Everyone's got their eye on Hanako-chan today!
No, that's not what I'm talking about. My dad's really the eye...
Hey, what are you still doing here?
Guests will be coming in here soon.
Kanamecchi, Kanamecchi!
Stop laughing!
Whose fault do you think this is?
But don't you think it's a bit fruity?
Not at all.
My wig!
Hanako-san, a woman's hair is her life.
What are you doing? That hurt!
It hurts me to see it, too.
We're opening the haunted house for business.
Ghosts, give it your best.
Come on. Let's hide.
Are we really clumping together like this?
Someone's coming.
What? Where? Where? Where?
Hey, hey... I'm so scared.
Just hold on and you'll be fine.
Okay.
Ignore them.
I can't stand the thought of someone using us to further their relationship!
We're not Cupid. We're ghosts, you know.
If you're a ghost, then scare them.
Come on. Keep walking.
That's Yuutan's voice!
Yuuta!
I-I'm sorry I came with you...
Don't apologize. I feel better if there are more people with me in a haunted house...
Yuuta!
Yuuta.
I'm Hanako-san!
Hey, you shouldn't come here.
You're going the wrong way...
It's Kaname-kun!
What's with your reaction?
Oh, um... I mean...
Why aren't you wearing your vest?
I thought this would help me blend into the darkness more.
Yuuki-kun, you're so smart!
You were pretty scared, Mary.
Are you stupid? What's with your outfit?
I'm so scared!
The next guests are coming!
You guys should go.
Okay.
I'm off, too.
Me, too!
You guys are the monsters!
Hanako may be a ghost, but she's also a girl.
I don't know about that.
Don't you think rokurokubi are too obscure to be here?
I don't want to hear it.
Sorry.
Mary, even if you're scared, try not to cry.
W-What are you talking about?
A haunted house like this is too silly to be scary!
I see.
It's dark! It's scary! No more!
Masaki-chan, are you okay?
Y-Yeah, I'm fine.
Let's go together.
O-Okay.
Is the exit still far from here?
I want to get out of this dark place.
We're almost there.
Okay.
We finally made it out.
Wasn't it scary?
Yeah, but it was fun.
So bright.
Ow!
What? Why'd you slap me?
Why were you holding my hand?!
Haunted House
Pervert! That's harassment!
What? That's ridiculous!
You grabbed my hand!
I never would've done that if I'd known it was yours!
I missed my chance!
So not cute.
What's her problem? I was just trying to...
Say cheese.
Culture Festival
Culture Festi
Culture Fe........
Wait, what?
What do you mean, "What"?
What are you two talking about?
Do they really have no intention of coming back?
I hope my shift ends soon.
Sis, you're screaming way too much.
Another customer.
Here we go.
Re... ve... n... ge...
That was great!
Shut up!
Stop laughing, Hisako!
What are you doing here?
Damn, this sucks.
That look really suits you.
No, it doesn't!
You're taking it off?
It's fine. It's about the end of my shift...
Really? Do you have some time after this?
Why?
Do you want to walk around with us?
We'll get lost by ourselves.
Sure.
Hey, aren't you in the Student Council?
Can you get us to the front of all the lines?
No.
Kaname-kun, you're in the Student Council?
Yeah.
That's amazing!
It's nothing, really.
It's amazing. It's really amazing.
Fine, it's amazing.
I'm going to get changed.
Chocolate Bananas
That's a pretty long line.
Yakisoba and chocolate covered bananas are the best part of a festival.
Um, excuse me?
Hey! Don't ignore me!
Don't cut in line.
Huh? Are we lining up from shortest to tallest?
No!
Then who cares?
I care!
Go to the end of the line!
Chizuru, if you get in a fight with people who aren't even students while you're looking like that,
Kaname will get mad at you.
I'm not starting a fight!
I'm just telling off this rude—
Kou-chan!
Hey, wait!
"Kou-chan?"
He knows Azuma-sensei?
I dunno.
Who does he think he is?
Fairy Tale Cafe
Excuse me!
Yuutan, Shun-chan!
Oh, you came to visit!
Of course.
We've been looking forward to it, since you told us you'd be working this afternoon.
But really, you two look so cute!
Really?
Yuuta, you're beautiful.
Are you Little Red Riding Hood?
Yes.
Somehow, I can vividly picture you being eaten by a huge wolf.
What?
Snow White, if you're not careful,
you know, a very vindictive person will bring something poisoned to kill you.
Well, I turn away all door-to-door salespeople.
I don't even listen to what they have to say.
You're surprisingly level-headed.
Of course I am.
I'm not a princess for nothing.
Sit down and I'll bring you some Fairy Forest juice.
Okay.
Huh?
So you're here, too.
What are you reading?
Why do you care?
She's practicing her lines.
Masaki's class is performing Cinderella this evening.
Really?
What part are you playing, Mary?
A mouse.
What's so funny?
It's just that you're the perfect size!
In case you didn't know,
the mouse has the important job of cheering up Cinderella.
Is that so?
Have you already memorized your lines?
Of course I have.
I've absolutely perfected them.
You're bleeding.
You're so clumsy.
I'm not clumsy.
What's wrong, Chizuru-kun?
I-It's nothing. Nothing at all.
I'm not clumsy or anything.
But...
Ah, I need to go get ready for the play!
Thanks for the food.
Masaki-chan...
Huh?
Break a leg. I'll definitely come see your play.
Really?
Yes.
You And Me.
Like hell!
What's wrong with Mary? She's not cute at all!
I was only trying to put a band-aid on her cut!
How nostalgic.
Masaki-chan got mad at me the first time I met her, too.
When I tried to give her a band aid,
she said she didn't need my help and ran away.
Huh? That happened to you?
She really doesn't appreciate the kindness of others!
But when I chased her down and tried to give it to her again, she took it.
What? You chased her?
I was rather persistent.
What's wrong with that?
Our shifts should be over soon.
Okay.
That's amazing.
Any normal person wouldn't bother chasing her.
I mean...
Maybe that's why she likes Shun-chan.
Chizuru.
Huh?
Shouldn't we change before we go see the play?
Yeah, yeah!
Where's Kaname-kun?
I'm sure if you check with the festival committee, they'll understand.
Okay, thanks.
He said, "They'll understand."
That's the power of the Student Council.
Stop saying that.
I just talked to her normally.
But you're so composed.
If I were your underclassman, I know I'd rely on you.
Okay, okay.
There he is!
Kaname-kun!
What's with you guys?
We've been looking all over for you.
You can't ditch the haunted house without saying anything!
Why are you still dressed like that?
There's no time.
Let's hurry to Masaki-chan's play!
Huh? Just go if you want to go.
In fact, it'll be enough if only you go...
No! Masaki-chan worked really hard on this!
If we don't all go, I'm sure she'll be disappointed!
No, I think she'll be disappointed by your stupidity.
Sorry. It looks like you have plans with your friends.
I don't!
Hello!
I haven't seen you since the fireworks.
I'm Hanako!
Don't talk to her!
Oh, no. We don't have time to change.
Way to go, Cinderella!
Always keeping track of time!
I'm Snow White.
We don't have time to discuss this!
Oh, well! We'll have to go straight there!
Let's go!
Hey! Cut it out! I have plans!
They're as lively as ever.
How nice.
Bring me a pumpkin, Cinderella.
A pumpkin?
That's right. The biggest one you can find.
I understand. I will bring you the biggest pumpkin I can find.
This brings back memories. It still smells the same.
There's a good girl. Make haste.
Don't be so loud.
What were you talking to Tachibana-kun and his friends about?
Tachibana? Oh, that short kid?
I just told him he's short.
You're one to talk.
He probably thought you were his age.
That's impossible!
I'll have to talk to him later.
What are you talking about?
Wait, Onee-sama. I didn't mean...
What am I gonna do? I'm so nervous.
Okay, people, underwear, imagine...
Shun-chan said he'd come,
so I have to do a good job.
B-B-But having him watch makes me even more nervous.
It's okay!
With all these people here,
I won't be able to tell where...
He's right there!
Satou-san, we're up!
Okay!
Um... I-I need to say my l-lines...
Um... Poor Cirerella!
Today...
Her s-stepmother and sisters must have bu-bull-bullied her a-
-gain.
I really stuttered.
Masaki-chan!
Good work. The play was fantastic...
What? Masaki-chan!
Hey, Mary? Where'd you go?
Sheesh.
Girls' Bathroom
I can't believe I screwed up such easy lines.
It was my chance to impress Shun-chan.
What am I gonna do? I can't face Shun-chan after that.
Mary?
Wh-What are you doing in the girls' bathroom?
What's wrong with Bathroom Hanako-san going in the girl's bathroom?
There's something wrong with your head!
So this is what the girls' bathroom looks like.
Get out!
Ow!
You're telling me to get out?
Then you should get out of here, too.
Everyone's looking for you.
What? Is it because you screwed up your lines?
Ow! Why are you so violent?
So you messed up one or two lines...
So what? The girl playing Cinderella messed up way more.
And she wasn't cute at all.
Well, it was my own fault for expecting more.
Hey, are you listening?
Are-you-lis-ten-ing?
M-My wig!
Do you want to try my wig on?
I guess not. I suppose you wouldn't want to.
When...
When I was rehearsing... I could say them.
I know that.
Everyone watching the play could tell.
Shun-chan knows, too.
Did Shun-chan say that?
No, but...
B-But he knows! Honestly!
But Shun-chan didn't watch me rehearse!
He doesn't have to see you to know!
Don't underestimate a man's imagination!
But what if he doesn't know?
He does know! 100%!
He knows!
He really does!
Definitely!
Okay!
Come on. Let's go.
Unbelievable.
You're the only one who'd run to the bathroom.
These days, kids go to the roof or the river, Mary-san.
Shut up. I don't need that.
But you're the only one who'd chase me into the girls' bathroom.
I can't go out looking like this!
We're really not going out there?
If I had the energy to go to the dance tonight, I'd go home.
But it'd make a good memory.
We've already made plenty of good memories, haven't we, getting-yelled-at Hanako-san?
Shut up!
Sensei! There's a boy dressed like a girl in the bathroom!
Shut up, shut up, shut up.
When I remember you holding my left hand,
my entire body feels conflicted...
and my stomach tickles.
Your red cheeks traced by the light pouring through the window...
and your brightly smiling eyelashes...
are all beyond that soft, wavy hair.
But I end up imagining this and that about being with you someday and...
Pervert.
Chizuru-kun?
Your attention everyone!
Who wants to know what the girls' bathroom looks like?
A-Are you stupid?
Becoming embarrassed tickled my stomach again.
boku wa nakimushi de kuyashikute dakedo
It pains me to be such a crybaby,
anata ni ima tsutaetain da
but I want to tell you my feelings right now
tada massugu ni boku wo mitsumeru tsuyokute
There you stand, silently gazing at me
Allowing me to answer those strong and gentle eyes of yours
yasashii sono hitomi ni kotaeru tame ni
itsushika miushinatteta ichiban taisetsu na mono mo
You taught me what I lost sight of
sotto anata ga oshiete kureta
What was most important to me
tashika ni sou omoeru kara
I have no doubts about that
boku wa yowamushi de iya datta dakedo
I hated how weak I was
motto motto tsuyoku naru kara
but I will continue to become stronger
anata no koto wo mamoreru you na boku ni naru kara
I will be someone who could protect you
dakara sukoshi mattete
So wait a little longer for me
Next time: Crescent Moon Silhouette.
Crescent Moon Silhouette