What are you doing, Shun?
Kaname-kun.
Let's go.
Yuuki...
Couldn't you at least have worn your blazer to the opening ceremony?
Yuuta, you're his older brother.
You should be the one telling him this.
The cherry blossoms are amazing.
They sure are. They're in full bloom.
Shun, you've got a petal on your head.
Thank you.
Kaname, you've got a petal on you, too.
I'm not going to get it for you, though.
It's not like I wanted you to!
Good morning!
Morning!
Looking forward to classes?
I wonder who our teacher will be?
I hope it's Taiazuma-sensei.
We met that spring.
We spent many seasons together after that.
It's another beautiful spring.
We entered our second year at Homare High School this year.
yappari kimi da yo ne
Oh hey, it's you
honto odoroita yo
You startled me
futari yoku aruita namikidoori
Here we are, on the tree-lined road we walked so often
otona ni naru no wo
I couldn't wait to grow up
matezu ni toozaketeitta no wa watashi datta ne
and I kept you at a distance, didn't I
itsumo
As always,
mainasu ichido no ame ga furu
the icy rain falls
kimi ga kureta namida
comprised of tears you cried for me
sono yasashisa made wakaranakute
That kindness I didn't understand
zutto kono mune wo shimetsuketa
lay heavy on my heart all the time
mainasu ichido no ame ga furu
The icy rain falls
tsumetasugiru namida
comprised of tears unbearably cold
hagurakasu taido ni okotteta keredo
Although I was angry at my evasive personality
jitsu wa sukuwareteitan da ne
you cured me of that, didn't you
I spy someone spending a hundred yen just for some oolong tea.
Does it really matter?
I've got plenty of barley tea in my fridge at home.
Must be nice to be rich.
If you're gonna buy oolong tea,
you might as well get milk.
Yeah. You've gotta get your calcium intake.
That's why you're always pissed off.
And whose fault is that?
Kaname, I'm sure you'll end up buying love with money, too.
I just don't get it.
And I don't get how you guys ended up there just from buying one oolong tea.
Now, now.
Let's go up to the roof.
This whirlwind of sakura petals,
or rather, this spring clouded by dust,
can't begin to satiate the hunger of us growing boys.
The wind's strong.
Who suggested we eat lunch on the roof?
But the weather's nice.
It'd be a waste to eat in the classroom.
It's a bigger waste if my food gets covered in sand.
You can take one of my sandwiches if you'd like.
You don't need to give Kaname anything, Shun.
Just eat them yourself.
Kaname, why are you making such a fuss over a couple of pieces of food?
You were just buying some
oolong tea like some rich kid.
Get off my back,
you two twins.
I'm tired of getting mixed up in your business.
Well,
even if it's covered in sand,
it'll all be the same in my stomach.
Well then,
when we invited you
you should have refused.
By the way, Kaname-kun, Yuuki-kun...
This is the first time you've
been in the same class, isn't it?
Um...
Everything sucks.
What?
You know this guy ignores anyone who tries to talk to him, right?
Is that so?
I don't intentionally ignore anyone.
Their words simply don't resonate with me.
You just aren't listening to them.
Yuuta-kun...
It's fine, isn't it?
That's just who he is.
As long as it isn't hurting anyone, who cares if he's a lone wolf?
Being ignored is plenty hurtful.
Yuuki's not nearly accommodating enough nor considerate enough.
He's gotta be more... you know.
Shut up already.
Ah, what a pain.
Kaname, you're such an old lady.
You used to be so much cuter.
Who you calling cute?!
Ah, back when Kaname had feelings for Kaori-sensei?
When did that happen?
Man, that was pretty cute.
Sure was.
Falling in love with your preschool
teacher is a little precocious, isn't it?
Your innocent little eyes sparkled.
Look at him now.
The reflective lenses of his glasses sparkle.
Shut up!
You guys are ones to talk!
What do you mean by that?
You guys used to be cute little brats,
getting all excited over nothing.
Apparently, the person in the middle loses years off their lifespan.
Yuuta-kun's gonna die!
Yuuta won't die as long as we don't forget him.
Does my lifespan really decrease that quickly?
Is this my last night on Earth?
Fine! I'll sleep in the middle!
Taking on someone else's life is a heavy burden.
You're right.
All my courage has...
I just thought of a way we can all live...
...without anyone getting hurt.
But I'm already hurt...
Let's ask Kaname-kun to come over.
Sleeping in the middle shortens your lifespan?
Is that why you invited me over?
If there's an even number of us, there technically isn't a middle.
Now we can sleep in peace.
What now?
Doesn't this mean both of us are in the middle?
What?
If identical twins lie side-by-side,
then we only really count as one person.
I can't sleep when I'm not next to you.
Being twins is tough.
For us, you mean.
Oh yeah, that might've happened.
But after that...
How's this?
I can't get any sleep with you two around.
Kaname-kun, you can't sleep?
Kaori-sensei!
How about I sing you a lullaby?
Please don't treat me like a kid!
Treat me like a man.
But you are a kid.
You made Shun sleep in the middle,
just so you could sleep next to Kaori-sensei.
The innocence in your eyes
began to cloud over that day...
Shut up already!
In any case...
Yuuki, go join a club.
What?
It's the fastest way for you
to get what you're missing.
You And Me.
You here to watch? No problem.
Would you like to play a game with us?
Yes, please.
Come on.
A club's not something you force yourself into.
If I don't force you to join, you never will!
I will.
I already participate in club activities daily.
In the Going Home Club.
Let's get underway.
Go on.
You can't run away now.
YuUki-kun, you can do it!
Go get the sweat, passion, and teamwork...
...that's missing from your high school experience!
You know what to do when
you have the ball, right?
Yeah, yeah,
I hurl it as hard as I can at you, right?
You pass it to your teammates!
Yuuki-kun obviously doesn't care.
That bastard.
Asaba-kun!
Don't dodge it!
But I didn't ask for it.
How are you supposed to play on a team like that?!
You never tried very hard in PE.
Are you just not really athletic?
Why don't you seriously give basketball a go?
I would, but...
If you really do suck that much,
you should join the Basketball Club, right?
That's right.
We play a lot of basketball in PE, too.
See?
Let's start the second half!
Where the hell did that come from?
Yuuki's extremely athletic.
What?
He's even more amazing when he actually tries.
He's even better than that?
The whole basketball club can't even keep up with him.
Yuuki-kun's popular.
What's so great about him?
No girl could keep her mouth
shut after seeing moves like that.
What's so cool about being a ball hog?
Nice shot.
Begin!
Wow!
Are you okay?
Good work.
What are you doing?
That kid suddenly grabbed my collar.
I thought he wanted something.
He was doing what you'd call "judo."
Swimming, huh?
They say it keeps your shoulders from getting stiff.
I guess I should think about my future health.
Are you unable to live in the present?
I'd get tired.
That would end in total rejection.
So, who am I supposed to shoot at?
The target!
Damn it. Why can't you make up your mind?
I don't need to—
No, that's no good!
You've got to see more of the world.
I feel like my eyes are being forced open.
What are you all doing?
Azuma-sensei!
A club for Yuuki-kun to join?
He can't make up his mind.
We've already checked out
most of the athletics clubs.
Athletics clubs?
He's really athletic.
Really?
What about you, Yuuta-kun?
What do you think he should do?
I don't know.
Yuuki should decide for himself.
I think, well...
I think you should check out the other clubs, too.
People don't always want
to do what they're good at.
So cool.
Azuma-sensei is really adult-like.
Well, he is an adult, you know.
What's wrong, Kaname?
Nothing.
It's the Cooking Club.
Well? Should we—
Huh? What? Yuuta-kun?
Not the Cooking Club.
What? But Azuma-sensei said...
In a middle school cooking class, Yuuki...
Y-Yuuki-kun, could you help us peel potatoes?
You start by holding the knife like this, and...
Amazing!
So fast!
Here's your knife back.
You're too dangerous.
I didn't mean any harm.
Yuuki-kun, do you want to
check out the Tea Club?
Kaname, you're almost perfect.
I guess.
Yuuki, you're up next.
Yuuki-kun, it's fine if you wanna take it easy today...
Don't talk to me!
I won't remember where Kaname put his mouth...
I wiped it!
I get it!
You don't want my indirect kiss?
He wanted an indirect kiss.
Seriously?
What a creep.
I didn't want one!
I know...
Kaname's part of the—
No.
...Student Council.
I give up.
If he doesn't want to do it, then he'll never choose a club.
And you're in no position to be reading manga!
Cut it out.
You know that I love manga and anime.
Yeah, yeah. Is that so?
Why didn't you say so earlier?!
The tea cup!
Kaname, you're paying for that.
Yuuta, you're his brother! You must've known!
You made us waste all this time!
Manga Society
This club will suit you perfectly!
You can talk all you want about manga and anime here.
Get them to stamp your admission form and turn it in.
Man, I'm exhausted.
Um, are you mad at Kaname-kun?
Why?
He's forcing you to join a club.
You've been awfully hard on him today...
We're always like this...
Kaname-kun's just worried about you in his own way.
Being in the middle shortens your lifespan...
Shun.
Kaname-kun?
It's okay!
You get to sleep next to your beloved Kaori-sensei.
I'm fine.
Treasure the moment, okay?
Let's talk about it and decide who'll be in the middle.
Kaname-kun, I didn't know you cared so much...
Kaname-kun showed me he cared a lot.
That was because Yuuta and I...
Let's talk about it and decide who'll be in the middle.
Kaname-kun, I didn't know you cared so much...
Is that true?
Yeah.
But...
Kanme-kun has always cared about us.
Probably...
Please forgive him.
Who cares about that?
Let's get that stamp and get outta here.
Our 17th spring...
That spring, something unchanging and something that's begun to change...
...intertwined like fluttering cherry blossom petals.
Excuse me.
It's just like the Going Home Club?
Yeah.
So what?
Did you really join that club?
Yeah.
Are you stupid?
This sucks! This was all pointless.
But look...
You managed to achieve your goal of getting Yuuki-kun to join a club.
Yeah, that's true.
There's an 80% chance nothing will change, though,
Maybe, but...
I'm sure there'll be plenty of changes to come.
On Our Seventeenth Spring
boku wa nakimushi de kuyashikute dakedo
It pains me to be such a crybaby,
anata ni ima tsutaetain da
but I want to tell you my feelings right now
tada massugu ni boku wo mitsumeru tsuyokute
There you stand, silently gazing at me
Allowing me to answer those strong and gentle eyes of yours
yasashii sono hitomi ni kotaeru tame ni
itsushika miushinatteta ichiban taisetsu na mono mo
You taught me what I lost sight of
sotto anata ga oshiete kureta
What was most important to me
tashika ni sou omoeru kara
I have no doubts about that
boku wa yowamushi de iya datta dakedo
I hated how weak I was
motto motto tsuyoku naru kara
but I will continue to become stronger
anata no koto wo mamoreru you na boku ni naru kara
I will be someone who could protect you
dakara sukoshi mattete
So wait a little longer for me
Next time: "The Day the Tulips Blossomed".
The Day the Tulips Blossomed