Oh, that's the tree I knocked over.
If it's still here, that means...
We can change the dream, right?
Hey, where's Jaune?
Aah!
What?! Let go!
Someone... help!
Jaune?
One, two...
My sword and cape are way too heavy.
This is how Weiss sees him, right?
I guess that means she thinks he can't handle his weapon.
Jaune, are you okay?
I guess I'm okay.
Three coins. What about you guys?
Me too.
Everyone got three.
Use them carefully. Let's go.
Aye yai yai!
I can't stop!
What the heck is that?
Any idea what it's trying to say?
Hmm...
Right, let's do it.
Ready, leader?
Yeah! Everyone get ready.
I'm good to go.
Hngh... Whoa... Phew...
I'm ready, too.
You sure about that?
There it is.
Okay.
Oops!
Everyone go! Hurry!
Roger!
Aah!
Hngh... It's stuck!
Whoa!
Aah! My cape!
Hi-yah!
I never dreamed I'd be
protecting a Company train.
What? Did you say something?
We've passed the spot where
the train stopped before.
Let's keep going!
Thank you. Report.
A train is on its way.
The White Fang infesting the valley
have been driven back at last.
What did you just say?
What in the world is happening?
We're out of the valley.
This is the last one!
Uh-oh! There's something huge up ahead!
Is it really a Company train?
There aren't any statues
of Father outside the city.
What if it's carrying the White Fang?
The train will arrive momentarily.
Will you give the order to open the gate?
You carry a heavy responsibility, Weiss.
Whoa!
Oh!
The gate isn't opening.
Isn't that bad news?
Open up, Weiss!
You carry a heavy responsibility, Weiss.
At this rate, the train
will crash into the gate.
Please, Weiss, open up!
Ice Queen!
Open it!
Don't shut us out! Weiss!
Open the gate!
Eek!
Ah!
It opened!
Amazing! The walls keep opening!
Hah! This must be some
of that dream maintenance!
Hmm?
Whoa! What?!
What in the world is happening?
How far will it go?
Look at the next wall!
The tracks are climbing upwards!
Go as far as you can!
Is that like a station?
The walls are gone,
but something new appeared.
Guess the plan worked, then!
Your plan is up next, leader!
Yeah.
Big Nicholas! Big Nicholas!
We won't be thrown out now.
All right, let's get started with my plan.
Jaune, go ahead.
Achoo!
I'm cold and my nose feels itchy.
My eyes are watery, too.
Having a bad reaction to the Nightmare?
You're still the only one who can move
around freely. We're counting on you!
Achoo!
Finally, finally we were able to
receive a train, Mistress!
Blake defended the train
from the White Fang.
Even Jaune... but why?
You carry a heavy responsibility, Weiss.
Responsibility...
What should I do?
Aah!
Where did those four go?
There's trouble, Sister!
Blake took Ruby, Yang, and Jaune,
and they all rode the train inside!
Silence yourself! I was aware of that.
Huh? Sister, are you trying
to let Faunus into the city?
Ha ha ha ha!
Are you truly worthy to be a child
of the Schnee family, Weiss?
Only I can uphold the Schnee family's pride
and carry out Big Nicholas's will.
Even if the train returns to the city,
the city will not change.
I will make Blake understand that.
He looks really uncomfortable.
Good luck, Jaune.
Good luck, Jaune. I know you can do it.
Sniffle...
Is he gonna be okay?
Ugh, I can't breathe through
my nose. I'm so cold.
I just want a coat.
Huh? Wah!
Ah... achoo!
He's being totally ignored.
Wow, Jaune!
I probably would've taken that as an insult.
Hello, hello!
Wha—!
Big Nicholas!
I'm Dopey Klein, one of the Seven Butlers!
I'm guarding the Sillies here
to make sure they don't esca—
Huh?
Weren't you a Silly, too?
You're not supposed to go outside, dummy!
That's kind of annoying,
coming from a bozo like you.
Would you mind opening up for me?
No way! I gotta keep the Sillies locked up.
But I'm one of them, right?
If you don't open up, I can't get in.
Are you a dummy or something?
Didn't you just say I was?
Oh, right!
Okay, go ahead.
Huh? Why can't I close?
Weird!
Mew! Mew!
Are those for me?
Ah, this helps! Thanks!
I came to let you guys out, but it's
really warm and comfortable here.
My nose stopped
feeling itchy, too. I wonder why.
Isn't this Team RWBY's relic?
Different color, though.
Tee hee hee!
Oh! What the?
I can't close! I can't close!
This is weird!
Wha—!
I wanna be free to go outside!
I wanna go out!
I love festivals!
Gimme a compliment!
I wanna be spoiled!
I wanna play!
Is that... Weiss when she was little?
Did she keep her childhood
feelings locked up all this time?
Is that right, Weiss?
It's from Jaune.
Hello? It's me.
Eh? A relic?
Hold it right there!
As long as my eyes glow red, I, Grumpy
Klein, will not let dummies run free!
I wanna be free!
I wanna play outside with my buddies!
I wanna eat lots of sweets!
I wanna have fun talking to my family!
Jaune!
Ruby. Here you go.
This time it's yellow. Thanks!
It feels like we're totally nailing it!
All of that stuff happening is...
fine, right?
I don't wanna mind my manners!
Yeah, it is.
I wanna play outside with everyone!
The feelings she always kept bottled up
are free now. Isn't that a good thing?
I wanna eat lots of sweets!
Everyone wants to be free.
You can't always keep the things
you care about locked up.
They gotta be free.
Be free...
Be free!
Oh! They talked!
That's the spirit!
You guys are the resistance.
You fight for freedom!
We will fight!
We'll fight!
For freedom!
Let's go!
I wanna be free! I wanna be free!
I wanna be fr—
Augh!
Oh, wow! You carry a
super-heavy responsibility, Sister.
There's no way you could say you're
worthy to be a Schnee now.
Ah! Eek!
Unforgivable.
We got this far coming straight through.
It looks like all the soldiers
went to where Jaune is.
Success!
Let's go.
This time, we have to beat
the Grimm and wake Weiss up!
Ahh, my nose and eyes hurt.
I can't keep this up.
Huh?
Thanks.
Let us fight!
For freedom!
I wanna play! I wanna play!
Let us fight!
For freedom!
I wanna talk to all sorts of people!
I wanna go outside! I wanna go outside!
I wanna have fun! I wanna play all the time!
This is getting kind of crazy.
I wanna make friends!
Whoa!
Let us fight!
For freedom!
What? Why?!
Yikes!
What is happening?
I wanna be spoiled!
I wanna be pampered!
You gotta be kidding.
What in the world...?
What's up with this weather?
What? I think I just saw something!
In the name of Big Nicholas
and the great Schnee Family,
all of you fools will receive
judgment!