This is bad.
Did I wake up from the dream?
She got away from us, Sister.
Klein!
Yes, Mistress Weiss.
Grumpy Klein is here for you.
Mobilize all imperial soldiers
and search for Ruby.
As you wish.
If you truly are suited to be
a daughter of the Schnee Clan,
then carry out your duties, Weiss.
I'll prove to you that I'm worthy.
Are you okay? Are you all the way awake?
Yeah.
I did find the dream Weiss.
But did I fail somehow?
For a first reconnaissance mission,
you performed very well.
Please tell us in detail about
everything you saw and heard.
There was a wall inside the city, too,
but I didn't find the entrance to
the area with the big statue yet.
It seems the closer you
get to the city center,
the deeper you penetrate
into the depths of Weiss's mind.
The city is a fortress that the Nightmare
built out of Weiss's thoughts.
The Nightmare itself should
be inside the core of her mind.
When you saw Weiss inside the dream,
what was she like?
She was really mad.
It seemed like she hated me.
She's the same awake.
Yang...
The Nightmare is trying
to make you believe that.
That is only the Nightmare
exploiting her mind.
Although I'm sure it would be traumatic
if you thought that was
actually her true self.
We should differentiate her
from the original Weiss.
Let's call her Negative Weiss.
Negative? I don't think
I've ever seen a positive Weiss.
Quiet.
Also, Weiss was super strong.
I couldn't handle her at all.
That, too, is because it's inside a dream.
The dream Weiss...
no, the Negative Weiss,
will become as strong as
her mind allows it to be.
Please decide who will enter the
dream by the time my Aura recovers.
I'll go!
This time, I'll go too!
Me too!
If there are too many of us,
they'll spot us right away.
I should go alone.
You want us to leave everything to you?
Well, hey, I am the leader.
What are you talking about?
This isn't only your responsibility.
You couldn't handle her alone,
so it's obvious we should go as a team.
You really don't want us to see
that dream Weiss, do you?
Well, it's...
Huh?! Ah, I get it.
I guess the dream Weiss
must be really nasty.
It's Negative Weiss.
I've been thinking about it
since Weiss fell asleep,
and just like Weiss,
I decided that I don't care.
So I'll be fine.
We can ask Weiss how
she actually feels later.
We're going in together, leader!
Yeah... okay.
Excuse us!
Now what do all of you want?
Class is about to start.
We really wanted to see how
Ruby and the others were doing.
Weiss hasn't woken up yet?
No. We have to go into her dream again.
So she didn't wake up the first time...
We'll still find a way. We're not
coming in second after Team JNPR!
There's no better team for the job.
Did we have that much trouble?
It seems like Jaune's case
wasn't that serious.
Dang, I wish I could get possessed
instead and take her place.
All right, you four get to class.
I'll check in again later.
I have faith in Team RWBY.
Thank you. We'll do our best.
My Aura has recovered.
Silence your hearts,
and entrust yourselves to me.
I will now invite you into the dream.
Only one of my ears is sticking out.
Is this how Weiss imagines me?
Wow, that's so cute!
Blake, it looks great on you!
Um, thanks. What's with the motorcycle?
Heh. Before I even realized, I was riding it.
I guess Weiss knows my tastes!
Check out what happened to my weapon!
See? It shoots out of the wrong end.
I mean, this is cool too,
but if I mess up, I might
shoot someone behind me.
What about you guys?
Mine is pretty much the same.
So is mine.
Maybe it is a little different.
Hmm...
Only you guys got stronger? That isn't fair!
She took it a little too far, if anything.
Save your complaints for Weiss!
Aw, why did she have to
get my Crescent Rose wrong?
Hold it. Don't use those yet.
Let's count how many we have first.
Twelve coins.
If we use up the last one,
we'll get trapped in the dream, right?
We have to use them carefully, one at a time.
Yeah.
Okay, let's go.
What?
It's saying so many things that I don't know
what it means. That's so like Weiss.
I think I had the same reaction.
So that's the train.
Those aren't Grimm...
It's the White Fang...
in Weiss's imagination, I guess.
And we're not supposed to help?
The professor said not to.
Where's the marker?
Over there.
The picture I took of the map is gone!
Maybe everything but Professor Shion's
power gets erased, then?
Hello?
It looks like our Scrolls work, though.
Okay, let's open it.
I think that's a lookout.
Jacques Schnee...
Huh?
He's the head of the Schnee Dust Company.
In other words, Weiss's father.
He looks like kind of a jerk.
Is that the wall?
Doesn't look like it wants to let us in.
Let's all look for the entrance.
Thank you, Klein. Report.
Another train has been attacked.
The White Fang infesting the valley
grow stronger by the day.
How long will it be before we are
able to safely receive trains again?
Ha ha ha ha!
Thankfully, there isn't
a single Faunus in the Empire.
But the girl in the black garments
keeps appearing again and again.
It's quite worrying.
True. I can't get my mind
off her for a moment.
Monitor her very closely.
What about Ruby and Yang?
Master Jacques' gaze has
not fallen upon anyone
who has gone outside without permission.
They should both still reside
quietly in the tower.
We may finally be able to
achieve true peace.
Let us offer a word in prayer
for the time destined to come.
I seriously have no clue what to do.
Big Nicholas!
What?! The door guy?
Why are you here?
That's 'cause the Sillies
are all over the place!
Over here, over there...
I'm keepin' an eye on them!
So, can you connect to the city center, too?
Of course not!
Why would Sillies be anywhere
near the esteemed Schnee family?
What a weirdo!
Oh, okay.
Mirror...
Huh?
Tell me something,
Tell me who's the loneliest of all.
Pyrrha!
She's a singer who likes to sing!
She sings for the city!
Mirror, what's inside of me?
Tell me, can a heart be turned to stone?
Mirror, mirror, what's behind you?
Save me from the things I see.
I can keep it from the world.
Why won't you let me hide from me?
Mirror, mirror...
Ah, Yang? Okay, I'm on my way.
Tell me something.
Who's the loneliest of all?
I'm the loneliest of all.
You're right. That shadow-like thing disappeared.
I wonder if that's the entrance.
If so, then that's in our way.
Wait! Don't waste them!
But it'll be a breeze if we use a decoy.
In that case, leave it to me.
Intruder detected!
Bingo!
Where's Blake?
I'm right here.
What are you doing?
We have lost sight of the intruder.
Hmm...
Yes! We're really close!
Then let's use this.
We can come and go from here.
And we've only used one coin so far.
That gives us a lot to play with!
That's teamwork for you!
All right, let's go wake Weiss up!
A beautiful resting place
to bring about true sleep.
Only daughters worthy of the Schnee name
can enter within.
Sister, we're in trouble!
Tell me anything.
I'll carry out any duty necessary to prove
my worthiness to bear the Schnee family name.
How big is that?!
That's how big of an effect
he's had on Weiss's life.
No kidding. That's really smart, Blake.
Just guessing, anyway.
Message to all imperial subjects.
Ruby Rose and Yang Xiao Long have escaped
from the Tower of our great Nicholas.
If we let them go,
disastrous things will happen.
All subjects of the Empire must work together
to return them to the tower!
What? So in the dream,
we're supposed to be locked up somewhere?
Sounds like it.
Your dream versions disappeared when
you came, so it looks like you escaped.
But just me and Yang? What about Blake?
Ah, yeah, I'm sure it's...
Maybe they haven't noticed
Blake is missing yet.
Or maybe I don't exist
in Weiss's dream in the first place.
If not, I'm worried that Weiss's mind
might treat me as an intruder.
Intruder...
Hey, is that the tower she meant?
It's the only place that makes sense.
You know, if they're trying
to put us back in there,
why don't we just play along?
We surrender! We're surrendering!
What a waste of my time.
Perhaps it would be wise to search
the structures in the perimeter as well,
as we do not yet know where
the girl in black could be lurking.
Oh my, if it isn't Grumpy Klein!
All is well, sir!
No it isn't, you buffoon!
Look at these two, Sleepy Klein!
Oh my! Miss Ruby and Miss Yang.
Whenever did you get past me?
A talking door? Is Weiss okay in the head?
Sis...
Hurry and open up!
Aye-aye, sir!
Huh. Nice room!
All of her favorite things.
Even our bunk bed.
Hmm. Maybe she really did always want one.
Ew, what's this?
Is this a relic?
Hmm...
That is likely a manifestation
of Weiss's will to resist the Nightmare.
A key to enter the depths
of her mind and wake her up.
Please take good care of it.
Understood, Professor.
What did the professor say?
It's a really important item
that might let us
get deep into Weiss's mind and wake her up.
Hold it. What are you doing?
Bringing Blake. Can't I?
Even if you put a door here,
we can't get out, right?
This is supposed to be a jail.
Are you both okay?
Blake!
Did you find a key for the door?
Well... it was a really basic lock.
You can pick locks?
If I ever forget my dorm key,
I'll call you for help!
Shh! Let's go before he wakes up.
Wait.
Maybe one of us should stay.
So Weiss doesn't notice.
Oh, right. Good idea, Ruby!
So who's going to stay?
Yes!
Sheesh.
I'll stay, but I want to
leave a marker, too. All right?
I think that's best.
Use one of your coins, Sis.
Okay, okay.
Miss Ruby, Miss Yang, are you there?
We're here! Go back to sleep.
When I looked around, I found
a door that goes underground.
It might lead to the core
of her mind, like the professor said.
Wow, Blake!
Even when you were on your way to
save us, you were checking things out.
I didn't spend a lot of time.
I hope that's useful for something.
I think there might be another one, too.
Another one?
This one was where we were,
so I bet there's one where
your dream version was, too.
I mean, there are two
relics in real life, too.
I'm opening it.
Okay.
What is this place?
I don't think we'll be able
to go straight through.
As expected.
No matter how many times
I expel you, you keep reappearing.
I already told you.
In this place,
there's no room for Faunus.