I wanna make friends!
For freedom!
Yikes!
What is happening?
I wanna go outside!
I wanna go on a trip!
I wanna be pampered!
What in the world...?
Why'd the weather suddenly change?
Huh?
What? I think I just saw something!
In the name of Big Nicholas
and the great Schnee Family,
all of you fools will receive...
judgment!
What now? Are we supposed
to fight a building?
If we get inside, it can't touch us.
That's a big "if."
I'll go in.
Then I'll use a coin inside to make a door.
All right. We'll distract it.
Don't be so reckless! Ruby, I'll...
It isn't reckless.
I can handle this.
Now isn't the time to treat me like a child.
Uh...
Let's believe in our leader, Yang.
Yeah.
All right then, fine!
Okay, here we go!
Oh? Aah!
I wanna play more!
I wanna go outside when I want to!
I wanna have fun talking to Daddy and Mommy!
I want them to spoil me!
Dad...dy. Mom...my.
Re...spon...si...bil...ity...
I wanna have fun! I wanna be fr—
Coin, coin...
It's Jaune, Professor!
The dream is out of control!
If the changes are too much,
her heart will start to resist them.
The Nightmare is taking advantage
of the resistance from Weiss's heart.
There's no turning back now.
If you can't get her to stop resisting,
then Weiss will no longer
have the means to wake up.
Easier said than done.
Aah!
Freedom!
For freedom!
I will allow you to behave
as freely as you please,
as long as you are tightly
locked up on the other side.
This way, you will remain pure.
I spotted a dummy!
Aah! What? A bat?
I'm going to tell my sister
that you're all he—
Gyah!
Sister? Did he mean Weiss?
It looks like Ruby got inside!
Let's go back!
Success! You did it again, Ruby!
We've still got work to do, Sis.
Let's get going.
We have to defeat the Grimm this time.
Oh...
Roger, leader!
Okay, let's go.
I'll do whatever it takes to wake her up.
You...
are merely one of the Sillies.
Wha—!
Be a good boy and return
to where you belong.
That isn't going to happen.
I'm going to make you wake up, Ice Queen!
Aah!
Ow! Ugh.
Remain in there for eternity.
If you do not, you will receive my judgment.
All the way back here again.
Hey, let me out of here!
I know you can hear me, Dopey Klein!
Aah!
The Grimm!
Run!
Aah!
How'd the Grimm get in here?
Huh?
Is it because I took the relic?
A door!
Door! Door!
The train's down there!
It isn't coming in. I wonder why.
Hold on a second, guys.
Hello, Jaune!
The Negative Weiss... Professor...
the heart resisting...
Jaune? I can't hear you well.
What's happening, Ruby?
Is something wrong with the scroll?
Aah!
The Nightmare is aware of us. Let's hurry.
Open!
It is time for your judgment.
Weiss?
Aah!
Yang?!
After all that you two have done,
I'm sure you are prepared
for what comes next.
Wait, Weiss!
Blake!
Ow!
You are banished from this city for eternity,
and will never see me again.
Weiss?!
You won't be needing this anymore.
Don't! Stop, Weiss!
Farewell, Ruby.
It's me, Ruby.
Jaune...
Where's Yang and Blake?
Weiss used her powers
to make them both disappear.
She said "banish," so they're
probably outside of the city.
Then I'll go searching for them.
Thanks. I'm going back.
I have to beat the Grimm.
It'll be impossible alone.
But...!
Anyway, we need to think of a new plan.
Do you have any coins? I used mine up.
Yeah.
Sillies? Here... on the train?
Yeah. I'll tell you what happened.
Listen...
Yang.
Oh! Blake.
Did Weiss throw you over here, too?
Yeah.
I thought I'd been thrown back to the start,
but it doesn't look like it.
I wonder if there are any more dummies.
And, because of that,
the Nightmare can't get in.
I guess it has to do with the immunity
the Professor talked about.
So, because you took the relic,
the Grimm turned those girls
into monsters or something?
That, and they probably
weren't supposed to be set free.
Huh?
Remember what Pyrrha and Ren said
before we started the operation?
She was protecting them
because they're precious to her.
She wasn't imprisoning them.
Then why did she lock them up?
You can't become an adult if you
cling to your childhood emotions.
Like wanting to eat sweets or play all day.
If you don't take responsibility
and control those feelings,
your life gets out of control.
Did I do the wrong thing to Weiss?
I selfishly thought I was helping her,
but didn't even consider how she felt.
Team JNPR is pretty great, huh?
Huh?
You really think about your team.
You empathize.
You're able to help each other.
Ruby...
I wasn't even worried about Weiss.
I never imagined something
like this happening.
Pyrrha noticed when it happened to you,
but I didn't notice a thing.
Don't talk like that, Ruby.
Aren't you fighting to save her right now?
Team RWBY is... an embarrassment.
I really have... no right to lead.
Ruby?
Huh?
Ruby!
I'm sorry, Weiss. I'm so sorry.
What bad taste!
What is this?
Big Nicholas!
Ew. Another door is talking.
Who are you?
I'm Bashful Klein.
I lock up the people who
aren't allowed in the Empire.
Aren't allowed in?
You mean Faunus like me?
Yes, that's right.
Now that you mention it,
when did you get outside?
Blake...
This is,
in Weiss's mind,
the place where I belong.
H-H-Heavy... r-responsibility.
Ha ha ha!
Thank you, Klein. Report.
The imperial subjects are calm,
Mistress Weiss.
Now that true order
and discipline has returned,
those who are suited to the Schnee Family
may attain true sleep.
True sleep...
Is it just me?
Where is everyone?
Ruby,
looks like you're awake.
Weiss!
Weiss, you woke up!
Yes, Ruby, thanks to you.
You're my best friend in the world,
and a fantastic leader!
I couldn't have done it by myself.
Hee hee...
Dad? Zwei?
Ha ha ha!
Eh?
Huh?