Today is the day when a fresh
crop of new students arrives at Beacon Academy.
Let's all hope they become excellent Huntsmen
who can protect the peace for our people.
Now for our next story.
After the entrance ceremony,
students will be split into teams.
It'll be crucial to get into the right team.
Outta my way!
This is crazy, Ren!
The bus is actually flying!
We've already been flying
for two hours, Nora,
and I keep telling you
that it's an airship, not a bus.
Does anyone have something for motion sickness?
I've never been anywhere this noisy!
That girl...
Pyrrha Nikos!
I get to go to Beacon with my
favorite sister. This is the best!
You skipped two years, so I bet they're
gonna start calling you a girl genius.
I don't want to stick out that much.
And I enrolled without knowing anyone here.
Why don't you make some friends?
It isn't that easy for me.
I'll just stay with you all the time!
I'd like that, but...
It's great that you support each other,
but it's not good for Ruby
if she's always depending on you.
Ahem.
All right! Let's make friends!
Eh?
Let's see, who's by themselves and looks bored?
Over there. Let's go!
H-Hey, Sis!
Hello! Got a minute?
I'm Yang, and this
is my cute baby sister, Ruby.
What's your name?
Blake.
Blake! Isn't the weather lovely today?
Almost as lovely as this book
that I'll continue to read
as soon as you both leave.
Oh.
Hey, what book is that?
It's about a man with two souls,
each fighting for control over his body.
Huh. Weird.
I like books, too!
Reading stories about heroes was what
made me want to be a Huntress.
Because they all have a happy ending?
The real world isn't
the same as a fairy tale.
That's why we're here! To make it a better place.
Nice one, Ruby! I'm so
proud of my baby sister!
Cut it out, Yang!
Now for our next story.
A riot broke out when members of the White Fang
forced their way into
a recent Faunus rights protest.
Suspicious of the White Fang's involvement
in a series of Dust robberies,
the Schnee Dust Company,
industry leader in the Dust trade,
The Schnee Dust Company
is really well known, huh?
is considering fortifying its security division
and is increasing precautions.
Rumor has it they're
the most corrupt in the world.
And they treat their workers like slaves.
What did you just say?
What do you two think you know?
Who are you supposed to be?
I'm Weiss Schnee, the company's heiress.
Seriously?
Um, we didn't mean to say
anything bad about you!
We've just heard those rumors...
Rumors?
You're swallowing every lie
the anti-human Faunus
and their lowlife group of thieves,
the White Fang, are feeding you.
Come on now, take it easy.
The White Fang used to be a pacifist group.
At least until your company
started exploiting the powerless.
Are you on the Faunus' side?
You're totally ignorant if you
think every Faunus is evil.
Why, how dare you...!
Wait, wait! We just got
off on the wrong foot.
Why don't we start over?
We're all Beacon students,
so let's try to get along.
Well said, Sis!
Hi Blake, Weiss. My name is Ruby.
Wanna go shopping?
We could go looking for school supplies.
Yeah!
Wanna, like, get all dressed up,
and go shopping and talk about cute boys?
Like him?
Hmm?
Wow, really?!
You've got to be kidding!
Please don't ever speak to me again.
I'm so bad at making friends.
Don't worry, Ruby.
Welcome to Beacon.
I'm Glynda Goodwitch,
one of your instructors.
Professor Ozpin has something to say to you.
You have all trained to become warriors.
Today, the true worth of your training
will be evaluated
in the Emerald Forest test.
A test? Already?
Dad told us, remember?
Make your way to the old temple and
eliminate any Grimm that get in your way.
If you don't, your life is forfeit.
In the forest, partner with the first
person you make eye contact with.
Two pairs will combine
to form a four-person team.
These will be your teammates
for your four years of study.
Hopefully, you can get along together.
Partners? Teams? Nobody told me about that!
Dad told you...
The temple contains several relics.
Choose one and bring it
back to Beacon Cliff.
We will monitor you, but will not intervene.
You must make it through on your own.
We will arrive at the test
starting point shortly.
Please prepare yourselves before then.
May you be victorious.
How do you do? My name is Weiss.
I overheard you earlier. I'm...
Pyrrha Nikos. Right?
Does she mean that Pyrrha?
The real thing?!
Would you like to team up?
I'm sure we'd be unbeatable together.
We'd get top grades
and be set for the future!
Right. I'll think about it.
I'm sure we'd be top of the class!
Hey!
I'm Jaune Arc.
You said I was your type, right?
Huh?
It sounds like we form
our teams in the forest.
I was thinking you and me
would make a good one.
Actually, I think the teams
are comprised of four students each.
You don't say.
Play your cards right and maybe you
could join up with the winning team.
Do you have any idea
who you are talking to?
She graduated top of her class at Sanctum,
and won the Mistral Regional
Tournaments four years in a row.
This is Pyrrha.
Huh, no kidding.
She's on the front of the Pumpkin
Pete's Marshmallow Flakes box!
Wow! Awesome!
But I never really liked that cereal.
Actually, me neither. It isn't very healthy.
Really? No kidding.
Step back!
Why?
Nobody invited you!
Oh, I'm sorry.
My dad said all that women look
for in a man is confidence.
Where did I go wrong?
We will now begin the initiation.
Take your positions.
Well then everyone, have a safe landing.
What? We're going on this?
Nice! Isn't this fun?
I've got a bad feeling...
Woo-hoo!
Yeah!
I wonder what kinds
of teams we'll get this year.
And what kinds of leaders
will appear, right?
I thought you went on a journey
in search of your prey, Shion Zaiden.
And that's exactly why I'm here, Professor.
So that Grimm is here?
Yes. The test may become dangerous.
There's no such thing
as a safe initiation test.
You believe that future Huntsmen should
be able to overcome any difficulty?
Of course. I also hope that
your hunt ends in success.
You never change.
Well, then. Until next time.
Where are you, Yang?
I don't wanna get split up!
That was close.
Yang! Yang!
Where in the world is Pyrrha?
Aren't we supposed to be partners now?
Somebody, help!
Hey! No, wait! Don't go!
What? What?
Let's get moving.
Even if I'm paired with her, as long
as I can get on Pyrrha's team...
Damn it! Come off!
Ouch, ouch...
Hi, Jaune.
Do you have any spots left on your team?
Ruby! Where are you?
Ruby!
Ruby?!
Hey, what's the hurry?
I don't want to be delayed and
lose time because you're so slow.
See? I'm not slow.
A Semblance?
I'll show you what I can do.
I bet you'll give me a second chance then!
Quit showing off your
abilities like a child.
Hey, wait!
Come on...
And you look like a child, too.
Were you really old enough to enroll?
Well, that's... I skipped ahead.
You skipped?
So you are younger than me.
Take that!
Wow, that was...
Nice working with you.
Remember your training, Weiss!
You're in the way!
No, you are!
Duck!
Huh?!
You got them in one shot!
You must have some amazing Dust!
The Schnee family really...
It's your fault that I set
the forest on fire.
All you do is waste Aura and Dust.
Do you think you can
pass the test doing that?
Quit complaining!
I wasn't trying to insult you!
I've already long forgotten
what you said in the airship.
No you haven't, and that's
why you're being so mean to me.
Fine! I won't be your partner.
I'll do it myself.
Wow!
You're so tough, you can ignore
the rules and do it all yourself.
Bravo!
You're not just slow, you also
have a temper. You're the worst.
I'm going to keep going.
You're so arrogant! I hate you!
You think you're perfect, don't you?
No, I'm not perfect.
But I'm still leagues better than you.
Hmm.
A bunch of them are missing.
I guess we weren't first.
Which one should we pick?
How about the cute pony?
Yee-haw!
Take... this!
Aw, it's broken.
Nora, would you please try
to fight normally?
That girl was riding an Ursa.
Impressive!
I got the castle relic!
I'm queen of the castle!
You're the king, Ren!
Whatever.
Ruby!
Ruby, I'm so glad you're okay!
Yang!
Hurry and take the relic!
Which one?
It doesn't matter!
Jaune, get the relic first!
O-Okay!
Um, this?
Pyrrha!
I finally found you, Pyrrha!
There's one above too! Let's go!
The test is to bring back a relic,
not to defeat those things.
Are you gonna just run?
I'm all for that!
But the Professor said we'd
have to kill the Grimm!
We have to go now!
Well, that's great!
This is bad.
We'll just have to fight!
Here I go!
Jaune, go ahead!
The bridge...
Damn it! We're in trouble!
Nothing is working!
We'll have to get close!
Jaune!
Ren!
Come on!
We have to predict its movements.
Weiss, please help me!
Ren!
Pyrrha! The tail!
Okay!
Take this!
Nora, nail it!
Heads up! Here I go!
Take this!
We made it...
Ren! Are you okay?
I'm all right, Nora.
Yang!
Come on!
Whee!
Of course you would come up with this.
If I show you my awesome moves,
will you give me a second chance?
You're trying to show off again?
What a child.
No. I just want you to know
I can really fight.
I already knew.
Hurry!
Ruby!
Okay. Weiss, now!
Finish him off!
Success.
It seems they've already
found the hiding place.
Good work. Let's prepare for the worst.
Jaune Arc, Pyrrha Nikos,
Lie Ren, and Nora Valkyrie,
the four of you retrieved the white rook.
From this day forward, you are Team JNPR...
We did it, Ren!
Nora...
...led by Jaune Arc.
You'll be a wonderful leader.
Huh... Yeah.
Finally, Ruby Rose, Weiss Schnee,
Blake Belladonna, and Yang Xiao Long,
the four of you retrieved the white knight.
From this day forward, you are Team RWBY,
led by Ruby Rose.
Huh?
You did it! You're amazing, Ruby!