Team RWBY, mission one!
Redecorating complete!
Not bad.
It looks really comfortable.
I've never seen a bunk bed before.
Okay, our next mission is class!
You're always so excited for everything...
Beasts of destruction
and carnage—the Grimm.
While much of their nature remains a mystery,
we have learned a few things.
Grimm are born and raised in the darkness,
where they learn to be very vigilant.
When Grimm die, they immediately
return to dust,
and they are thought to have no soul.
It is the Huntsman's duty
to wield this knowledge in battle.
Do any of you wish to test your skills?
How did they capture that thing?
Go get 'em, Weiss!
Represent Team RWBY! Yay!
Be quiet!
Begin!
Its weak point is its belly! Go low!
Stop telling me what to do!
You did it! You did it, Weiss!
Huh?
Wait up, Weiss!
Hey, what are you so mad about?
Hey!
Quit babbling like a child!
Are you really so happy about being team leader
when you barely did anything?
I just want us to work
together as a team and—
Not a team led by you!
Wait, please!
Let Ruby handle it. If she doesn't deal
with this herself, it'll keep happening.
After studying and
training myself to death...
I deserve better than this.
Weiss?
Come on.
Weiss, where are you?
I don't think I'm fit to be a leader, either.
At this rate, they're gonna tell me
I don't even belong at Beacon.
That remains to be seen.
Professor Port.
May I speak with you?
I do not consider your appointment
as leader to be a mistake.
But Weiss doesn't agree.
She says I haven't made any effort.
Of course, nobody will follow a leader
that doesn't do their best.
Take some time and think about
how you should carry out your responsibilities.
And you think making you
team leader would solve everything?
Your skills are exceptional,
but your attitude is a problem.
They cancel each other out.
Wha... How dare you!
My point exactly.
You've probably spent your whole
life getting exactly what you wanted.
That isn't... true. At all!
Instead of throwing tantrums,
try to become the best person,
the best teammate you can be.
You'll soon realize that it
doesn't matter who the leader is.
Go for it!
You can do it, Jaune!
Hang in there!
Calm down and keep your eyes on him!
You can do it, Jaune! Team JNPR!
Oh. Am I too loud?
No. Cheering needs to be loud.
That's enough.
As you can see, Jaune's Aura has been
greatly reduced from taking damage.
You must choose a fighting style
that fits within the limits of your Aura.
Aura is present in all
living things, except Grimm.
See, you have to release the Aura
that sleeps inside you.
I'm glowing.
But what is this good for?
It is your strongest shield
and your most powerful weapon.
As your Aura grows, your own
unique power will also awaken.
That's your Semblance.
Do your best.
Okay. I will.
How was he able to enroll
when he didn't even know about Aura?
But what's more important is that
Pyrrha unquestioningly accepted
that useless Jaune as team leader.
Maybe you can score more points
by being a perfect teammate
and supporting a poor leader,
rather than becoming a leader yourself.
That must be it.
Weiss...
Oh, I fell asleep!
Shh.
Cream and five sugars.
Just how you like it, right?
Here. Coffee.
I know you'll become a good leader.
Huh?
I've decided to be the best teammate I can.
Good luck studying.
Thanks.
I always wanted a bunk bed.
This is more exhausting than I thought.
My own unique power...
It'll never happen.
The truth is, you've
got no right to be here.
Don't you agree?
Jaune, it's time for class. Wake up.
What's wrong? Did he catch a cold?
He must be tired from training.
Something's wrong with his Aura.
It's my target. We need to
begin immediately.
My name is Shion Zaiden.
I'm a Nightmare Hunter.
What's a Nightmare?
A type of Grimm that possesses humans
and grows by draining their Aura.
The possessed victim is trapped in their dreams,
as their body becomes
a breeding ground for Grimm.
So we just have to kill the Grimm?
Yes, inside his dream.
Inside his dream?
It's a task for his close friends.
If a stranger tries,
his heart will reject them.
Are any of you willing to enter
his dream to battle the Grimm?
Absolutely. We'll go.
For generations, males of the Arc Clan
have been fated to become glorious warriors.
And then you showed up.
What a disappointment you are, Jaune.
You incompetent, miserable coward.
No... I know I can do it.
I can do it!
Big Sis, I'm scared. Help me!
Jaune!
Who's there?
We've come to get you, Jaune.
It's me.
Did you find him safely?
Very well. You must fight to set him free.
They were able to find Jaune.
That was quick. Excellent.
The care they show for each other
is what makes them a good team.
Pyrrha...
Now it's your turn to be trapped, Nightmare.
Stay in there, and turn back into a seed.
A seed... It's like a plant.
Typically, Grimm take on a beast form.
But some Grimm are unique.
Keep that in mind.
I overslept! Is class—
What's going on?
I'm glad we caught it before it grew.
It's probably because his Aura
is still undeveloped.
His Semblance hasn't awakened,
and his Aura in combat is below average.
I'm glad you're safe, Jaune.
That proved fortunate for him.
Thanks.
I've never seen someone benefit
from a weakness before.
I sensed other Nightmares
in the forest, too.
The more sensitive or emotionally
conflicted you are,
the more susceptible you become.
Please tell the students to remain diligent.
Listen up, everyone.
If you're feeling down,
talk to each other about it.
You must be joking.
You can't possibly expect
a Grimm to possess me.
Yeah. I'm sure you'll be fine, Weiss.
It certainly does seem unlikely.
She's got her own thorns
to use for keeping Grimm out.
I don't think I like the sound of that.
Anyway, since tomorrow's a day off,
shall we go into town?
The festival is soon, too.
Festival?
I didn't know you liked festivals, Weiss.
That's a surprise.
What happened here?
Hmm?
Another robbery.
They took the Dust and left everything else.
Probably the White Fang up
to their old tricks. Excuse me.
The White Fang again? What a bunch
of violent, crazed degenerates.
They're a collection of misguided Faunus.
They say they're going to wipe
humanity off the face of the planet.
That's only a small minority!
And we don't even know
if Faunus did this to begin with.
Blake's got a point.
The Dust robbery I saw was done by humans.
Stop that Faunus!
You no-good stowaway!
You trash!
If I were trash, you'd already
have collected me.
My skills at stowing away are second to none.
What a weird comeback.
Hold it right there!
Fine. I'll capture that Faunus
and show you just how bad he is.
Wait! Weiss!
Ah!
Are you okay?
I am fine, but...
Are you? Can you get up?
Yes! I am wonderful. Thank you for asking!
And-a upsy-daisy.
My name is Penny.
It is a pleasure to meet you.
Very nice to meet you, friend.
If we don't hurry, the vagabond will get away.
What did you call me?
She wasn't talking about you.
No. You.
Did you just call me "friend"?
Uh, yeah.
Grin!
How touching! I have made a friend!
I'm so glad I came to Vale!
What is with her?
Sorry, but we're in a hurry.
All right. Be well.
Let's give up. He's just a stowaway, right?
He's a law-breaking scoundrel.
If we let him go, he'll surely
join the White Fang.
That's wrong! This is why
you're so ignorant.
What did you just say to me?
You're being prejudiced.
You treat all Faunus like criminals.
If he's a scoundrel, then so are you.
It's an organization of pure evil
that hates humanity.
How can you defend them?
There's no such thing as pure evil!
People like you drove the Faunus into a corner.
Please don't fight, you two.
Have you attended any of the
funerals of the people they killed?
Do you know the pain of the families
whose loved ones were killed
just for being Company board members?
Do you have any idea how much
they've made me suffer?
Well, maybe we were just
tired of being pushed around!
"We"?
Blake, where are you going?
I thought so.
I knew you'd look better without the bow.
Did you find Blake?
No. She might not be at the harbor.
We should just leave her be.
She's our teammate!
You heard what she said.
So you're going to treat
her like a criminal?
I'll go check by the warehouse.
Huh?
Hey... Ruby!
If you're going to hate her just for being
a Faunus, then you really are a bigot.
I... Maybe I went too far.
But that organization is—
That's enough about the organization.
Wha—
Wait a minute. You were
a member of the White Fang?
That's right. I was a member
for most of my life.
Stupid creeps that use force to get whatever they want...
That doesn't seem like you.
The White Fang was supposed to be
a bridge between humans and the Faunus.
But they changed, so I left.
I wanted to dedicate my life
to something truly important.
So, have you told your friends any of this?
Then, what's your plan now?
I want to find out who's
behind these Dust robberies.
You know, someone was talking
about it on the ship.
A Schnee Company freighter
is bringing in a load of Dust.
You're sure?
To replace what was stolen.
The thieves must feel like the goods
are being delivered straight to them.
Where could Blake be?
You mean the Faunus girl?
Where did you come from?!
Wait, how did you know that?
Because of her cat ears.
Ears? Not a bow?
I saw her with it off, too.
Where?
You don't care about her at all, do you?
I bet you're only pretending
to be nice to my sister, too.
Like making up that stuff
about always wanting a bunk bed.
Why don't you say something?!
I don't know what to do!
I couldn't become the leader,
couldn't even get on Pyrrha's team,
and now one of my teammates is a Faunus!
Nothing is turning out the
way I imagined it. I...
She's crying?
Oh, come on.
You don't have to help me.
I'm already on board.
You know I'm an expert stowaway, right?
All right. Take all of the cargo.
The White Fang!
They're not supposed to work with humans.
I guess they changed their minds.
Hey, what are you doing?!
What was that sound?
That was a gunshot.
You spoil Ruby.
That's why she's always showing off
her abilities to get praise.
Am I wrong?
Okay, fine.
But why don't you stop bragging
about being the perfect teammate,
and actually think about
what it means to be a friend?
It's a Dust robbery! Hurry!
Damn it! What is that monster?
Swoosh!
Battle complete.
What in the world happened?
Ruby! Blake!
Weiss!
Blake isn't in the White Fang anymore,
and she has cat ears under her bow.
Isn't that cute?
Huh? Really?
Weiss, I haven't been in the organization—
I don't want to hear any more
about the organization.
But I have been thinking about things.
I kept thinking, thinking,
thinking, and decided...
I don't care about any of it.
You don't care?
Right. So, the next time
you have a big problem,
come and talk to your teammates,
not some stranger.
All right.
There it is.
Team RWBY is back together!
You're celebrating a little too much.
I wasn't lying about always wanting one.
You've buried all your dreams
that didn't come true,
and it takes all your strength
to pretend not to care.
The Faunus, the White Fang...
You will never be able to forgive them.
What... What is this... thing?