Otani-kun~
Good morning~
Gross!
What do you mean, "gross"?!
Is that the kind of attitude you should have towards your girlfriend?
Don't you think your attitude is a little arrogant?
I've suffered a lot up until now.
I need compensation.
What do you mean, "compensation"?
A-chan!
Good morning.
Ah, this girl is...
...Otani's neighbor.
Meimei-chan!
It's Mimi!
Your girlfriend sure is funny.
Oh no! We're gonna be late!
That's because you took so long.
That's because you were being stupid.
See ya, Mimi-chan.
Declaration of War!! The Dangerous Beauty Who Burns With Jealousy!!
What's this?! Why didn't you tell us?!
When did this happen?
I see. Congratulations.
What did you say when you asked her out?
Oh? That's great. Congratulations.
Is it true, Senpai?
Ahdsakafajdags!
This is wonderful.
I'm so moved!
So the comedy duo is finally a couple.
Congratulations!
Thank you.
Don't make such a big deal out of it.
Why?!
Please tell me why, Risa!
Think about this seriously! It's weird! Choosing a guy like that...
What do you mean, "a guy like that"?
Beat it, mini-man!
Don't get cocky.
Who's getting cocky?!
You...
Fine...
I knew this day would come eventually.
Oh... that's right.
Sensei was looking for you two earlier.
It's over already?
Did you forget to do your summer homework?
Yes.
Sorry.
Well, at this stage there's nothing more that can be said.
Just turn it in by Monday.
Yes.
I totally forgot about it.
Let's work on it together.
Where?
Do you want to go to the library with Suzuki and the others?
Bad idea.
If I'm in a quiet place like the library, I'll be all "eek".
It will be all "eek", won't it?
Want to come to my place?
Welcome home, A-chan.
So you brought your girlfriend over?
What are you doing here?
I brought today's milk for you.
M-Milk?
She brings me milk everyday, saying it'll make me taller.
Today I've brought something really great.
This is high calcium milk, straight from the pastures of Hokkaido.
What's so funny?!
Well, milk...
If there's nothing else, hurry up and go home.
Awww. But I wanted to chat with your girlfriend.
No. We're gonna study now, so you can't.
It's okay, Otani. It'll just be for a bit.
Yeah!
Just for a bit, okay?
Understood.
A-chan, could you come here for a sec?
What is it? Geez...
How cute...
Mimi-chan, you're pretty tall and slim.
How tall are you?
172cm.
Wow! Same as me!
Really?
But A-chan always said he'd never go out with a girl taller than him.
Ah. That'd be right.
But he doesn't seem to mind my height for some reason.
Hey, did you know that A-chan's last girlfriend was really short?
Yeah, I know.
She was small and cute.
That's why I gave up on A-chan.
You like Otani, Mimi-chan?
But A-chan only likes short girls...
...and I'm tall.
That's why I bring him milk everyday, so that he'll grow taller.
I-I see...
I decided that when A-chan grew taller than me, I'd become his girlfriend.
Um... uh... Sorry, I guess...
Damn. I missed.
"Sorry"?
You've got some nerve!
What kind of dirty trick did you pull to get him, eh?
Do you want me to thread a noodle through your nostrils and tie a chignon?
Noo. No, I don't...
A-chan can't possibly have a girlfriend like toy.
M-M-Mimi-chan...
Don't say my name in that disgusting voice!
If you get any closer to A-chan,
I'll make what's left of your life extremely painful.
I brought tea.
Otani! Save me!
Cake! Cake!
I want the Mont Blanc cake!
Can I start?
G-Go ahead.
Your girlfriend is really nice!
Was that a hallucination just now?
What's the matter, Koizumi?
Uh... Nothing.
It wasn't a hallucination.
What's up with you?
Mimi, after you finish that, go home, okay?
Okay.
I had no idea she was a model.
So that's Otani's neighbor?
She looks amazing.
Oh, it's Mimi.
Saying anything to Otani would be pointless.
Well, there's no point in worrying.
Want to go have some fun, now that we've turned in our homework?
Let's! Let's!
No matter what happens to me or what's said to me,
I'll be happy as long as I have Otani's love.
A-chan!
What are you doing here?
Your girlfriend and I are really getting along,
We're going to hang out together today, Right?
Right, right. In that case, you two go on ahead.
What about you, A-chan?
I don't want to walk home stuck between two amazons.
You'll look like a captured alien.
I'll smack you!
Man...
Ah! Wa-Wait! Otani!
Hey.
Get it yet, hag?
We need to have a little talk.
Why has it come to this?
She's totally staring me down.
How did someone like you manage to get to the point of going out with A-chan?
I-I worked really hard!
You idiot! I've been working really hard too!
I'm really cute when I'm with A-chan, aren't I?
I've been acting like that ever since I met him.
Do you have any idea how tiring that is?
Th-That would be difficult...
And that's not all.
I give A-chan milk every single day,
But he hasn't grown at all since his first year of middle school.
Seriously?
Seriously.
I, on the other hand, was already over 170cm when I was in elementary school.
I was already 168cm when I was in sixth grade.
No way. Are you serious?
Man, I've been put back because of my height since I was in kindergarten.
Me too! Me too!
I was even taller than the tallest boy.
Me too!
It's a real pain, huh?
No matter what you do, you always draw attention.
Totally.
If you talk, even just for a second, the teacher always sees-
Hey! Why the hell am I reminiscing with an idiot like you?!
Uh... You were trying to catch me off guard?
Shut up!
When A-chan was going out with that short, cute girl, I completely gave up.
Naturally. You'd think you had no chance with your height.
I understand.
Right?
That girl was really sweet.
I thought that deep down she would've been nasty.
Yeah. She's not like you, Mimi-chan.
Yeah, yeah. Deep down I'm really a nasty-
Shut that damn mouth of yours!
Who the hell are you calling "nasty", you idiot?!
S-Sorry.
So after he broke up with that great girlfriend, he moved on to this?
Tall and stupid!
In any case, I'm not going to lose to you.
I'm definitely going to win A-chan back.
That's all I have to say.
W-Wait!
What is it?
So...Sorry. Could you lend me some money?
I only have 50 yen on me.
50...
You've got some guts, walking into a family restaurant with only that much cash on you!
I forgot that I bought a magazine today.
You looked so cute and sweet that I totally forgot.
Well, I guess that can't be helped.
It was a special situation today, so I'll lend you some money.
Wow. You sure are nice.
I think I left my purse at work. What should we do?!
What should we do?!
No idea...
The total comes to 630 yen.
What were you thinking?
I'm really sorry.
A-chan.
Just what is it that you like about her?
What's this, all of a sudden?!
Well, she's nothing like your last girlfriend.
She's taller than you,
and she goes to family restaurants with only 50 yen on her.
I just can't see what's so great about her.
This isn't the time or place to talk about this.
Tell me! I need to know!
You don't need to. It's not like it's any of your business.
Otani...
It is my business!
I like you much more than she does!
Mimi-chan...
Are you serious?
You're an idiot, A-chan!
Mimi?
I'll go after her.
Huh? Wai-
After all, I understand how Mimi-chan feels.
Did A-chan say anything?
Is he angry at me?
No. he's not angry.
But I... I yelled at him and called him an idiot.
You're an idiot, A-chan!
You don't need to worry about that.
He really is an idiot, after all.
How could he say that in response to a confession? That idiot...
A-chan is not an idiot!
Anyone would be shocked by a sudden confession like that!
I'm the one who was in the wrong.
Don't say bad things about A-chan!
I've never talked to him that way before.
I lost it and said something I shouldn't have...
This is all your fault, you cow!
It's your fault that my life is falling apart!
What are you gonna do about it, eh?!
Cat got your tongue? Why don't you try responding?
Are you lookin' for a fight, you dumb bitch?!
Mi...mi?
Oh dear...
She must be really down now that you've seen her true colors.
What do you mean by that?
Are you trying to tell me that the Mimi I know...
...is fake?
Of course she wants to act all cute in front of the guy she likes.
I do it too!
Gross, gross.
What do you mean, "gross"?!
See? There you go.
How is that cute?
This happens because you say pointless things-
Well, never mind that.
Has Mimi-chan contacted you?
Yeah.
She said the three of us should do something after school today.
W-Why?
Now that her cover is blown, Mimi-chan's going to get serious, right?
What do you mean by "serious"?
What would happen to an idiot like Otani if a pretty girl like her got serious about him?
I'm not going to lose!
I'm not going to let all of my efforts go to waste!
We'll go wherever you want, A-chan.
That's okay, right?
It's fine.
H-Hold on, you two...
Let's go, A-chan.
Please, just go away, both of you.
Sweet!
What should we play? What should we play?
That one's free. Let's go!
Awesome!
A-chan?
Where's Mimi-chan?
There you are.
Mimi-chan, come play with us.
I'm going home.
What?
I'm going home!
Mimi!
There's something I need to say to you properly.
I don't want to hear it.
You're going to reject me, right?
Mimi-chan...
Mimi...
No.
Mimi.
I said no!
Mimi! Listen to me!
No! I don't want to hear it!
About Koizumi, I...
No!!! No!!! Stop!!!
Mimi!
No!!!
I...
Don't say it!!!
Idiot!
Wh-What the...
I thought you liked Otani more than me!
Was that all just talk?
You're his girlfriend! Like you'd know how it feels to be rejected!
I do know! I was rejected too! Twice!
I thought about giving up too,
but in the end I kept trying.
No way.
I might be his girlfriend now,
but he calls me an idiot, and says I'm gross all the time.
I can hardly tell whether he actually likes me or not.
Hey, what're you sayi-
But I love him more than I can say, so it's fine.
I'm not going to give Otani up to someone who just runs away when they get rejected.
So, did Mimi-chan storm off?
No, no.
She said she can't deal with an idiot like you, so she's giving up on me.
What's up with that?
It must have hurt her a lot the first time you rejected her.
But she worked hard to win you over.
She really is amazing, that girl.
What was that you were saying back there?
Something about not being able to tell whether I actually like you or not, wasn't it?
Ahh, that was just...
You deliberately stood on higher steps.
Well, it wouldn't have been as cool if we were standing on level ground.
Let's go.
A lot has happened...
but from now on, I hope we can be together like this...
...forever.
Are you writing test questions?
Ah, no.
I was just looking over what the students aim to do in the future.
It's almost time for them to make their final decisions, isn't it?
That it is.
It looks like All Hanshin-Kyojin will finally have a break up.
Career Guidance Questionnaire Name: Otani Atsushi Future Plans University
Are you going to go to a university?
Impossible!
Huh?
What are we going to do while your away, Otani?
Lovely Complex~ Love Com.
Next: Premonition of Separation?! The Different Paths Risa and Otani Will Walk.
Premonition of Separation?! The Different Paths Risa and Otani Will Walk!
Be sure to watch!