Otani...
Sorry.
I'm going to have to take back that "Let's pretend nothing happened".
I still like you, after all.
Just keep that in mind.
'Kay.
I like who I like.
You got a problem with that?
A Confrontation with the Ex-Girlfriend?!
The Great Chest Baring Plan!!
What the hell is this?!
I've been cut off!
Pretty lame, huh?
Seriously, Umibouzu's wife, couldn't you have done better?
Look, here's another picture of you looking lame.
What? There are more?
What the hell is this?!
Gimme that!
Why should I? I took it using my own camera.
No good will come of you having that picture.
I could print out a few more copies and put them up in the hallway.
I'll hit you!
Is that how you treat the guy you like?
Why do you have to say stuff like that?!
It's your fault, no matter how you look at it.
Now I'm definitely gonna print more copies!
In Japan, small packets of tissues are commonly handed out for free as a method of advertising.
I'll make a hundred copies and hand them out with tissues in front of the station.
I really will hit you!
Go ahead, if you dare.
The data is still stored in my camera, anyway.
They're back to normal.
A little too normal.
This is bad.
Otani knows my biggest weakness now.
This is making me mad.
This isn't the time to get mad.
I thought you were going to make Otani-kun regret rejecting you.
That's easier said than done.
Nevertheless, don't make that ugly face!
Think. Why did he reject you in the first place?
It was because he thinks of you as his comedy partner, right?
Yeah, something like that.
Right!
You can't just keep doing comedy with him like before.
Use your seductiveness! Seductiveness!
"Seductiveness"?
Exactly, bare your chest completely and move forward!
How can I do that?
Then do a lap of the station area!
I'll be arrested!
I mean show that kind of attitude!
What?!
What the heck is a "chest baring attitude"?
It's Christmas again.
A year sure goes by quickly, huh?
What, are you an old woman?
Come to think of it...
...last Christmas, he blew off his ex-girlfriend and kept me company.
She sure was cute...
Hey Otani...
What was your relationship with Kanzaki-san like?
What's with this all of a sudden?!
It would bother anyone in my position.
It was normal. Normal.
Normal, huh?
What?!
Nothing.
Well you guys weren't ever a comedy duo, were you.
The girl Otani went out with...
The girl he liked...
I want to become the girl that Otani likes.
How should I do that?
What should I give my darling for Christmas?
Chiharu-chan, what are you going to give Suzuki-kun?
Well, last year I gave him a sweater...
U-Um...
It's fine. Don't mind me.
Risa, you don't have any plans for Christmas this year, right?
So what?
Why don't you ask Otani-kun out?
Tell him you want to spend Christmas eve together, just the two of you.
Yes, Yes!
He rejected me!
There's no way I could say something so embarrassing!
He already knows you like him, and nothing could be more embarrassing than that, right?
I still like you, after all.
Just keep that in mind.
I'm remembering pointless things again!
How embarrassing! I'm so embarrassed I could die!
I should never have told him!
Huh?
Leave me alone.
You'll be fine, you'll be fine.
Love is naturally embarrassing.
Everyone loves whilst fighting against embarrassment.
How did you get together with Nakao-chi, Nobu-chan?
Me?
It was a winter's day, when the rain was cold as snow...
It's a former gang leader, Nakao-kun.
I heard he put twenty delinquents from another school in the hospital all by himself.
Oh my! How scary!
Stray cat, please take me in
Sorry. I live in an apartment, so I can't take you in.
You really like milk, huh?
And then one day, I was picked on by some delinquents,
and the leader of their gang turned out to be...
I've heard enough.
And then I put a love letter in his locker...
I've heard enough!
Just kidding. just kidding.
In our last year of middle school, we attended the same cram school and became friends.
Cram school?
I said to him, "if only I had a boyfriend like you, Nakao-kun..."
And he said, "If only I had a girlfriend like you, Nobu-chan..."
And then it was like, "So why don't we go out?"
There was no drama involved.
That's a good thing. I've had enough of drama.
The person you like likes you back. That's pretty impressive in itself.
It's almost a miracle, in fact.
Risa...
Risa-chan...
You too, Chiharu-chan.
Yes?
You got your miracle easily enough, and things have gone well with Suzuki-kun.
You two should be more thankful to God.
It-It-It's just me that's...
Damn it! What the hell...?!
What's this? Alcohol?!
It'll be fine, Risa-chan.
He didn't  say that he didn't like you at all.
That's right, Risa. Just do your best.
But I can't bare my chest!
You idiot! No one told you to do it literally!
I meant mentally bare your chest!
Mentally bare my chest?
That's right.
Reveal the inner breasts that lie deep within your heart!
Mine aren't as big as yours, Nobu-chan.
This has nothing to do with size.
Bare them! Go on! Bare them!
I think you should lower your voice...
You can do it if you really want to!
Yeah. You're cute too, Risa-chan.
Cute?
Just use a bit of charm and Otani-kun will be done for.
But I'm All-Kyojin...
So you're tall like a model. What's wrong with that?!
I agree.
Do your best.
Believe in miracles.
"Believe in miracles"...
I want Otani to fall in love with me.
Okay! I'll give it a try!
The great Christmas plan!
Yeah!
First, I'll need to find a Christmas present for him.
I'll reveal my chest!
Yeah...
Otani-kun...
...are you doing anything for Christmas?
Disgusting!
Wh-What do you mean, "disgusting"?!
Here I am, desperately trying to bare my chest to you...
Chest?
Uh... anyway... are you free for Christmas?
For Christmas?
No.
It's over.
Why?
Why does it matter? So you're doing something for Christmas?
Yeah. My middle school's basketball club is getting together for a Christmas party.
So it's like the one that Kanzaki-san invited you to last year, but you didn't go?
Uh, yeah. You remember that?
How could I forget?
T-Then Kanzaki-san will be going too?
Uh... Probably.
She was the manager, after all.
Don't pull that face! It seriously pisses me off!
What's your problem?
Nothing.
I'm telling you, there's nothing going on between me and that girl, okay.
"That girl"?
You're calling her "that girl?" now?
Oh my! Have you heard, ma'am?
He just said "There's nothing going on between me and that girl".
I'd like to be able to say something like that myself. How cool.
What exactly did you want?
Nothing.
Last year, he hung out with me.
I did make plans with you first, right?
But that was because of the Umibouzu concert.
It's not like he considered me more important than his ex-girlfriend.
I knew that. I knew it, but I was still happy.
Without an Umibouzu ticket, I'm just an All-Kyojin to be rejected.
Fine, Go have a merry Christmas with that girl.
And then, when you just happen to get back together,
this rejected All-Kyojin will simply stand by silently.
Koizumi?
What is it?
Want to come along? To the Christmas party, I mean.
What are you saying? I don't have anything to do with your middle school.
It's open invitation.
It is a party, but we'll be playing a bit of basketball too, so the more the merrier, right?
The Nakao couple are coming too.
What's this?
This is the first I've heard of it.
Well, we can spend Christmas Eve alone together,
then we can go to the party on Christmas day.
Ahh. That's okay then.
Right.
See?
You're free anyway, right?
Yep!
They said they already ordered a cake.
We're gonna eat it in the gym? Won't we get in trouble?
We'll get in trouble.
Risa, Risa!
Time for the great Christmas plan.
Bare your chest, and more forward!
Chest.
Right. Whether it's an ex-girlfriend or whatever, bring it on!
Using my chest baring power I'll make Otani fall for me!
Merry Christmas!
It's Otani-senpai and Nakao-senpai!
Otani-sempai is as short as always.
I'll smack you for that, damn it.
The ex-girlfriend isn't here yet?
Otani-sempai, I'm really sorry.
Manager Kanzaki couldn't make it today.
So are you two back together yet or what?
Geez, you guys! I told you there's nothing going on between us.
And you, don't look so obviously happy about it.
So she's not coming?
What's this? What's this?
Otani's new girlfriend?
Seriously?
Uh, n-no. I mean...
She's just an amazon who's in the same class as me.
So she's not your girlfriend?
She doesn't look like she would be, huh.
Oww! That hurt!
Couldn't you have phrased that better?
Don't you have a sense of kindness or compassion?
It's not like I said anything wrong!
You didn't say anything right, you microbe.
Good grief!
You didn't bare your chest. You bared your ass!
But...
Anyway, how is this a Christmas party?
Apparently we'll be having a cake later.
Ah, I see.
Time for a break.
The sweaty look doesn't suit you at all, darling.
Why don't you guys join in too?
I didn't bring my sneakers.
I can't play basketball.
So why couldn't Kanzaki make it?
She said something came up.
And we were going to go to all that effort to get her and Otani back together too...
But doesn't she have a boyfriend?
We could have just passed that off as a thing of the past...
Th-That was close.
Otani liked Kanzaki-san a lot, after all.
It was like he died after they broke up.
It really damaged him.
It was difficult to watch.
I never heard about this.
I thought that it would bother Koizumi-san if I mentioned it.
Risa...
Hey, what were Otani and Kanzaki-san like as a couple?
What were they like?
Well, Otani was head over heels in love.
Before they started going out, he'd get incredibly nervous and could barely speak around her.
So we thought it would be funny to lock the two of them in the storeroom together.
After they got out, they started going out.
Who knows what happened in there.
I wonder what could have happened...
Wh-Wh-What happened?!
That's payback for before.
And you two, how long are you planning on drawing out that break for?
Gossiping again, were you?
We were not!
You worry too much.
In front of someone he likes, he gets so nervous he can barely speak...
Risa...
I hate Christmas!
Wait! What about your chest?! Your chest!
I've had enough already!
What's that girl doing?
Hey, Otani, are you interested in that girl?
Why do you ask?
Well, she doesn't seem your type at all, but...
...she's a fun girl.
Fun, huh?
It's rare to find a girl as fun as her.
Oh, so you kinda like her then?
Remember the chest! Reconsider, Risa! Reconsider!
I dunno.
Listen up. You bring Otani-kun and...
Okay. I'll get everyone to help.
Risa, we'll get yelled at if we eat cake in here, so we're going to eat outside.
Ah, Okay.
Oh, before that, could you put this ball back in the storeroom?
Why me?
Just go, just go.
Here's the ball.
Ah. Toss it over.
Hey, was that a click just now?
I can't open it.
Yo, this is for real, You got mail.
Nobu-chan
Bare your chest
We'll come and open the door
later. Do your best!
Bare your chest!
We'll come and open the door later. Do your best!
Why...
Who was it?
Nobu-chan.
What'd she say?
She told me to bare my chest.
Hey! Don't expose such a dangerous area.
Ah. They got us.
Oh well.
"Oh well"?
Hey, Otani...
...when you and Kanzaki-san were locked in the storeroom, you weren't this calm, were you?
H-H-H-How do you know about that?!
I just heard about it.
Who told you?! I'll kill them!
What did you two do?
What? What do you mean?
In this dark room, all alone with Kanzaki-san, what did you do?
Nothing at all, you idiot! We just talked!
Considering you were so nervous you couldn't even talk straight,
what could you two have talked about all alone together?
You even know that?!
Damn it, those guys are gonna pay!
Did you confess?
Well, I guess it was something like that.
So you really liked her.
I already told you...
I already told you, that was in the past.
I know.
That's not it.
You sure have been crying a lot lately, Koizumi.
Who do you think is to blame for that?!
Huh? Me?!
Don't look so genuinely surprised. Who else could it be?
I see. I guess that's right.
Geez, you idiot...
Miracles can't happen to me.
What's this?
A Christmas present.
Huh? For me?
I brought it on a whim.
It's pointless keeping it, so I'll give it to you.
Oh, they're gloves! I've been wanting some.
Good for you.
But I didn't get anything for you.
I figured.
It's not like I was expecting anything.
That much?
You really like me that much?
What?! Why are you saying that?!
But you...
"But" nothing! Stop blabbering pointless things like that!
Hey! Hurry up and open the door, Nobu-chan!
What's with that smile?
Nothing.
You're laughing!
Am I?
Find something funny, do you?
It is funny, isn't it?
Risa...
What the hell is wrong with you?! Maybe you really do have a bad personality!
Funny, funny!
Shut the hell up!
It is Christmas, so it'd be nice if a miracle happened to me.
Kanzaki broke up with her boyfriend?
This is bad!
Otani is going to be swept off his feet by his ex-girlfriend.
You're overdoing it with the adrenaline.
Lovely Complex~ Love Com.
Next: Complete Despair! A Love Revival with the Ex?!
Complete Despair! A Love Revival with the Ex?!
Be sure to watch!