We're going to lose anyway.
Otani.
You idiot!
You slacker!
O T A N I
D o  y o u r b e s t !
D o  y o u r b es t !
O T A N I
D o  y our best!
Do your best!
I guess I'm just... no good without you, Koizumi.
The Best Birthday in History
I'm just no good without you, Koizumi.
Otani...
And so, summer vacation starts tomorrow.
Stop that!
Me too...
Koizumi-san!
What are you going to do over the summer vacation?
Hmm...Well...
What a nice dream.
Summer. The last summer of my high school life.
I still don't know how Otani feels, but...
I'm gonna have some fun!
Summer Studies Sign up
You lot have forgotten that you'll be sitting entrance exams soon, haven't you?
Yes. I completely forgot.
For the little idiots I just named, the summer study session is compulsory.
Little        Idiot
You have to work hard to make up for your past laziness.
Got it?
You exam students don't get a vacation.
No...
My precious summer...
So in the end,
Chiharu-chan and Suzuki-kun are the only ones who don't need to attend summer classes...
That's because they have study dates at the library every day.
They're not dates. We just study.
But we'll be attending summer classes too.
And here I thought I'd have the chance to have loads of fun...
What do you mean loads of fun?!
An idiot like you who misses all the important stuff, sleeping away and not hearing the best part!!!
What's got you so angry these days?!
So we've got to attend summer classes again this year?
And here I thought I could have fun, now that I'm done with basketball club.
I thought you retired so that you could concentrate on your studies?
Oh well...
Well, at least I don't need to come up with any excuses to hang out with Otani over the summer,
I guess it's not so bad.
Nobu-chan, why didn't you plan study dates with Nakao-chi too?
I don't see why the ones with red crosses all over her work should be asking me that.
Hot... So hot...
Why are you melting?!
I can't take it...
Want to go somewhere cool?
Yes~!
Yay! Paradise!
I'm revived!
What would you like to order?
Oh yes, yes, My order...
Let's see...
Oh! A new item on the menu?
I'm gonna try it.
One Polynesian Dancer!
Why are you copying me?
You're the one who's copying me.
I'll go with the drink bar.
Me too.
Same here.
Thank you. Please wait one moment.
Chiharu-chan, that's a cute ring.
Uh, thank you.
When did you get that?
Eh? Well...
Oh? Did Suzuki-kun give it to you?
It was your birthday not long ago, wasn't it?
Uh...yes.
Ah. Well done.
Well done, Suzuki-chi.
Uh... I guess...
Oh, Nobu-chan, you got something for your birthday too, didn't you?
Yeah. A handbag!
Sorry it was only a cheap one.
It's okay.
It was given with love, after all.
I love you Nobu-chan~
Me too! I love love love you~
I love love love love love love love you~
I love you~
Everyone's happy, huh...
Oh! that reminds me, it's almost Risa's birthday!
smirk... smirk... smirk... smirk...
Hey! What's up with this atmosphere?!
Otani-chi, naturally you'll be giving Koizumi-san a present, won't you?
Yeah.
I mean, he just can't live without Koizumi-san, right?
What was that anyway? A proposal?
Wha-What the hell?! You guys were listening?!
We heard it all.
What?
I didn't say I couldn't live without her!
What's this about?
Shut up! It's none of your business!
Hey! What's going on?! This is getting on my nerves!
Shut up! Just be quiet!
For the customer who ordered the Polynesian Dancer...
Oh, it's here! My Polynesian Dancer!
Mmmmm... Polynesian....
That's not the point.
What the heck?
Koizumi!
Hey.
Geez! I get it!
What do you want?
What do you want for your birthday?
I don't want anything.
Are you refusing my good intentions?
More importantly, what were you talking about yesterday?
Th-That was... just forget about it.
How can I?
No one is telling me anything, and everyone seems to find it hilarious.
It's really irritating me!
Forget it, okay. Just tell me what you want.
Nothing. I don't want anything.
Seriously?
Don't complaint to me later if I don't give you anything.
I told you I don't want anything!
Why do you always make things worse?!
Well, I just unconsciously...
Idiot!
But...!
But it's true!
I don't want a cute ring or a handbag.
The only thing I want is...
...Otani's love!
Get away from me!
I'm home.
Yeesh, It's so hot...
Ahh. What a nice wind.
My birthday, huh?
Come to think of it, on my birthday last year...
I like you, Otani!
What's with you? Saying a thing like that out of nowhere...
You're embarrassing me.
Well, I wasn't taken seriously, but...
It's been a whole year since then, huh?
Umibouzu!
Maybe someone like you is more suited to me.
What did you say?
Just talking to myself.
I'm a real idiot.
Accept it!
Ko-Koizumi...
Koizumi...
I've had enough.
I've had enough of this.
I'm through with loving you!
A lot has happened, but... I wonder if my hard work has paid off?
I mean, he just can't live without Koizumi-san, right?
I never said I can't live without her!
What were they talking about?
If you're going to buy something, hurry up and do it.
We're kind of out of place here.
I think she'll be happy with anything you get her.
I'm not doing it. I'm not buying anything.
This is stupid. It feels wrong.
Huh? You're not?
Don't give her Umibouzu stuff again. That's boring.
Why should your boredom be my concern?
I hope something good happens on my birthday this year.
Risa.
Senpai!
Ah!
You have to attend summer classes too, Haruka?
Nope. I just wanted to see you.
Haruka-senpai may not look very smart,
but he's quick to understand things so he does well on tests.
Seiko-chin...
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Here, Koizumi-senpai.
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Koizumi Risa
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Koizumi Risa
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Koizumi Risa
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Koizumi Risa
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Koizumi Risa
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Koizumi Risa
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Koizumi Risa
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Koizumi Risa
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Koizumi Risa
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Koizumi Risa
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Koizumi Risa
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Koizumi Risa
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Koizumi Risa
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Koizumi Risa
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Koizumi Risa
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Koizumi Risa
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Koizumi Risa
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Koizumi Risa
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Huh? What's this?
An invitation to Koizumi Risa's Birthday Party?
Yeah. We're going to prepare lots of delicious food and cake and host it!
Invite everyone, okay!
Y-You guys are so nice!
I am, huh. Feel free to fall for me.
Not gonna happen.
How cruel!
Forget it. I'll just win you over with my party hosting skills.
Otani-senpai!
Here. Take one.
What's this?
An invitation to Koizumi-senpai's birthday party.
Please come, okay?
For Koizumi's birthday?
I'm inviting you because I don't have a choice.
Better this that having you two off alone somewhere.
Haruka-senpai! Did you really have such an underhanded motive?
Say what you want.
I'm not going to let you have Risa all to yourself on her birthday.
You're the worst!
Well, I want to celebrate with her too.
Nakao and Nobu-chan are both planning to go to your party, huh?
Maity-sensei is going to come too.
What about you, Otani?
Are you going to come?
I though you didn't want me to do anything for your birthday?
You said you didn't want a present from me.
I-I didn't mean it like that!
Then what did you mean?
Then what does "Can't live without me" mean?
I-I said I didn't say that! as if I'd say that!
What's this all about?
Did this happen when I fell asleep that time?
I-I told you, they got it all wrong!
Man, I'm seriously going to get those guys.
Hey, What about the party?
Like I care!
Otani!
What the heck?!
Sorry I'm late!
Happy Birthday to you, Happy Birthday to you,
Happy Birthday dear Risa...
I..I'm so happy...
Happy Birthday to you!
Congratulations, Risa!
Thank you, thank you.
You sure had a long talk with our homeroom teacher.
What did he call you for?
Well, my test results were pretty terrible...
Huh? Where's Otani-kun?
He's not here?
Nope.
We thought he was with you.
Hey, what about the party?
Like I care!
Well, maybe he went home.
Who cares if he's not here.
Come on, Risa.
Haruka-senpai....
...don't tell me this is your doing?!
I didn't do a thing!
Oh no! This aggressive reaction is very suspicious.
You...
Ahhh! he's getting worse!
Stop this ridiculousness!
Now, now. Let's put that aside.
"Put that aside"?
Happy Birthday, Koizumi-san.
Maity-sensei!
Congratulations.
Thank you so much!
Now, take a seat.
You're the guest of honor today.
That's right! I just put all of my love for you into this food, just to make you happy, Risa.
Wow! It smells so good!
I'm so hungry!
Wait Risa. What about Otani-kun?
Wow! This cake is super cute!
Isn't it? Isn't it? I decorated it myself.
Never mind that. Check this out!
I made all your favorites: Chirashizushi, fried chicken, sandwiches, takoyaki, French fries,
and spaghetti with Neapolitan sauce!
Geez!
He's not answering his phone. Where could Otani have gone?
What's going on! This is so frustrating!
They're definitely both interested in each other now...
That's true!
It's fine.
Even if Otani isn't around, everyone else is here celebrating with me.
Ahh. That was just delicious!
You're very welcome.
Hey, did you hear something from outside?
Yeah. It's probably fireworks.
Oh yeah. I heard there's a fireworks festival on today.
Really?
If we go up to the roof, we should be able to see them.
Fireworks?
Come to think of it, last year too...
Risa, let's go up to the roof.
Ah! I can see them! I can see them!
How pretty!
Beautiful...
Amazing!
Wow!
I thought watching the fireworks would cheer you up.
Wow. They sure are pretty.
It really is no good.
If Otani's not with me, I just don't find the fireworks pretty...
...and I can't cheer up.
Yo, this is for real. You got mail.
Mail?
Otani
Behind You
What's this?
Something you didn't want.
A present.
Huh? No way!
Why would I lie?
Can I open it? I've already opened it, thought....
It's not my style, but you always have rabbit stuff, so I just went and...
Wow! It's super cute!
Keep it down! They'll see us.
That hurt!
What's that?
Fireworks. I bought them at the convenience store.
Cool. Then let's get everyone and...
You can do that later. Just put that away for now.
This?
If they find out I bought you that, they won't let me live it down, you know?
Don't tell me you were late because you went to buy this?
Where did you get it?
Does it matter where?
Thanks. I'm really happy.
Really?
I thought you weren't going to come.
I was just thinking "I guess I'm just not good without Otani".
Hey, are you listening?
I'm listening.
I said the same thing after that last basketball match.
Although someone fell asleep and didn't hear me.
I guess I'm just... no good without you, Koizumi.
So... that wasn't a dream...
Koizumi...
Can't you pull a better face than that?
What? But... uh...
Do you have a fever again?
It's not like that.
Ah... Not like that... Not like that...
Don't laugh.
Then... what is this?
Am I still dreaming?
This isn't a dream, right?
My first date with Otani!
Otani bought it for me - !
You're late!
Why don't you buy me juice as penance?
Oh! I forgot my purse...
You idiot!
Lovely Complex~ Love Com.
Next: Sudden Downturn!! The First Date is the Beginning of Misfortune
Sudden Downturn!! The First Date is the Beginning of Misfortune
Be sure to watch!