I said do whatever you like!
It's not like I like Koizumi or anything.
The truth is, I know how to perform magic.
I can use magic to bring you happiness, Koizumi-san.
Just so you know, I'm the one Koizumi-san likes.
There's now way she'd fall for someone like you.
Seriously... for real this time...
I'm really going to stop liking Otani.
This time, we really can go back to the way we were.
The Fist of Love! Intercept it, A Maiden's Spirit!!
Sea Urchin
Brush
All Hanshin Kyojin
Yes!
Perfect!
D'ya see that?
I saw.
I'm not gonna lose to you again.
Challenge me anytime you want.
That's great.
Otani really is great!
Oh, oh, oh?
Weren't you meant to be cheering for Maity?
Well, Maity-sama is wonderful, of course,
but Otani tries so hard despite being short...
He deserves some praise.
So what's going on with you and Otani anyway?
Well... nothing.
We've progressed so little that we've gone back to the way we were before.
You...
The comedy due has been revived!
"Revived"? Are you serious?
How exactly did you guys end up like that again?
It's fine. This is the most comfortable way for us to be anyway.
Risa, are you aware of your situation right now?
Otani is...
President Koizumi!
President...
The Maity Club is...  is... disbanded now, right?
Right?
Eh...uh...Um...
It's so awful that Maity-sensei has a fiancee!
Seriously?!
I see.
I wasn't trying to hide it or anything...
...but I guess someone told you.
Everyone is really down about it.
It hasn't got you down, has it, Koizumi-san?
Well, no... Uh... That's...
Maity, get this:
Risa says and Otani-kun are back to being a comedy duo again.
Say something to her.
What?
"What" nothing.
Despite what people might think, you're actually quite timid, aren't you, Koizumi-san?
Well, in any case, I'm glad that Otani-kun is better now.
See you.
My magic spell hasn't broken yet, Koizumi-san.
Gather round! Gather round!
His ankle healed, so he's in top form.
And since his final competition is coming up, he's trying even harder.
But then again...
Just so you know, I'm the one Koizumi-san likes.
There's now way she'd fall for someone like you.
Don't tell me...
...he was jealous?
Risa, what's the matter?
H-Hey!
No good.
This is no good!
I'm not going to hold onto any inappropriate hope.
It's gonna go back to the way it was. Back to the way it was.
So, Risa...
...what are you going to do from here on in?
Whatever is...
You're in the way.
That hurt!
You didn't have to hit me!
Yeah, yeah. Sorry 'bout that.
What the hell was that?!!
Oh, I'm ever so sorry.
My legs are just so long...
You got a death wish?
I'm gonna get you!
Stop right there!
Risa, are you really fine with things going back to the way they were before?
So the basketball camp is going to be this weekend?
I might come watch.
You must be bored, huh?
Not really.
Ah! I'll bring "that" with me.
What?
You know... the kind of cute things that a manager would bring.
Lemons in soy sauce.
What on earth would that taste like?
That's not it?
Then, lemons in vinegar?
How sour would that be?!
Don't. Please don't.
What? But I want to cheer you on...
If I eat anything weird like that, I'll get sick.
Fine, fine.
Then I'll make it for Maity-sensei.
You idiot. The coach will be back tomorrow.
We don't need that guy anymore.
Serves him right.
Could it be that he really is jealous?
What are you doing, shaking your head like that?
What are you, a dog?
No, I'm not.
Oww... That hurt!
Please dip the lemons in honey, okay?
Oh, so that's it. Honey, is it?
Yeah, yeah. Honey.
Don't mess it up, okay?
Back to the way it was, back to the way it was...
What was that?
Nothing.
What's up with you?
Nothing at all.
Honey dipped lemons, huh?
Bittersweet, isn't it?
Isn't it?
Geez! Forget reviving the comedy duo... Just hurry up and get together!
Yeah. If Otani would make a move now...
Yeah...
In the end I guess it's Otani-kun who holds the key to all of this.
Darling, why don't you give him a push?
No, no. Let's just leave the youngsters to their own devices.
If we leave those two alone, they'll go on like that until they're old and grey.
Too true...
Indeed.
Push him down...
Push him down and claim him as your own!
If you don't, I will!
What the heck?!
It annoys me just watching you two!
If you're going to get together, hurry up and do it!
Don't be ridiculous!
It's easier said than done!
It is easy!
It is not!
It's fine. I've decided I'm not going to hold onto any hope.
No hope?
But you haven't given up, have you?
Bullseye
What's that?
Don't tell me you're just going to hang on and wait like that until Otani confesses to you?
That's a little...
Well...
Ah. Otani-kun!
Good morning!
Waiting for that guy to take initiative is like going fishing in a swimming pool.
But there might be koi swimming in there.
What kind of pool are you thinking of?
What's going on? You seem to be in a good mood.
We'll find out the tournament draw tomorrow.
Ah, for basketball?
Yeah. It's our last big competition.
I'm really looking forward to it.
Hey, hey, come shopping with me after school.
Ok, sure.
What happens if we fluke it to the finals?
Don't be silly.
When I go for it, I really do go for it.
I can't be held responsible if you fall for me again.
Just kidding.
You're an idiot.
It was a joke, a joke.
You really are an idiot.
Still, at the end of the day, I just can't give up.
Hey, Otani...
is it... is it so bad if I hold onto just a little bit of hope?
Gather around!
Our goal is... the finals!
They're a little too energetic, huh?
What's the matter?
My darling is just a bench warmer...
You're still going to cheer for them, right?
Well, yeah... but...
Really? You're going to come and watch us?
Darling!
Nakao-chi.
Hey, what's that?
The competition draw.
Oh? Let me see, let me see.
It's amazing.
Hey, hey, since we're all going, let's invite Chiharu-chan and cheer them on properly.
Oh, good idea!
Wha-Wha-Wha-Wha-What?!!
What's going on?
Oh, our first opponents are last year's champions. They're real veterans.
It's all over.
I thought you were going for the finals.
Impossible. Impossible.
Oh no. He's turned into a robot.
No good. This is no good.
Okay! Let's do this!
Despite what people might think, you're actually quite timid, aren't you, Koizumi-san?
That's right. As you said, I'm just afraid to find out what Otani is really thinking.
Please dip the lemons in honey, okay?
If I just go back to pretending things are the way they were before, without doing anything,
I'll definitely regret it.
It doesn't matter what Otani thinks of me.
So...
She's late...
What happened to Risa-chan?
The match is about to start.
Good morning.
What's up with you?! Don't scare me so early in the morning!
What's wrong? You look really tired.
I was up all night making our cheering gear.
Cheering gear?
Otani
for  life
Otani fan
Otani fan club
Otani                for Life
Starting today, you're all part of the Otani Club!
Like hell!
Otani
fan
club
Otani!
For life!
Do your best!
Otani!
There, there, Captain. Don't be so down. Cheer up.
You guys too.
I'll cheer for you from the bench, okay?
Hey! Are you Captain Otani?
Hey man, we're your first opponents.
Best of luck, okay?
YES!
I... My... Me... My... You... You're... H-Huge...
Otani, pull yourself together.
Hello! We're the Otani Club!
Yes!
Why... why...
Oh, you came.
Huh? Where's Otani?
We met our opponents just now, and it left him quite shocked.
He wandered off somewhere in a daze.
Isn't the first match about to start?
Yeah... but...
Oh, don't worry. I'll go look for him.
Look. I got dragged into the Otani Club.
That's okay. I'm just a bench warmer, after all.
Cheer for Otani.
I love you, Nakao-chi!
Yay.
Where'd he go?
What are you doing?
I guess you could say I'm trying to focus my mind.
What's that?
The Otani Club.
What?
Come on, now. The match is about to start.
What's with this Otani Club? How embarrassing.
What do you mean embarrassing?!
After I came specifically to cheer you on and all!
It's fine. You don't need to cheer.
I mean, we're going to lose anyway.
It's more embarrassing if you're cheering away loudly while we're losing.
Otani...
You idiot!
You slacker!
If you keep saying you'll lose, you won't be able to win even if you do have a chance, idiot!
Well, what can I do against those guys?
Oh, I see. So that's how it is.
Fine. I get it. I don't want to cheer for a guy like you, anyway.
What?
I'm going to call you a loser midget for the rest of your life!
What's up with her?
What's this?
What the heck is this?
Huh? You're going home?!
What happened?
I'm gong home.
I stayed up all night, so I'm tired.
What's going on?! After making a girl with a boyfriend act so disloyally...
Hold it right there!
It's okay. I'm wearing one too.
Wait!
I don't want to watch a pointless match.
Did something happen?
That... That useless loser midget...
Who's a loser midget?!
What's this about going home?
Why don't you go home after you've cheered me on properly?
Otani...
Otani-kun...
I'm not cheering for someone with no spirit.
You idiot. I'm fired up and ready to go.
It's been a while since I've received it, hasn't it?
That Idiot Punch of yours...
Watch closely. You'll fall for me again.
Whatever.
Say what you want, say what you want.
Really now...
Wh-What the heck is this?
That's no normal height range...
W-Will they be all right?
Yeah! Of course!
When Otani goes for it, he really goes for it.
Amazing, Otani-kun!
He got past that tall guy!
Otani...
All right!
Otani!
O T A N I
D o  y o u r b e s t !
D o  y o u r b es t !
O T A N I
D o  y our best!
Do your best!
What exactly did you put on these lemons?
Ri...
"Ri"?
Rice wine.
Rice wine?
I didn't have any honey, so...
Good thing I didn't eat these before the match.
What? And after I stayed up all night, rubbing sleepy eyes in order to make them...
Thank you.
Well, you came to cheer me on and all, but we still lost.
Yeah, but you were still really cool.
Oh. Really?
Yeah. You made me fall for you again.
Well, I played so well thanks to you.
Oh. Really?
I know you said you've given up on me, but...
...don't.
I guess I'm just... no good without you, Koizumi.
Listen to me...
Oh well.
Risa, that idiot! What is she doing?!
Now, now, now...
Koizumi, what do you want for your birthday?
I don't need a cute ring or anything like that.
All I want is your love, Otani!
That's not for sale!
Lovely Complex~ Love Com.
Next: The Best Birthday Present in History.
The Best Birthday Present in History
Be sure to watch!