Ko...Koizumi.
Nothing...
It's all a blank after that.
"It's all a blank after that"?!
A Killer Crush on Maity!
Risa, what's wrong? You look upset.
It's not like you.
I look upset, do I?
Why don't you cast away all of that sadness, and smile for me like you usually do?
There. That suits you much better.
Seeing you smile is what gives me strength.
Cain-sama sure is sweet.
It'd be nice if I could meet someone like him for real.
Ah... For some reason, my heart is racing.
Risa, maybe I...
No. Never mind.
No, no. Tell me, tell me.
Is this really my sister? This isn't good.
Who's Cain-sama?
Risa, come back!
Hey, can I sit next to you?
I want to be near you...
Let me just say this. That was my first kiss.
But... But that idiot...
Man, the last thing I remember was eating oranges. It's all blank after that.
"It's all a blank after that"...
What the heck do you mean "It's all a blank after that"?!
You think you can get off by just saying that?!
Risa!
Have you seen the notice board?
We're all in the same class again.
Is that right?
Feeling down? What's the matter?
Nothing.
Me, my darling, Chiharu-chan and hers, and Otani-kun too.
Are you serious?!
Don't eat me!
Ah... We'll be in the same class for all three years...
Right up until the end, we'll still be called All Hanshin-Kyojin.
How are you going to make this up to me?
That's my line, you stunted dwarf!
What's your problem?!
Ask yourself, you jerk-off!
What's up with you?! Getting so upset right at the start of the new semester...
What the heck did I do?
I-I'll go find Chiharu-chan and the others, okay?
See ya.
You've been in a foul mood ever since that last Umibouzu concert.
Was it something Umibouzu did?
Umibouzu was awesome, as always.
Then what is it? Explain it to me.
Did you really forget?
F-Forget? What are you talking about?
My... My first kiss...
Give it back! Give back my first kiss!
Ko...Koizumi?
It's 119 for an ambulance, right?
What are you doing?!
What kind of hallucination did you have?
Next you'll turn up with a marriage certificate and tell me we got married!
Pull yourself together!
I may not remember what happened, but don't confuse fantasy with reality.
Okay?
Don't get carried away, okay? Okay? Okay?
Patience
Go to hell!!!
What the heck?
What the heck was that?
Did he really pass out right at that moment?
In any case, if he doesn't remember, then it really was just an accident.
Hey...
What are you angry about?
Nothing.
Did something happen when you went to Otani'-kun's place?
Nothing happened. Nothing at all!
Okay? Okay?! Okay?!!
Risa-chan...
I'm nothing more than an unattractive girl, after all.
Excuse me.
What the heck do you want?
Nothing serious.
I'd like to ask you to kindly move aside.
Oh... I'm sorry.
No. I should be the one saying that.
Go ahead.
Thank you.
Who's that?
Someone we don't know.
What's wrong? It's such a waste to spoil such a cute face with a furrowed brow.
Go on. Smile, okay?
Yes!
Wha...What is this?
What is this cold feeling I seem to remember?
Cain...Cain-sama!
That's it!
A guy that cool really exists!
Ugh... I'm getting goosebumps...
What's so good about that guy?!
He's tall, cool and charming like a prince!
He's totally my type.
That's the complete opposite of Otani-kun.
Right.
That idiot who breaks a girl's heart isn't really my type at all.
From now on...  Cain-sama is the one!
I wonder what class he's in...
What are you on about?
You're seriously sickening.
No, no. I need to maintain my cute face.
"Cute"? More like monstrous...
Cain-sama told me it was!
This is bad!
Koizumi is fantasizing about some imaginary lover.
And he's a foreigner to boot.
Oh? So she can't get over it, huh...
What? Did I do something?
I don't know.
Okay, back to your seats.
We've got the gorilla again?
I'm tired of seeing him already.
Don't call me that. I'm Nakano-sensei.
You got that right!
Since it's a pain, let's get some of this out of the way.
The class reps will be Otani and Koizumi.
HEY!
Is there a problem?
There are a lot of problems!
Oh, sorry, sorry.
Before that, there's something important I forgot.
Is there? Is this decided already?
We have a new teacher who will be our assistant homeroom teacher.
Let me introduce him.
Maitake-sensei.
That was cruel, sensei.
Here I thought you'd forgotten me.
Sorry, sorry.
Cain-sama!
Calm down, Koizumi.
That person doesn't actually exist.
Ah. You're that girl from before.
Yes! So you're a teacher?
Is his name really Cain?
No, no. he just looks like a character from a game.
Nice to meet you. I'm your new assistant homeroom teacher.
My name is Maitake Kunimi.
Please just call me Maity.
I just moved here from Tokyo, so I'm not familiar with Osaka at all.
If it's not too much trouble, please show me around.
Sure!
Is it all right if we decide class reps now?
Sure.
Yes! I volunteer!
Really? Then the other one will be...
This shorty here says he volunteers too.
All right. Is that okay with everyone?
Yes!
Hey!
We call those two "All Hanshin-Kyojin". They're celebrities around here.
Oh?
Sensei!
What a cute nickname.
He's so nice... Maity...
Don't tell me you're giving up on Otani-kun, and going after Maity?
No way.
Maity is like Cain-sama...
An oasis for my withered heart in this harsh reality.
It'd be simpler if I did like him, though.
I'd stop you! A gross man like that...
If it was a game, I could reset after failing.
Even if you say that casually, it still sounds like the rambling of a game fanatic.
And that face isn't cute at all.
How long is Otani going to string me along?
Even now, I can't see a single ray of hope.
How long will that idiot waste my precious youth away?
Why do I have to be a class rep too?
Why not?
Never mind that, for now.
What are you doing mixing up real people with game characters?
Shut up. what do you care?
Hey, what did I do?
Weren't you going on about it this morning? Something about me forgetting something.
Never mind, It's fine if you don't remember.
I do mind!
What is it? Did something happen when you came over?
I said it was fine! Nothing happened, okay!
Oh, I almost forgot.
What?
You left right after that Umibouzu concert, right?
I waited in line to buy souvenirs, and I got something for you too.
Here.
It would've been a hassle if you came to me later saying that you wanted one.
Wow! How cool!
Isn't it?!
Awesome! Are you really giving this to me?
Yep.
It sure is easy to cheer you up, Koizumi.
S-S-Something like this...
You're shaking a lot.
If you don't want it, I'll take it back.
Thank you very much. I humbly accept it.
Right. You sure are simple.
Damn it. I hate this.
Maity is so cool...
He's like a foreigner...
He's so awesome!
His shirt is so...
His shirt is way too open...
His hair is too long in front...
Ahh! He's so cool...
So, who's going to translate this next part?
Otani-kun?
Otani-kun, Otani-kun...
Hey, Otani, wake up!
He's off in dreamland, huh?
Hey... Otani-kun...
Sssh. Let me handle this.
Time to open your eyes.
Good morning, sleeping beauty.
But I'd prefer it if you gave me your attention while we're in class.
Goosebumps, goosebumps, goosebumps...
How nice! I'm going to sleep too!
All right, all right...
Damn you, Otani. I'm going to sleep too.
Oh class rep.
Yes!
Nakano-sensei wanted me to give you a message.
Could you organize the roster for cleaning duty?
Yes! Gladly!
Otani, the coach is taking the day off.
Huh? Seriously?
Hey Otani, about the roster...
Sorry. Can you start on it by yourself? I have club duties.
Sorry. I need to set the training menu today.
Why do I like Otani?
Maity is so cool and all...
Don't say that! Please!
Otani left all his work to me and ran off to play with his club.
If the coach isn't around, shouldn't they just take the day off?
Well, they can't do that.
Besides, Otani-kun is the captain...
What?
Didn't you know?
When last year's seniors graduated, Otani became captain.
No way!
He did say he might make it, but I didn't think he'd actually...
This was decided half a year ago.
Ever since then, he's been working really hard.
That's great.
Line up! Has everyone warmed up?
Ahh. It's a matching pair.
Well of course.
Is it all right for you not to do the class rep work?
Ahh. You're right.
I'll be in the classroom, so tell Otani to come later.
Got it!
Oh, and so we don't get in your way, the rest of us will leave early.
You...
Why... Why is it Otani?
There are way too many reasons.
I don't even know, myself.
In the end, I still prefer Otani, after all.
Sorry I'm late.
Ahh. Thanks for all your hard work.
I'm tired.
When you're playing basketball, you're like a completely different person.
Is it because I'm so cool when I play basketball?
Don't say that yourself.
But I am cool, right?
Yes, yes.
So, are you done?
Done? Don't tell me you're not going to help?
Of course. It's your fault I'm class rep, in the first place.
Take responsibility.
But if no one had volunteered, I'd have felt bad for Maity-sensei.
What is it? Did you remember Maity-sensei's gentle whisper?
No! Don't mention Maity! He's disgusting!
Why not? Maity~
What is it?
What?
What "What"?
Maity. Do you seriously like that guy?
I do.
Ugh. That's gross.
Don't. Don't go for a cold guy like that.
When he says "don't"...
...does it mean that he wants me to keep liking him?
No way.
He probably just said it without thinking.
I get it.
Ahh. I remember now.
When I was sick and you came to visit me...
That's right. I was staring at your face like this...
And then...
Your hair...
There was a grain of rice stuck to it.
Rice... Rice... Rice...
Rice stuck to it...
Rise stuck to it...
RICE... RICE... RICE...
So then I was thinking I'd take the rice off while making a joke, when I suddenly got dizzy...
I don't remember anything after that.
But you're angry about what happened after that, right?
After or before, above or below, left or right...
...it's all pissing me off.
You damn idiot...
Rice? Rice?!
Of course there would be rice. I am Japanese!
Rice is a staple in my diet.
I eat plenty of rice!
Then why are you so angry?
Because you were sick and didn't come to school,
so I ate in a hurry and rushed over to visit you!
I-Is that so?
Sorry.
What do you mean "sorry"?
Even though the two of us are alone in this room right now, I don't feel a thing.
Because you said that... I was trying my best.
Now that I think about it, I was so embarrassed I could've died.
But "rice", you say...
Rice...
Yes?
You didn't take the rice.
What you took was my lips.
Huh? What are you on about now?
Wha-Wha-Wha-What did you do that for?!
I guess that really was just an accidental bump, huh?
An accidental... bump?
I'm really no good?
I've been trying so hard...
Even though you rejected me, I've been trying my best.
But if I go on liking you like this, nothing will change.
Koizumi...
I've had enough.
I've had enough of this.
I'm through with loving you!
Koizumi!
I've had enough.
Even though I like him, if nothing will change...
If there's no point at all...
I give up.
What do you mean "Maity for life!"?
Huh?!
You stole a kiss from me too...
Shut up! Shut your mouth!
Lovely Complex~ Love Com.
Next: A Dangerous man. Maity's Sweet Seduction.
A Dangerous man Maity's Sweet Seduction
Be sure to watch!