We've been a comedy duo for such a long time...
I don't think I can suddenly see you as my girlfriend.
Sorry.
Koizumi Risa, heartbroken.
Here.
Thank you.
Do you like stars?
Yes.
You too?
Yeah.
Oh, my name's Otani.
I'm Koizumi.
Koizumi Risa.
If we'd met as a normal short girl and tall guy,
Look. See that?
we wouldn't have ended up a comedy duo, and we'd naturally fall for one another.
How pretty!
We'd confess, and things might have gone well for us.
But the reality is...
Back from the Dead!! Aim for Girlfriend Status!!
...He's short.
Owww!!!
That hurts! That hurts!
Stop!
Silence!
Look over there.
Risa is so shocked you can see the whites of her eyes.
What are you going to do about this?!
"W-What am I going to do"?
Poor Koizumi-san...
Weren't you the one who told me to tell her what I was thinking?!
But even so...
Yeah! You're cruel!
Just what don't you like about Risa?!
I already told you, it's not that I don't like her or anything.
Then what?!
It's just, uh...
Say for example I told you that these pickled radishes are now crabs.
Would you really think, "Yes, that's true"?
Pickles... Pickles... Pickles...
Crabs... Crabs... Crabs...
Idiot!
Don't say things we can't understand!
Oww! Oww! Don't! It was just an example!
Don't compare Risa with pickled radishes!
Ahh, I'm stuffed.
Me too. Let's go play cards in the room.
Koizumi?
What is it?
Uh...
What do you want?!
Well...
Nobu-chan, hold on, hold on.
He just asked me to give them some time alone together during free time the day after tomorrow.
If we leave them alone right now...
...that would be bad, huh?
Umm... well...
Seriously, I'm sorry.
"Sorry", "sorry"...
How many times are you going to deal that finishing blow?!
Saying "sorry" once is enough!
I didn't mean it like that.
It's just that I'm worried.
I don't need you to worry about me!
It just makes me realize that this wasn't worth the effort at all.
I am just a pickled radish, after all.
I can't become a crab.
Uh, I know I picked a bad example, but...
You heard all that?
Well, at least you seem more lively.
"Lively"?
How could I be lively?!
What the hell?!
So no matter what I say, it's just gonna upset you?
Just don't say anything!
I told you, didn't I?
Just pretend that nothing happened.
Never speak of it again!
Well, that's fine by me if that's what you want, but...
Right.
Good boy.
So... is this how you treat guys you like?
Wh- Wh- What did you say?
Don't you have a sense of delicacy?!
What's this? Looks like they're back to normal.
I can't believe you can even say that!
You're right.
Seems like they're back to their old selves.
I wonder if they'll  just go back to being the way they were before...
Let's chat some more after I take my bath.
Hey, Nobu-chan...
Did I seem back to my old self just now?
A partner in our comedy duo?
Yeah. I was surprised.
That's good.
I'm glad.
Risa...
Hey, did you hear?
One of the boys in class 5 just confessed to Hikari-chan!
Really? Was it that guy she's liked all this time?
Yeah? So it was mutual then?
Um... I haven't told anyone yet, but the truth is, I also...
How did it go?
You spent the whole day together, didn't you?
I told him that I like him, and the he said "okay".
No way! Are you serious?!
Wow! Congratulations!
Wh- What is this?
Everyone else is having a great time on this trip...
...yet here I am at rock bottom after being rejected on the very first day.
What the hell is this?!!
Risa...
Nobu-chan...
Hey, Risa!
Get this - I'm super popular!
Girls keep confessing to me!
There's Ishida from class 4, and then from class 2 there's...
Hey, you.
No boys allowed on this floor.
Get out of here already.
But...
You lookin' for a fight?!
There's no need to be so aggressive.
I get it.
Oh, it's Haruka-kun!
Hey, can we have a picture taken together tomorrow?
Risa,
there's no need to hold back.
If you feel like crying, then go ahead and cry.
There, there. Let's go back to our room, okay?
There, there.
I told him to pretend that nothing happened,
but can I really do that to myself?
If none of this had happened...
If I didn't confess...
If I didn't like Otani...
Risa...
So, what are you going to do?
What do you mean?
Are you going to give up on Otani-kun?
It's not a matter of giving up.
Pickled radishes can't become crabs, right?
You're still thinking about that?
For starters, what are you going to do during free time the day after tomorrow?
If you don't want to be with Otani-kun, you and I can go around together.
I'll be fine.
I'd feel bad imposing on a lovey-dovey couple anyway.
Come on!
What are you going to do, Risa?
I'll just find someone else.
And it's not like I really mind being around with Otani that much.
Still...
I was the one who said I wanted us to go back to the way we were before.
Avoiding him now would be pointless.
Hey, Risa...
What?
I'm sorry.
What for?
I'm the one who pushed you into confessing...
I feel like this is all my fault.
What?
What the heck are you saying?
The confession... it was just me telling him how I felt.
But still...
Anyway, I'm grateful that you motivated me to do it.
Risa...
Risa!
Nobu-chan!
Hey, don't touch me there!
Who's making all those weird noises?
I can't sleep.
Geez, you guys woke us all up.
Want to play something?
All right!
How about a pillow fight?
Take that!
No good, no good.
If I'm depressed, I'll worry everyone.
It's fine.
I'll just pretend that nothing happened, and go back to being the way I was before.
There's no point on brooding over it.
Let's make the most out of this class trip!
Good morning!
Good morning, darling. Did you miss me?
How long are you going to be sleepy, shorty!
Get a move on or you'll be left behind again.
You...
Yeah. I don't want to go on feeling awkward forever.
I'll just pretend nothing happened and go back to being part of our comedy duo again.
And you...
You...!
Let's get some snacks for tonight.
Yeah.
Let's get these.
Otani! Otani!!
Look at this! Umibouzu's in it!
Wow, he really is!
It's a local magazine you can only get here.
"After his concert on Sapporo, he left for Hakodate for a quick vacation"...
Hakodate? Aren't we going there tomorrow?
And we'll have free time...
I want to try the soft serve ice cream he recommends!
I want to have a picture taken in that exact same spot!
Let's go there tomorrow!
I'd like to...
...if you're okay with being with me.
I told you to stop worrying about me!
Yeah.
That's why I'm trying not to let it get to me.
Then... let's go.
Yeah!
You'd better have brought a camera.
We can't just take photos with our cell phones.
Of course!
What about you?
Looks like we don't have to worry anymore.
Yeah. Thank goodness.
Right. Free time!
Where should we go first?
The morning markets, the morning markets.
Let's go eat the seafood Umibouzu recommends.
Huh?! Didn't you just eat breakfast?
For someone so small, you sure eat a lot.
What?! Fine then, I'll just go by myself!
It's okay. I'll come with you.
But you have to go halves with me.
All right. Let's go!
Wait up!
It looks delicious!
This feels great!
Trams are awesome!
Wow. it really is shaped like a star.
My turn! Hurry up, hurry up!
Rickshaws are the best!
How's this?
Hurry up and take it. This is embarrassing!
Never mind. I'll pose normally.
No way!
Don't forget why we came to this specific spot in the first place!
Remember, it's your turn next!
Awesome.
I really do still like Otani.
But... if I tell him I like him, it'll get awkward.
If we can stay like this forever, it's enough for me.
Excuse me.
Can you take a picture for us?
Sure.
Please!
'Kay, I'll take one for ya.
Hehe, he said "'kay".
Here ya go.
Thank you.
Are you from the Kansai district?
Uh... Yeah.
Say "You're kiddin' me"!
You're kiddin' me.
Ahh! It's a real Kansai accent!
Hey, hey.
Look, there's something over there.
Sorry!
That guy sure was cute.
But who was that tall girl? His girlfriend?
Huh? No way!
Right. No matter who's looking, no one would ever see me as his girlfriend.
Hey, Koizumi!
What?
It's your turn for a picture.
The magazine showed this spot too, right?
I don't think I can suddenly see you as my girlfriend.
I get what he means.
If he can't think of me as a girlfriend, it's pointless to go on liking him.
Koizumi?
Ahh, a picture, right?
Yes please! It's my turn.
It's fine.
I'll pretend nothing happened, and give up completely.
Should we head back to the meeting point soon?
Yeah.
What is it?
My wallet.... I've lost it!
What does it look like?!
It's red, and round, with a picture of a rabbit on it.
Did you lose it when we took that picture?
Let's go!
They said it hasn't been handed in.
Well, let's go look around the places we went to today again.
It's okay.
We wont find it.
There was only about 1,000 yen in it anyway.
1,000 yen?!
Do you know how much you could buy with that?!
You'll be cursed for giving it up, idiot!
But it's already time to meet up.
If we're late together again, more rumors will start.
Let them say whatever they want!
If you've got time to spout such pointless crap, you've got time to keep looking!
Otani...
Right. I'll take this side of the road, and you take that...
Wh- What's with you?
D- Do you like that wallet that much?
That's not it, you idiot!
Why am I an idiot? I'm trying to help you-
Shut up, you!
Why are you like this...
Just when...
Just when I'd finally decided to give up for good...
It's so hard...
...when you're so nice to me.
What's the matter with you?
That hurts!
What are you doing that for?
U...
"U"...?
Umibouzu!
He's a nice guy...
Hey!
G- G- G- G- Go say something to him!
M- Me? Me?!!
Hell yes! This is a once in a lifetime opportunity!
My wallet!
Ah, is this yours?
I was just about to turn it in at the police station.
Ah, of course. Sorry. I have 20-20 vision.
Are you on a class trip?
Yes!
Crap! It's past the time we were supposed to meet up.
What should we do?
Just run!
If you like, we can drop you off.
We were just about to get a taxi to take us to the train station.
Who are they?
Bouzu! I'm tired!
Hurry up with the car!
Hey, haven't I told you to call me "Papa"?
Umibouzu's wife?
Umibouzu's kid?
So he's married...
Hey boy, come help me hail a taxi.
Huh? Me?
Sure!
Right, let's go.
Gee, you sure are short.
But will there even be any taxis around here?
We already called ahead.
So, are you on a family vacation?
Yes. He always says how much he likes it here, so we come here regularly.
He may look scary, but he's a really gentle guy.
Where did you meet?
We went to the same high school.
So you've been going out since back then?
We didn't go out until long after we graduated.
I like you.
He confessed to me when we were in high school, but I rejected him in a big way.
We'd been friends for ages, so I couldn't imagine dating him or anything like that.
But...
The taxi's here!
Over here! Over here!
Now we're married, and we even have a son.
Life is really hard to predict, huh?
So even pickled radishes can become crabs, huh?
Huh? What do you mean?
Oh, nothing.
Come on. Let's go!
Yeah, that's right.
Even I didn't fall for Otani right away.
Otani's reply may be "sorry" right now,
but if we take things slowly, bit by bit...
...his answer might change.
How beautiful!
There's no need to force myself to give up.
I got to meet Umibouzu. I'm so happy.
Otani...
Sorry.
I'm going to have to take back that "Let's pretend nothing happened".
I still like you, after all.
Just keep that in mind.
'Kay.
What kind of dopey response is that?
That's what you get for saying things like that out of the blue!
I have to, since you're always slow on the uptake. Am I right?
What?!
Aren't you the slow one?
Just who was it that dropped their wallet?
Tha...That's that.
What's what?
That's just that!
What the heck are you on about?!
One day I'll make you regret saying "sorry",
so be prepared.
I like who I like.
You got a problem with that?
Otani-kun, are you doing anything for Christmas?
Ick!
No can do.
My middle school's basketball club is having a party.
Then that Kanzaki-san going too?
Lovely Complex~ Love Com.
Next: A Confrontation With The Ex-Girlfriend?! The Great Chest Display Plan!!
A Confrontation With The Ex-Girlfriend!? The Great Chest Display Plan!!
Be sure to watch!