Atsushi-kun...
Risa, after thinking about it,
Complete Despair! A Love Revival with the Ex?!
I've realized that you're all I think about.
I love you.
I got him!
I got Cain-sama!
Cain Osugi         [ Hahaha .  .  . ]
This is straining my heartstrings...
Risa, we've come to pick you up.
It's almost time for Hatsumode.
What on earth are you doing?
SUMIYOSHI GRAND SHRINE
As expected, there are a lot of people here for New Years Eve.
Where are darling and the others?
In the end there was no miracle, and another year passed.
Nobu-chan!
Ah! Darling!
Over here, over here.
It won't be as easy as it is in a game.
Hey.
What's the matter?
This is straining my heartstrings!
Huh?
The way Otani gets me so worked up everyday...
....it kinda pisses me off.
Grant me happiness this year!
Happiness!
You sure are funny.
What exactly is funny about me?!
I was giving you a compliment.
No. You were definitely making fun of me.
Noisy, aren't you.
That grin of yours is pissing me off.
Owww, oww, oww, oww!
Let go!
Just pretend we don't know them.
Suzuki-kun...
See what you've done? People are laughing at us again.
Well, I am just a comedienne.
So, should we go our separate ways from here?
Sure thing.
Risa, a moment.
Listen up. You need to do your best from now on.
With what?
That chest you didn't reveal over Christmas, reveal it now!
For a girl, you sure say some shameless things.
Huh? What's with this lack of motivation?!
A maiden's heart is fickle.
This is a rare opportunity. Why not keep it at it until morning?
Until morning? There you go saying shameless things again.
Nobu-chan, let's get going.
I'll be right there!
Listen. Do your best, okay?
See ya.
Otani-kun, you'd better walk Risa home properly.
Bye bye.
See you later.
What did Nobu-chan say to you just now?
Nothing...
Oh... I see.
So, what should we do now? Are you tired?
Huh? not really.
Then let's think of something to do until morning.
Wha-What do you mean by that?
Video game arcades and karaokes places are open so let's just stay out all night.
It is New Years, after all.
Ah. So that's what you meant.
What was that?
Nothing at all.
I hear the karaoke place by the train station has heaps of Umibouzu songs.
Seriously? Let's go!
Right! Let's go for all-night karaoke!
Yeah!
Hokkaido is cold but there's no point in worrying about that.
I could call you but we use the same cellphone.
Family discount plants are pretty awesome.
Even if tears of anger come,
I'm not interested riding around in a fancy boat
or taking an expensive looking dog for a walk.
You're not pale enough to need to use a parasol!
Man, you don't have what it takes to do this!
I can't believe the first thing I'm hearing from you this semester is this stupidity!
You spent all night getting worked up singing karaoke?
What the heck?!
But...
Don't tell me you're still concerned about that Kanzaki-san?
Of course I am.
Kanzaki-san is super cute.
I don't think it's even possible for Otani to like a girl like me....
That's not true.
But I've been rejected once already.
But you decided to keep trying anyway, didn't you?
An ex is just an ex, after all.
You have your good points too.
Like what?
Can't you think of any at all?!
You're funny! You're very funny!
Funny?
I mean, Otani-kun is always saying so, right?
Why not use your comedic skills to win his love?
That's right. I am funny.
Comedy... for love!
Good morning.
Otani-kun!
What the heck?!
How am I supposed to react to that?!
Come on, I'm just trying to tug at your heart strings...
Risa is so simple.
She sure is energetic, so early in the semester.
Say, how are things on Otani-kun's end?
Huh?
Has he said anything about Risa?
No, not really.
Ah!
Darling, what was that "ah!" just now?
Third years students should remember that entrance exams are just around the corner.
I'm completely stumped.
How can I get more of a romantic mood going?
What exactly would that be like between us, anyway?
Dummy.
Don't!
Ugh, that's disgusting.
Like hell!
I recall something that happened back when I was a student...
Ssssh! Keep your voice down!
But you're saying Kanzaki-san and her giant boyfriend broke up!
Still, Nakao-chi's info isn't always  reliable.
No. This time it's true.
He bumped into Kanzaki-san the other day, and heard it directly from her.
A-Are you serious?
He didn't ask why they broke up,
but apparently it happened just before Christmas.
So that's why she didn't come to the party...
S-So, does Otani know?
No. We don't want him to get any ideas. So we haven't told him.
Is that so...
I mean, last time Kanzaki-san said she just wanted to talk,
and look how worked up he got.
Th-that is true...
While Kanzaki-san's heart is still wounded...
...if only Otani-kun should happen to say some kind words to her....
Her heartstrings!
And up against a girl like her, Otani-kun would...
His heartstrings!
Still, who was the one who told me "An ex is just an ex, after all"?
The situation has changed.
In any case, we shouldn't let news of Kanzaki-san's break up reach Otani-kun.
Don't bring up Kanzaki-san in front of Otani at all, okay?
And we need to take countermeasures to prevent the two of them meeting...
Good afternoon.
Ahh! She appeared!
Uh, nothing.
Are you here to see Otani?
Yes. Did he already leave?
He did. Sorry.
Didn't he say he'd be right back after dropping by the staff room?
I told you, we can't let them meet.
Ah. Right.
I see.
So he's already gone home?
What's this? This crushing guilt...
My heart... My heart hurts...
Oh, did you two attend the basketball club's Christmas party, by any chance?
Uh, yes...
I thought so!
I heard that a lot of Atsushi-kun's friends went.
That's why I thought you might have gone too.
She calls him "Atsushi-kun"...
Actually, everyone is getting together next Sunday to play basketball again.
You're welcome to come along if you'd like to.
Will you be going to, Kanzaki-san?
Yes.
I'd like to surround myself with people in a cheery environment right now.
Truth be told, that tugged at my heartstrings just now.
This is bad.
I guess the thing about the break-up was true.
So, could you please let Atsushi-kun know about basketball on Sunday?
Thank you so much.
I'll be on my way, then.
She's so cute...
You're not wrong...
Hey, what are you doing saying a thing like that so casually?!
She said they're gonna play basketball again. Kanzaki-san and Otani-kun will meet!
Y-You're right!
What should we do?!
Sorry for the wait!
What's with you two?
Atsushi-kun...
Someone... Someone save me! Help! Help!
How rude!
Fine. I guess I am just a comedienne, after all.
What was that just now?
An impression of Kanzaki-san.
She dropped by earlier.
She said there's going to be another basketball get-together.
Oh. Nakao already told me about that.
Risa!
She already knew that darling would tell him!
That means she came in person just to see Otani-kun!
You two are going to come along too, right?
We'll come!
If Otani-kun is going, it'll bother you if you don't go, right?
Th-That's not true, but...
Imagine her making a face like this,
and saying "I just broke up with my boyfriend. I'm so lonely"...
A guy would want to do something about that, wouldn't he?
Oh no...
What are you whispering about over there?
Nothing!
Huh?
It's really bad this time.
I've gotta do something!
Hey!
Oh, he's here! He's here!
Hey! We've been waiting for you, Otani-kun.
Wha... What?
Th-These people...
Right. They're planning on getting Otani-kun and Kanzaki-san back together.
They definitely know about Kanzaki-san's break-up too.
Risa!
Kanzaki-san is already here.
Wh-What should we do?
She looks so obviously lonely.
This is bad.
She's exuding an aura that says "Comfort me".
Hey, what are you guys doing?
Nothing, nothing.
Risa, get Otani-kun's attention before he's swallowed up by that aura!
Wh-What do you mean "get his attention"?
Do whatever you have to, keep them from talking.
What is this, all of a sudden!
Owww!
What'd you do that for?!
No reason.
You trying to pick a fight, idiot?!
Lord.
Otani!
T-Teach me how to play basketball.
Huh? What's this all of a sudden?
Otani-kun, look over there.
Kanzaki-san seems really down for some reason.
Why don't you go on over?
Why? What happened to her?
Why don't you go ask her yourself?
Otani!
Come on, come on. Hurry up.
That hurts!
That hurts, you guys!
Both of you, know it off!
I can walk over there on my own!
I'll teach you how to play basketball later, Koizumi!
Atsushi-kun...
Uh... What's wrong?
Did something happen?
Uh... It's just, you don't seem well at all.
Is that so?
Oh, it's looking good.
We'll get to witness the moment they get back together first hand!
Otani, Fight-o!
What the heck are you guys doing?
Atsushi-kun...
What?!
Uh... No...
I didn't mean that...
S-So, how's the giant... I mean, your boyfriend?
We broke up not long ago.
Risa...
I think I'm gonna go home, after all.
Then I'll...
It's fine. I just want to be alone.
Risa...
Atsushi-kun?
Wh-What?
Can we see each other again sometime?
There's something I'd like to discuss with you.
Right now, they're probably locked in the storage closet like before.
And when the door is opened, they'll probably be together again.
What's this?
A Christmas present.
You really like me that much?
It is funny, isn't it?
If it's me trapped in there with him, all he can do is derive amusement from me.
In the end, a comedienne is no match for an ex-girlfriend.
I've had enough of that Otani!
Oh. So this is where you went.
If you stay in a place like this, you'll catch a cold.
What... are you doing here?
I was thinking "Maybe Koizumi is crying again", or something along those lines.
Me?
Why?
Ugh. What an ugly expression.
Why...
What about Kanzaki-san?
It's been a while since I last spoke to Kanzaki. It was pretty exhausting, for some reason.
Because you were nervous?
No, it wasn't that.
Why, huh?
I don't really know myself.
It's snowing.
I wonder if there'll be snowdrifts tomorrow...
Why...?
You idiot.
What's so funny, dammit?!
I don't know.
Maybe someone like you is more suited for me.
What did you say?
Just talking to myself.
It's looking good.
Looks like it.
Before we go home, let's go to that karaoke place by the train station again.
Karaoke!
Every time Otani says or does something,
I end up going to heaven, or hell.
My whole world has been revolving around Otani, going round and round.
You're so annoying!
What the hell?! I haven't said anything bad!
Shut up! You seriously piss me off!
I'm inviting you for some fun karaoke... What's that attitude?!
Shut up! I told you to shut up!
You amazon!
Can we see each other again sometime?
There's something I'd like to discuss with you.
Uh... I don't think I can do that.
Well, there's this one hopeless idiot...
...who'll probably end up crying if I see you again.
So...
Sorry. I don't think I can do that.
The second Valentine's episode is all about the winning chocolate!
"Winning?"
Ho           pe
Koizumi, are you expecting to win a kiss or something?
This is bad! She's acting weird!
Don't try to run!
Lovely Complex~ Love Com.
Next: Recapture Love! Improve As A Girl with Winning Chocolate!!
Recapture Love! Improve As A Girl with Winning Chocolate!!
Be sure to watch!