The place where we made our first step...
nee, yakusoku dayo
It's a place we should commemorate, right?
kakegae no nai stage wo
Thanks for coming with me.
Of course. I slept early last night,
so I'm totally fine.
Ah ready? We go! Yes!
Please take me out!
Mei was the one who didn't wake up—
even though I tried to wake her.
But you'd never leave me behind, right?
Stand up! Without you!
Wh-Who knows? I wonder...
nemurenai yoru to setsunai asa wo
You're so stubborn, Suzu-nyan!
Stop it, Mei!
Suzu-nyan, you're so warm!
I said stop, Mei!
tsunagi tomeru no wa yume nandakara
Big Sister took her first step here, too.
And today,
we're going to stand on the finals stage she
was supposed to stand on three years ago.
ushinai kaketa utagoe mo
tomo ni asu ni kimi ni tooi ni hibiku you ni to
We really made it.
Yeah.
Look! It's sunrise!
How beautiful!
toki ni wa mune ga itakute (feeling heart)
Let's make it the best performance.
Yeah.
sore demo muchuu de
Let's go back before we catch a cold.
Wake me up! Wake me up!
Kotono.
hikari to kage wo
Happy birthday.
nee yakusoku dayo
ano basho de kagayaki au koto
Thanks.
kimi to nareba takaku toberu
Hey!
makenaiyotte waraou
Sakura...
nee yubikiri shiyou
dare hitori furimukanai you ni
It's so pretty.
It's so refreshing.
zutto tooku wo mite
It's going to be an unforgettable day.
hashire tsuzuketeiku
The finals stage.
Let's fight with our all.
Yup.
The weather's fine today.
Are you there, Mana?
You are, right?
You promised you wouldn't disappear
until you saw the finals performance.
Oh...?
Not here?
What is it?
Where's Mr. Makino?
He was here at the end of rehearsal...
Could he be in the other dressing room?
He wasn't there.
Where could he be?
I don't see Mana anywhere.
Yeah, she's been gone since this morning.
What?
Could it be she's already...?
No, I don't think she disappeared yet.
She said she'd watch
everyone's finals performance.
She was always good at keeping her word
for important things like that.
But she did seem really distressed.
Maybe she's trying to conserve
her energy as much as possible.
Maybe.
There you are, Mr. Makino!
What's up?
Actually, I wanted to tell
Miss Mana something.
Is she here right now?
What?
Yeah...
Yeah, she's here...
Where?
Miss Mana, I'll be singing, putting in my all.
And I'll fight against Kotono and
the others with all my might.
So please watch me.
Big Sister...
I want you to watch me...
The finals performance of
Moon Tempest's Kotono Nagase.
The Next Venus Grand Prix finals battle
between Sunny Peace and Moon Tempest
will begin momentarily.
All our seniors are here!
Y-Yeah...
Hey, hey.
If you don't greet them properly,
you'll get beat up by
the scary person from LizNoir.
Wh-What?!
W-We better hurry, then!
The finals three years ago...
It was Mana Nagase vs. LizNoir.
To be honest, I couldn't imagine
LizNoir winning.
Mana at the time was unbeatable.
That finals turned out to be a mirage.
Fans are still after that mirage today.
Along with you and me.
You're right.
But watching the semi-finals
changed my thinking.
Between the current LizNoir and TRINITYAiLE,
I can't say who'd win.
Next year's even more of a toss-up.
Same goes with us, too.
I gave you the game this time—
It was a narrow margin.
Next time, I'll win.
This feeling in our hearts
Together
Let's shine
Brightly!
I should be used to this path home (the usual town)
Amazing...
That vortex of light looks like stars!
It's strange, it looks brighter today
Feelings are flowing into me
from all around this place.
My heart is beating so fast.
Way faster than ever before!
I won't forget the tears from that day
That's a promise
Impatience, dreams and excitement
There's more to this sensation
than just pleasure.
It's scary and it feels like
it's about to burst.
I don't want to regret anything
If I do ever get lost
But it continues to beat my heart passionately!
It's my very own beating heart!
The important things
The beating of my heart lets me know
These feelings in my heart
If I can face them
I can
Establish myself
Become
Even
Stronger
This feeling in our hearts
Together
Let's shine
Brightly!
I want to illuminate you brightly!
Sunny P! Sunny P!
Hold me tight right now
What should I do?
The beating doesn't stop
Are you watching, Mana?
Five peace signs together
Become a star
I want to shine all the time
Gekka Hakanabi
A single flower blooms at night
Big Sister, are you watching?
A precious and beautiful sight
Three years ago, you said you wanted me
to watch your finals performance.
I really understand how you felt now.
Why am I shedding tears?
Everything is out of focus in front of me
And yet, that time, I...
I breathed hard
I looked straight ahead
But... I can say this now.
But I was still trembling a little
I'm glad you were there, Big Sister.
In the true darkness
I couldn't see anything
But I found out what it means "to shine"
The moonlight shines on your light
I'm glad you were an idol, Big Sister!
The first time I felt this true wish
It's so bright and brings happiness
Everything starts to change
The waxing and waning shakes the darkness in my heart
I'll accept it and won't hesitate anymore
I'll do as much as I want to in this moment
It's so uncertain
I could crumble at any moment
But you illuminate me
So I'm able to shine
I was watching you, Kotono.
It was the best finals.
Thank you.
Big Sister...
This is the finals!
The audience is fired up to the max!
Making their debut on the same day
from Hoshimi Production,
the newcomers Sunny Peace
and Moon Tempest!
The two lowest-ranked groups
of the preliminaries
unexpectedly face off in the finals!
They're the dark horses
of this year's Grand Prix!
And now, the winner gets determined here!
Next Venus Grand Prix!
Who is the winner?!
This is the final count!
And the winner is...
A draw?!
Nobody was expecting this!
A...
...draw...
This is an unexpected development.
According to Grand Prix regulations...
The results just came in.
A draw that occurs with
astronomical probability.
When that happens in the finals...!
Both groups are tie-score winners!
We won...
All of us together...
Kotono! We did it!
I thought it was a wonderful performance!
Thanks, Suzu-nyan!
Thanks to you, we all had fun singing.
Y-You can't say such a thing right now!
I had a lot of fun.
Yeah, I don't want it to end yet.
Come on, we need to greet our audience.
Right, Miss Haruko?
I know, right?
Were you watching, Mana?
The finals stage where you wanted to stand...
They all performed admirably.
What did you think? Amazing, right?
Kotono and Sakura...
At last, they each performed with
their own self-discovered voice.
That was the performance you wanted, right?
Yup.
Mana?
Now there's nothing to worry about.
Thank you.
Mana...
Everyone, that was
an outstanding performance.
Congratulations.
You all did well.
Thank you very much!
The winner's performance
is happening after this.
Since you're tie-score winners,
both Sunny Peace and
Moon Tempest can perform.
That means...!
We can keep performing then?
Yeah.
All right!
Let's standby with the songs
each group prepared—
Actually, Mr. Makino...
What do you think of this idea?
Mr. Makino.
Was Miss Mana happy with what she saw?
Yeah.
I think I saw her, too.
My sister in the audience.
I heard her voice, too.
What was she saying?
She said, "Thank you."
Yeah, she did say that.
Hey!
The new setlist was approved.
Got it!
All right everyone, get ready!
Yes!
Mr. Makino...
Where's Mana?
No...
I didn't get to say goodbye yet...
Mei.
You still need to perform.
Go do it for Mana.
Yeah... You're right!
I will!
They went beyond my expectations.
Yes.
And... you, too.
Thank you very much.
A lot happened,
but I think you're finally full-fledged now.
Um, Mr. Saegusa.
I've got a favor to ask.
Mana... You always disappear unexpectedly.
You don't let me say anything.
I'm still in the middle
of a faraway dream
To the utmost
Go on...
As the precious things
stay the same
From the beginning
Wow! A shooting star!
I want to bring my voice to you
Right now
song for you!
Actually...
Your gaze
Will you be my manager?
It was
Your gaze
Manager? Isn't this a bit...
I won't make you regret it.
That lit up the cold world for me
I won't make you regret it, no matter what.
There could be a ton of challenges.
My emotions are overflowing endlessly
But someday you'll feel like saying,
"I'm glad I became a manager
and said yes that time," I promise!
Even if it costs me my life.
With pride in my heart
When she makes that face,
she carries out her words no matter what.
I sing out
Even if it costs her life, huh?
She didn't need to go that far.
Hey! Makino!
You can't sneak out in the middle!
It's an important performance.
Give me a break at least at the end.
It's time, right?
I'm surprised you knew I was here.
It's the second time.
Still, you can be pretty dull, Makino.
I'm... aware of that.
You don't change at all, Makino.
You, too.
So you don't regret accepting
my invitation that time, right?
That's right.
But I really wanted to be a top idol.
Then, I would've been able
to fulfill my real dream.
Your real dream?
Yup.
I wanted to make you the manager
of a top idol, Makino.
That's... your... real dream?
That's right.
And my only regret is
how I never got to tell you in person.
No way...
But I'm fine now!
There are others who'll
fulfill this dream for me.
Right, Makino?
Why...
Why did you choose me?
Why...?
Let's see...
Well, you're pure, hard-working, serious...
I mean, there were lots of things
that bothered me, too.
But I'm glad...
...that I fell in love with you, Makino.
I'm... the manager...
That's why...
That's why... I always...
If only I could kiss you.
Song for you.
The closest
You were always the closest to me
Always watching
Always watching me
To the precious days I spent with you
I want to send a "thank you"
The courage
The courage you gave me
I'll hold it in my arms and hope for tomorrow
I'll become the brightest light
With pride in my heart
I sing out
There's still a long road ahead.
Yup.
Everyone, this is the last song.
It feels a bit sad.
I want to keep singing.
It feels like I'm dreaming.
Me too. It all seems so surreal.
This isn't a dream, it's reality.
The only thing left to do
is to deliver the best performance we can.
Hey, hey. Do you think
we can reach the top as idols?
We will!
My heart's beating fast
and telling me we will!
This is the starting line of our next goal.
Hey! What makes it a coincidence?
What makes it meant to be?
When I'm with you I don't know
Ah The strong impression like a dream
And the impulse I felt the day we met
e l'impeto che ho provato quando ci siamo incontrati
We drew each other in without a second thought
Without realizing
The works of fate
We were always there for each other
Isn't it funny?
In the center of our miraculous meeting
It's okay for me to cry a little, right?
The story that begins with goodbye
The heartrending feeling stabbed
Deep into my heart is painful
But when I start to run
I create the starting line there
With you (with you)
I want to keep running
Destiny
Pray for you
kokoro wa motto chikaku naru doko ni iyou tomo
Minareta hazu no keshiki na no ni
Naze ka kyou wa kagayaiteru ashidori karuku
Dare ka ni tsutaetai shoudou
Tonari wo mireba onaji kimochi
emi ga rensa suru
Omoide ni suru ni wa mada
Hayai kedo hokorashii jikan
Kimi to issho datta kidoairaku subete
Ima wo ikiru asu wo nozomu
Chikara ni natteru kara
Pray for you
atarashii monogatari no peeji hirakou
tachidomaru nante niawanai
Pray for you
sou iu kimi no kotoba ga itai hodo wakaru yo
Dakara mayowanai furimukazu yuke
MOON TEMPEST
SUNNY PEACE
Mana Nagase
Pray for you
watashi nari no puraido misete yaru
MOON TEMPEST
SUNNY PEACE
Mana Nagase
The Story That Begins With Goodbye