See you later.
I can, too...
LizNoir, the hottest idol group
among young women right now,
FINALLY ANNOUNCED THE LONG AWAITED SINGLE!
NEWS
The Current Buzz!
Idols to
Watch Out For !
The Current Buzz!
Idols to
Watch Out For !
just announced the release
of their new single.
Don't miss Rio Kanzaki and Aoi Igawa
shine in their new music video.
Morning, Kotono!
Morning.
Morning, Kotono.
Would you like scrambled eggs or an omelet?
Um...
Hey, you two, did you take out the trash yet?
S-Suzu and Shizuku,
let's wake up now.
Give two more hours...
Seconded...
What...?
Come on!
There's a delicious meal waiting for you!
Go wash your face...
...and get changed!
Chisa, where is my uniform?
Suzu, don't undress here!
So...
What's your preference?
What everyone else likes.
CHORE CHART
Saki
Suzu
Kotono
Shizuku
Sakura
Chisa
Trash
Food
Cleaning
nee, yakusoku dayo
kakegae no nai stage wo
Ah ready? We go! Yes!
Please take me out!
Stand up! Without you!
nemurenai yoru to setsunai asa wo
tsunagi tomeru no wa yume nandakara
ushinai kaketa utagoe mo
tomo ni asu ni kimi ni tooi ni hibiku you ni to
toki ni wa mune ga itakute (feeling heart)
sore demo muchuu de
Wake me up! Wake me up!
hikari to kage wo
nee yakusoku dayo
ano basho de kagayaki au koto
kimi to nareba takaku toberu
makenaiyotte waraou
nee yubikiri shiyou
dare hitori furimukanai you ni
zutto tooku wo mite
hashire tsuzuketeiku
Hoshimi High School
I see...
That sounds lively and fun.
I don't know.
We sometimes argue over
Miss Saki's nit-picky rules.
What do you do when that happens, Kotono?
Huh?
"I'm fine either way."
"I'll follow what everyone decides on."
Spot on?
Not at all.
You're all a group, right?
You all have to get along!
You know me.
I'm not good at that kind of thing.
Hoshimi Production
Well, you've gathered quite a group
with a diverse range of skills and characters.
I really hope they work out together.
It's our job to help them achieve that, right?
A group is all about balance.
If anything is off, it can collapse any moment.
Yes.
Excuse me.
Is Makino available?
That's "Mr. Makino," to you.
Or call me "Manager."
So, why is everyone gathered here?
We've finished our core
and vocal training for the day.
And so...
I am sick of basic training every single day!
It's about time we start practicing
choreography or do a recording!
Well... How can we record
when we don't even have a song?
That's what I said, too.
But I can understand
where Suzu is coming from.
Yes, basic training is important,
but doing it so long without trainers
or a goal makes us anxious.
That's true.
You've got a point there.
So, we actually talked about it...
And we're wondering if we could practice
choreography of an easy song.
Would that be a problem?
I think it's fine.
Basic training is a drag
when there's no motivation.
I get that, but...
It's your job to get the girls excited,
right, Makino?
You say that like people
won't misinterpret it.
What do you mean?
Oh, nothing.
I want to make sure this
is everyone's request.
Shizuku? Chisa?
Yup.
I'm not too confident, but I'll do my best.
How about you, Kotono?
I...
As long as I can start real lessons,
I'm fine with it.
I see.
All right, then I'll find a song
to work on by tomorrow.
All right!
This is so great!
Let's do our best, Kotono!
We did it!
Y-Yeah...
Now we've got singing
and dancing to work on!
As expected of Makino.
The manager who chose me
as the center idol!
He really gets it.
What? Suzu, you're the center idol?
Well of course! I am the daughter
of the prestigious Narumiya family.
Our name is known to everyone
in Hoshimi City.
O-Oh, I see...
I think we can be a fun group with you, Suzu.
That is right, indeed!
Hey!
How about we go out to eat
as a celebration tonight?
Splendid idea!
What is the dress code for that establishment?
What? I don't think it would be
that kind of place...
Miss Saki, what do you think?
Well, as long as we don't get home too late...
And I actually have lots to say to everyone.
Be quiet at night.
Put away your dirty clothes.
You'll oversleep again
if you don't go to bed now.
So it's set. Let's go, Kotono!
Yeah?
Sorry.
I still have things to do.
Things to do?
You all have fun.
Bye.
Hey!
There she goes.
Yes...
It's hamburg steak tonight!
Wow, yay!
Don't you know the curry flavor is better?
Leave me alone.
This is my dinner.
It's Kotono.
Good evening.
Hey!
What was that?
Oh... It's nothing.
Kotono... Late training today?
Yes.
I see.
If you get back too late,
you'll get everyone worried.
Mr. Makino.
Why does it have to be a group?
You do know that the Venus Program's
top-ranking idols are groups, right?
But my sister was a solo artist.
Well, I consider her as a sort of miracle.
I've come to understand after
three years of trial and error.
In order to satisfy the audience,
you can't just be good at singing or dancing.
You can't survive in today's program
with just a unique character, either.
That's why I needed a
diverse range of characters.
Character...?
It hasn't come together yet,
but eventually everyone's characters
will blend together and become a great appeal.
That's what I believe.
Still not satisfied?
To be honest...
I still don't understand.
But...
I'll be okay as long as I can stand on
the stage my sister dreamed about.
Well, if you want a great concert,
you'll eventually need to talk to everyone.
I know.
All right.
Then I'm counting on you to take care of
our new member who starts tomorrow.
What?
It might surprise you.
Especially since she's—
I-I'm going to jog home!
Hey!
I'll get to meet her tomorrow!
Well... We all can't change overnight.
Hoshimi Production
What?
I'm Nagisa Ibuki.
A second-year at Hoshimi High.
It's very nice to meet you all.
Nagisa?!
But why?!
I secretly applied to this
agency when you did, too.
Is she a friend?
Y-Yeah.
Are you Sakura?
Yes.
Kotono talks about you all the time.
I see.
She was wrong about you
when she first met you,
so she felt really bad.
What?
She couldn't understand your
reasoning to become an idol,
but she's impressed at how you take on
the lessons more seriously than anyone.
She's been wanting
to apologize for a while now.
Nagisa!
I knew you hadn't told her yet!
It's better to communicate
these things, you know?
That's how you get closer!
I've never seen Kotono make
that kind of face before.
Yeah, it's a bit surprising.
All right, let's start with the basics as usual.
I'll announce the song after that.
Yes!
Not fair.
Not fair?
You could've told me Nagisa was joining.
Actually, you're the one
who left when I was about to.
Kotono!
Let's do some stretches together.
Y-Yeah!
Idoly Pride.
And now, in celebration of
Nagisa joining the group...
Cheers!
I never expected you to be interested
in becoming an idol, Nagisa.
I would see you working hard
and it made me want to try, too!
Does it bother you?
Not at all.
To be honest, I was feeling a little lonely.
So thank you.
Hey Suzu, so why do you
want to become an idol?
Huh? M-Me?
Yeah.
Everyone else, too.
Right, Kotono?
Huh?
We'll be working together as a team now,
so let's get to know each other better.
Right...
Well,
I thought it would be a breeze
for me to get to the top.
I've always loved idols.
Chisa, you too, right?
Y-Yeah.
I knew my sister would pass the audition,
but I don't know why I did.
I wonder if I passed as a backup idol.
Did I just trigger something?
How about you, Sakura?
I'm here because...
My heart pounded really fast!
Um... I do not understand.
So... It was some sort of fate, maybe?
How about you, Shizuku?
Because I... love idols.
So the same as us.
Yup.
So... Um...
Care to tell us?
Me?
I want to stand at the top of
the Venus Program for my sister.
That's my goal.
Your sister?!
Nagase?!
Could... your sister be...?!
What? It's Miss Mana, right?
So it is!
Late, much?
I see, for your sister...
Is that bad?
No, I'm very moved.
How Miss Mana's spirit is being kept alive.
Miss Mana was an amazing idol.
Miss Mana was that amazing?
How could you say such a thing!
Who do you think Miss Mana is?!
She is the Miss Mana!
Known as the miraculous star idol
who put Hoshimi City on the map!
Her video became one of the top ten
most watched in Japan within a year!
The Next Venus Grand Prix
was just a passage point.
She was eventually set to stand
at the pinnacle of idols.
You all have no idea how hard it was,
even for me, to acquire her autograph!
Stay right there!
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
See?!
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Wow, that's amazing!
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
You are witnessing Hoshimi City's
prestigious Narumiya family's power!
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
That is, my power!
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Impressed?
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Dear
Miss Suzu
Mana
Mana Nagase's Autograph
I'll keep quiet.
She was an amazing idol,
even to her sister's eyes, right?
Well of course!
Her voice, her smile!
Anyone would be captivated by her,
seeing her up close.
That is why Kotono,
you must take up her mantle—
Stop.
Kotono?
I'm sorry.
I'm gonna go back to my room now.
Suzu...
W-Was it my fault?!
No, I wasn't being mindful enough, either.
To take up the mantle
of such a great idol...
She must be feeling incredible pressure.
Do you think Kotono's mad?
No.
I don't think she is.
I think she ran away because she felt
responsible for making it awkward.
Ran away...?
Kotono's always been a little complicated.
Smiling when it's not fun for her,
and acting like she's interested
when she's not...
She doesn't like doing that.
So she'd rather leave like she did now.
I wonder if she'll be able
to work with us like that.
I know, right?
But I think she knows this herself, too.
I personally like people like that.
Hoshimi Production
We made it through the whole song already!
Barely, yeah.
We're still off rhythm and all over the place.
But it sure is fun.
Kotono, what's the matter?
Will I really be able to catch up
to my sister at this slow pace?
What?
Sorry!
I'm gonna go get some fresh air.
Kotono...?
One of your idols?
LizNoir...?
Kotono, what's the matter?
Oh... It's nothing.
Sorry to startle you. They're my guests.
They stopped by to say hi
for old time's sake.
Mr. Saegusa.
I'm...
That matter is done.
I don't intend on returning to
Van Production.
What if we leave Van Production
and transfer here?
Give me a break.
I have no desire to rock the boat
with Asakura any further.
Then, how do you explain Mana Nagase?
You're the one who made her.
Big Sister...?
Big Sister?
So you are Mana Nagase's...
Yes, I am her sister.
You do resemble her.
This is perfect.
Could you watch their lesson as a favor?
What?
Mr. Saegusa, what are you—?
What do you think, Kotono?
If you're aiming for the top,
don't you want to steal
whatever you can get from LizNoir?
The top...?
I understand.
Please watch us.
Th-Things just got serious...
Well, as you can see,
they're just beginners who just started lessons.
That's all right.
We all start out as beginners.
Could Rio and I dance through it once?
What?
You two have yet to watch
the example video for the song, right?
It's not necessary.
But how could you dance without it?
They can... probably.
What?
LizNoir is the real deal.
They were always in competition
with Miss Mana.
A-Amazing...
That's right...
This is what idols are!
This is what... idols are...
Now...
Let's try it together, shall we?
Yes!
Hoshimi Production
President's Office
So, what did you think?
If they're trying to make it
to the top of the Venus Program,
they'd get there quicker with us.
You're right.
But that'd be boring, don't you think?
I'll make you regret this no matter what.
How did the lesson with LizNoir go?
To be honest,
they were on a whole other level...
But you can't reach the top
unless you surpass them.
But I had a lot of fun.
Huh?
The LizNoir duo was incredible!
They showed me what idols are...
Miss Mana must've been incredible, too!
Of course she was!
That's right!
I want to practice even more,
and work hard to become idols like them!
Mr. Makino.
What can we do to win?
Kotono...
I already told you.
Shi-Shizuku...
You recorded their dance, right?
I did...
And the lesson after that...
Why don't we watch them together?
I thought we could do a review meeting...
Yeah! That's a great idea!
Yeah, we should review our good
points and bad points together.
Oh, I'm making the wrong pose.
Right off the bat?! How sloppy!
You missed, too, Suzu.
Everyone's Looking for the Answer
All right, let's review it
from the beginning.
Everyone's Looking for the Answer
You've got this, everyone!
tashikametai yo doko made toberu no ka (tobitai yo)
tsubasa nante nakutatte sora e to (te wo nobase Jumping)
kore made yori korekara da to shinjiteru (korekara sa)
dakara motto nani ka nani ka wo (tsukamanakya nanda)
nageki no naka ni mieta hikari ga donna imi ni kawaru ka
wakarikakete kita kara ato ippo darou?
tooi ho to agaru yo soko e ikitai to
subete norikoete tadori tsuku ni wa
mata tarinai no doushite tarinai no
aseru na aseru yo kodou ga atsui
moe agaru yo soko e ikitai yo
koe ni dete shimau utatte shimaunda
yokan yori hayaku
The Last Chance, wow!