Leave the group...?
That's right.
Shizuku, Chisa, you two as well.
What?
Us, too...?
I want the three of you to form a new group.
What?!
nee, yakusoku dayo
kakegae no nai stage wo
Ah ready? We go! Yes!
Please take me out!
Stand up! Without you!
nemurenai yoru to setsunai asa wo
tsunagi tomeru no wa yume nandakara
ushinai kaketa utagoe mo
tomo ni asu ni kimi ni tooi ni hibiku you ni to
toki ni wa mune ga itakute (feeling heart)
sore demo muchuu de
Wake me up! Wake me up!
hikari to kage wo
nee yakusoku dayo
ano basho de kagayaki au koto
kimi to nareba takaku toberu
makenaiyotte waraou
nee yubikiri shiyou
dare hitori furimukanai you ni
zutto tooku wo mite
hashire tsuzuketeiku
Hoshimi Production
I've been thinking for a while now about
how to bring out the best in each of you.
Hoshimi Production
Hoshimi Production will launch two groups,
with Kotono and Sakura as the leaders.
I know that everyone may feel
startled over this sudden decision.
But I want you to believe in this decision.
I'm... the leader?
Will you tell us your reasoning?
That's...
Did you really think we would agree
to your unilateral decision
without some sort of justification?
We've been working hard all this time together.
Are you saying that this group isn't working?
Kotono and Sakura, I think each of you
has your own unique strengths.
You have to be separated in order for each
of your lights to shine the brightest.
Like the moon and sun.
The moon...
And sun?
That's right.
The moon and sun exist far from each other.
The world of day and night...
They bring each other out
because they're separated that way.
And each of your lights will illuminate
Mei, Suzu, Nagisa, Saki, Chisa,
and Shizuku brilliantly.
Quietly... yet vividly.
Powerfully and warmly...
I regret not coming up
with this idea from the start.
I'm sorry.
If you've really thought this through,
there's no objection on my part.
What?
I agree, too!
If you think you are too burdened,
I can switch places with you.
Suzu...
I think they're both suited
to be the leaders, too.
Nagisa...
Are you two okay with it?
Yup.
How about you, Chisa?
Y-Yup...
Okay.
Kotono...
I believe in you, Mr. Makino.
Please make us both shine brilliantly.
I will.
Hey, so is Sakura's group only three members?
Actually, I've scouted a new member.
I'll introduce her tomorrow.
Hoshimi Production
Come on in, both of you.
Hey!
A student from our school?
I'll be working with you all starting today.
I'm Haruko Saeki,
I'm 17 years old!
I-I'm 17 years...
Old!
Miss Haruko...
What is with that outfit?
Well since I'm 17!
She is the office worker, is she not?
Office worker...?
No.
She's one of our idols here.
I never got popular, though.
Weren't you two school grades below my sister?
So that would make you... 20?
Haruko Saeki... She came up.
Only three hits... though...
B-But you look great in that uniform!
I really thought you were 17!
Yeah, you're so cute!
Like a real student!
Like a real...?
Are you done?
Y-Yup, go on, take it away.
I'm Rei Ichinose, 18 years old.
My specialty is dancing.
Rei's won first place
in the national dance competition, too!
Amazing, right?
National competition...
How did Mr. Makino scout
such a talented person...?
I'm the one who gave him the tip!
She would always watch me practice.
She's the reason why I met Mr. Makino.
Hoshimi Production?
So you represent an entertainment agency?
I'm in the middle of forming a new idol group.
Idol...?
May I join the agency, too?
And that's why you're here?
Yes.
I've seen Rei dance, too.
I'd say her ability is impeccable.
Miss Haruko's taken lessons
diligently for years, too.
So her singing and dancing are at a high level.
With the both of them,
Sakura, Chisa and Shizuku...
I think the five of you will become a group
that illuminates each other's
strengths to the fullest.
This five of us, a group?
Are you the leader?
Yup! I am.
I see.
I'm here because I heard you
were all aiming for the top as idols.
It's great to meet you all.
Yup! Glad to have you!
Will you teach me how to dance?
So it's the five of us now.
I'm looking forward to working with you all.
Chisa, is something on your mind?
You seemed down all day today...
Is it because I'm the leader?
No, it's not.
It's just...
It's just?
I'm not in the same group
as my sister anymore...
And as far as dancing and singing,
I'm behind everyone.
I'm worried I won't make it
as an idol by myself...
Chisa...
You're not by yourself.
We're all doing this together!
We've got this!
I'm here, too...
Yeah... Thanks.
Hoshimi Production
I
I am exhausted.
I bet you are, Suzu.
You were working hard.
Yes, while I let Kotono
take the leader position,
I have yet to give up on
becoming the center idol.
On the day of our debut,
the idol world will be shaken.
Suzu Narumiya will shine in Hoshimi City!
Then let's first remember the
choreography to make that happen.
Right, Kotono?
Huh?
Oh...
Yeah.
Suzu, you were sloppy in
a few sections of the dance,
so you were out of sync with everyone.
What is it?
Kotono, you were frowning
all throughout practice.
What?
Idols are always smiling
when they're singing, right?
So you better smile, Kotono!
Hey! Mei! Wait!
Oh?
H-Hey... Q-Q-Quit it...!
Like this? Like this?
Look at her face!
That's a funny face, Kotono.
But it's kind of cute.
They love it!
They love it, Kotono!
You should get changed already.
Okay!
Wow!
That's what experience looks like...
I've been taking lessons for a while now.
But I'm still not as sharp as Rei.
Miss Saeki, you have a habit of moving
your limbs first when you move left and right.
It would help if you were more
mindful of your body's center.
I-I see.
Interesting.
Miss Kawasaki, you tend to rush the tempo.
Miss Hyodo, you've got great rhythm,
but your movements are small.
You should make bigger movements.
Yes!
O-Okay.
And Miss Shiraishi.
Yes?
You tend to lag behind because
you try to follow the others.
If you don't dance on the beat,
you'll appear out of sync on stage.
Y-Yes...
Let's try it again.
What? Already?
Let's not waste any practice
time sitting around.
Come on, stand up!
Y-Yes!
Wow, so strict!
Thank you.
I appreciate it.
Seems like you've gathered quite the characters.
Yes.
Because I was fortunate to meet them,
I was able to set my mind on
separating Kotono and Sakura.
Even I was surprised when you said you
were going to split the group in two.
I didn't think you would
approve of it so readily, either.
Thank you very much.
Your vision of the new Hoshimi Production
idol is beginning to take shape.
Yes.
Well, if they come together, that is.
Right...
This is where you show your faith, Makino!
Right.
Did you make this coffee, Mr. Saegusa?
Yeah.
It's pretty bitter.
Sure is.
My body hurts...
Let's ice ourselves again.
We need to soothe our muscles
that worked so hard.
Th-Thank you very much...
Is everyone all right?
Yup, we're hanging in there.
Okay.
This is for everyone.
There were sections that
weren't mastered yet today,
so please review them
before our next practice.
What?
Right... now...?
I've got a matter to attend to,
so I'll be leaving now.
What? How about dinner?
I'll be eating over there,
so please don't worry.
I don't think you'll see me
here at night too much.
Goodbye.
A matter to attend to this late?
She's so mysterious.
Idoly Pride.
How's practice?
Huh?
Are you able to keep up with everyone?
Yeah...
I'm okay...
Are you sure?
Yup.
I'm fine. Don't worry about me...
Miss Rei, stop! Hold on!
We already took a break an hour ago.
But we're still not ready to dance
through the whole practice yet.
You and I are used to dancing so we're fine,
but the others are still beginners,
so it could be good to take it a little easier.
Will you be saying that on stage, too?
What?
Will the other idols take it easy on us, too?
Once we debut, we're all professionals.
That's...
I saw the video of the
joint lesson with LizNoir.
To be honest, I was shocked
to see where everyone was at.
In order to surpass them
starting from this point,
I don't think we can afford to take any breaks.
Miss Rei...
You're able to think like that
because you can actually dance.
Chisa...
I started out as a beginner myself, too.
Then why...
How did you come to be like that?
I don't give up,
I keep practicing,
and I don't stop once I start.
I'm not able to do the same as you.
I was with my sister...
I want to be with my sister...
So I don't see myself
being able to do this right now...
When you haven't done anything yet?
Do you really like idols?
Let's call it a day for today.
It won't do us any good if we
keep practicing like this.
Mr. Makino, is that all right?
Yeah.
Rei and Chisa, is that all right?
That's fine.
Yes.
If we're done, I'll be excusing myself.
What? Will you be late again tonight?
Yes... Thank you for today.
Chisa and Shizuku,
what do you feel like eating?
When you feel down, you gotta fill
yourself up with your favorite food!
Let's buy it on our way back.
Then...
Bananas...
Mille crepe...
Sounds good.
How about you, Sakura?
Were you thinking about Rei just now?
Yes.
I'm curious about a lot of things.
Like, where does she go after practice?
Why does she want to become an idol?
Why is she in such a rush?
In a rush...?
Yup, it's hard to say,
but she reminds me of Kotono from before.
Maybe Miss Rei also has an
important reason to become an idol.
An important reason...?
Food
Super Market
What should I get?
Thank you very much.
Next customer, please!
Thank you for waiting.
Would you like a bag?
Oh my gosh, could that be...?
It's pretty clear.
It's Miss Rei.
Miss Rei has a part-time job?!
One daikon radish and three onions.
The total comes out to...
What?!
E-Excuse me.
Your total comes out to 104,700 yen.
¥
Grand Total
Subtotal
VAT
...100,000 yen?!
I-I'm very sorry!
I can't believe you were working part-time
at a supermarket so close to us.
I started right before I moved into the dorms.
I'm usually working in the back,
but I've been put on
cashier duty starting today.
I didn't expect to be caught on the same day.
Why were you hiding this?
I didn't want you all to worry about me.
What... do you mean?
Tell us why.
I want to know more about you, Miss Rei.
We're in a group together!
Okay.
To be honest, initially,
I didn't want to become an idol.
I don't have any dreams
of becoming one, either.
Really...?
I've loved dancing all my life.
And I've dreamed of making it my profession.
But my parents wouldn't approve of it.
Even when you won the dance competition?!
If I go off the path they set for me,
they won't be happy.
My parents won't approve,
no matter how well I dance.
But if I reach the top as an idol
and get the public's approval,
even they would have to approve.
That's why I decided to become an idol.
But since I left the house like that,
I can't get any support from them,
nor will I accept any.
That's why I started working here.
I see...
I'm going to go back
since my break is about to end.
Okay!
Good luck!
That's amazing...
I would've given up already if I were her.
I'm so full of fear right now...
Chisa...
I'm sure Rei is scared, too.
There's no guarantee that she will succeed.
That's why she practices so much.
Over and over again, to vanish those fears.
Fears...
Sakura?
Morning, Kotono!
I saw Mr. Makino leave just a moment ago.
He was in a suit, so it must be work.
But it's the weekend! How tough...
Was something on your mind?
It just seemed like it...
Yup.
Will you lend me an ear?
Miss Ichinose and Chisa, huh?
Yup.
Miss Rei seems so busy, so I haven't
been able to talk to her too much.
I'm not sure what to do.
Saki's worried about Chisa, too.
She seems to have her mind set
on not interfering in matters
of the other group, though.
Oh, really?
She's not present during practice at times.
That leaves only Nagisa and me as the ones
who have to keep a handle on Mei,
so it's been a challenge.
You've been doing that, Kotono?
Why are you so surprised?
Because...
You're thinking that it's unlike me, right?
Sorry.
I am the leader, after all...
It's scary, but I need to do my best.
I see.
Hoshimi Production
I've gotta do my best, too!
Everyone!
Come see this!
Right? Isn't it amazing?!
This flower...
It's the nemophila.
But was it necessary to interrupt
practice to come see this?
Yup, this is really important for us.
Now, here's a question!
What is the flower language
behind the nemophila?
Flower language...?
"Success everywhere"...
That's right! Those are just the words
we need, don't you think?
Success... everywhere...
You're right.
When you see them in full bloom like this,
it feels really encouraging!
Miss Rei, I'm sorry about yesterday.
What?
I gave up and told myself I couldn't do it
before I even tried to work hard like you.
But I know I can't keep this up, either.
So, will you keep teaching me about dance?
Miss Chisa...
B-B-But Miss Rei...
Will you be a little less strict...?
Please...
I agree.
Rei can be a little scary during practice.
Spartan style... Demon coach.
The pressure is immense.
What?
See? That pressure.
Yup, yup, yup, yup...
Oh, yeah!
You think so, too, Miss Kawasaki?
I know!
Let's stop being formal, too.
It feels like it creates a little distance.
But...
I agree!
You can all call me "Haruko" from now on!
What? But Miss Haruko, you're our senior...
No, I'm your fellow!
But...
Just call me "Haruko"!
H-Haruko!
There you go!
Go on, the rest of you!
What...?
That's a bit...
But why?!
Okay.
Sakura.
Shizuku.
Chisa.
Miss Haruko.
Was that okay?
Yeah!
What?
Isn't it weird that I'm the only one
addressed with "Miss"?
I can't bring myself to
address my senior without it.
What?
Sakura, do something!
What?!
Is it my fault?
Hey, Chisa and Shizuku!
kirameki sagashite
fumidasu ippo wa kiseki ja nai
tomadoi mo mayoi mo mada kakaeta mama
sore mo ii ne warau kimi ni sukoshi sunetari shite
itsunomanika itsumo no jibun ni naru
fushigi da keredo
kimi dake
kirameki no naka e
hizashi no atataka sa tsutsumarete
kagayaki no naka e
tsuki yo ni mo rinto sake
mabushisugiru kurai hoshi yo kagayake Shinin' Star
Mr. Makino, we're ready!
All right.
Hey! There you are!
What are you doing?!
A group photo?
Nice!
I wanna be in it, too!
Mei, wait!
Don't get in the way!
I am sure you want me in the center, right?
Suzu, not you, too.
It's fine!
Let's all take one together!
Gosh.
All right, ready?
Separate Lights, One Feeling